Chapter 1532 – Union of Phoenix and Dragon

Lin Ming stiffened. Xiao Moxian’s words echoed in his heart and stirred an inexplicable pain. He felt that this love was too heavy, something he could not afford to bear.

“I… am not deserving enough for you to do this. If Senior Demondawn were to find out about all this then how would you continue to hold your head up high in the monster race and demon race?”

If the demon and monster races really did sign a pact with the saints then Xiao Moxian might be married off to the Good Fortune Saint Son. If so, then Xiao Moxian deciding by herself to make love to Lin Ming today would be a great crime of betraying her own people. Not only would Empyrean Demondawn lose all face with his race, but so would Xiao Moxian!

“It’s enough as long as I think you are deserving!” Xiao Moxian sobbed, her voice cracking as she vented her grievances. She grasped Lin Ming, saying to him, “Why do you have to bring up these matters, why do you have to bring up my grandfather? Today is only today. Can’t you stop lying to me and make me happy? I won’t think about what the future brings nor do I want to.”

Xiao Moxian began to strip off her clothes as she spoke. Her fingers trembled as she undid her ties and her upper clothes began to fall off, revealing her smooth neck and snow white skin.

“My body, my primordial yin and phoenix blood, countless people have desired them. I give you my body without asking for anything in return and without caring for what the future may bring… as long as you want it.”

Xiao Moxian’s eyes were wet with tears and her cheeks were blushing red. With a flick of her finger, all of the clothes she wore burst into flames!

The brilliant flames flashed, burning her clothes into fading ash. Then, her body, the delicate and supple body of a young woman, pressed up against Lin Ming, leaving a shine in his eyes.

Her slender waist, her slender thighs, Xiao Moxian was filled with the beauty of a young woman in her prime, an enchanting beauty as mesmerizing as the brightly lit moon…

Underneath the endless starry skies, starlight sprinkled down on Xiao Moxian’s perfect body, covering her with a faint veil like liquid mercury. In that moment, Lin Ming’s breath caught in his throat. The Xiao Moxian in front of him was far too beautiful, far too dazzling, making it impossible for anyone to look straight at her.

Xiao Moxian pressed her finger against Lin Ming. Before he could respond, his clothes also burnt away, leaving them exposed to each other without the slightest barrier of clothing.

An unspeakably soft touch, the atmosphere of a young girl that could enthrall anyone, all of this challenged the final bit of brightness in Lin Ming’s mind.

Loving lips kissed Lin Ming. Two soft white arms slid around his back like snakes. In that moment, Lin Ming nearly lost his mind.

Even though Xiao Moxian didn’t ask for any result between them in freely offering her body today, Lin Ming wasn’t willing to have Xiao Moxian lose all standing within her two races.

To a girl, especially one considered a Saintess in the eyes of the monster and demon races, reputation was extremely important. With Lin Ming’s personality, he refused to ruin her good name.

But...

Perhaps he had the ability to change things!

If he was strong enough then he could be the one to give Empyrean Demondawn and the Monster Emperor what they wanted. If he could do this then he could reverse their situation with the saint race and there would be no need to sacrifice Xiao Moxian!

In that moment, Lin Ming felt a firm resolve in his heart, one that he had never felt as deeply before. He needed strength! He needed strength beyond strength!

And, the premise to achieving all of this was…

If he could face Tian Mingzi and survive!

As all of this passed through his mind, Lin Ming growled. He picked up Xiao Moxian from his body and pressed her to him. His hands recklessly roamed over her body, feeling all over her without anything separating them.

He could feel the softness pressing against his chest. He affectingly traced her back, traced her curved bottom, and stroked her soft thighs.

Sensing the sudden change in Lin Ming’s thoughts, Xiao Moxian felt as if she was melting. She enthusiastically responded by sucking on Lin Ming’s skin.

Her warm tongue lapped up Lin Ming, teasing him all over. The desires within Lin Ming exploded like a volcano. Finally, he couldn’t bear it anymore and thrust into her body.

Xiao Moxian cried out as a strange and aching feeling passed through her. She could feel that there was no barrier that existed between her and Lin Ming fusing together. She had no idea why she cried out, but she wasn’t able to suppress it from echoing out of her throat.

She stretched out a shivering hand and stroked Lin Ming’s cheek. “Lin Ming, do you know? If we were to die in the next moment I would not be afraid of anything at all.”

“You won’t die. We will live on, I’m sure of this!”

Lin Ming’s voice was firm. He thrust into Xiao Moxian’s body, again and again.

The energy within Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian became turbulent. The phoenix blood essence that entered Lin Ming’s body finally fused together with the two yang energies, rushing into him like a tide.

As for the power of blood vitality inherited from the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone and the ancient Black Dragon energy that he absorbed from the God Beast Tomb array formation, all of that poured into Xiao Moxian.

This energy flooded through Xiao Moxian’s body, intertwining with the waves of pleasure that coursed through her as she made love to Lin Ming. Xiao Moxian cried out again and again, unable to her prevent groans from leaking out from her overwhelmed senses.

Her face was like a red tide, flirtatious and loving. Through the blending of their blood vitality, not only did Xiao Moxian not lose any phoenix blood essence but the yin yang harmony within her began to rapidly rise and her inner world constantly expanded.

From the peak of the Divine Transformation realm, she was nearing the Divine Lord realm!

Xiao Moxian had absorbed a massive amount of the grandmist spirit bead essence. However, she still hadn’t been able to break through to the Divine Lord realm. For some reason, she had been missing just the tiniest spot. Now, she finally understood that her failure wasn’t because she hadn’t accumulated enough energy, but because the Grandmist Spirit Bead essence was far too yang attributed. If she couldn’t achieve yin yang harmony then it would have been near impossible for her to make a breakthrough.

A brilliant divine light began to shine out from Xiao Moxian’s lower abdomen, completely surrounding her and Lin Ming. Beneath the cover of this light, Xiao Moxian’s strength rapidly rose!

Woosh!

The remaining Grandmist Spirit Bead essence was summoned out by Lin Ming. It dissolved in the air, turning into two mighty streams of gray energy that submerged into Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian’s bodies. Thus, the Grandmist Spirit Bead essence had been completely absorbed by Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian!

In that moment, the endless starlight of the universe gathered around Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian, forming a swirling whirlpool of dreamy starlight around them.

In this sort of enthralling and confusing environment, Lin Ming made love to his heart’s content. He kissed Xiao Moxian’s lips, kissed her slender pale neck, and kissed her bright red nipples.

All the energy within his body merged together with Xiao Moxian as one. But compared to Xiao Moxian, Lin Ming’s harvests were far greater!

The energy brought forth by Xiao Moxian’s primordial yin blood was different from the Grandmist Spirit Bead essence that Lin Ming absorbed as well as the strength sealed within the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone. However, these energies weren’t much stronger. With a pure strength joining with them, all of this power came into equilibrium, fusing together in Lin Ming’s body where he could utilize all of it!

His mortal body began to subtly change. His broken meridians began to regenerate, becoming even tougher than before. His skeleton developed a crystalline luster and even his battle spirit that had been stranded at the early blue soul realm seemed as if it would make another breakthrough!

Anf!

A resonant dragon roar echoed out. From between Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian, the phantom of an Azure Dragon flew upwards. But following that, there was also a clear phoenix cry as a Dark Phoenix phantom shot up into the skies. The True Dragon and True Phoenix danced in the void, both of them rejoicing in life.

The True Dragon phantom was flooded with thunder and flame. As for the Dark Phoenix phantom, it was filled with pitch black flames, flames that seemed as if they could burn down the world.

“This fiery atmosphere, these are the flames that Xiao Moxian has comprehended, the phoenix nirvana true flame!”

In that instant, Lin Ming obtained a deeper comprehension of fire. Lin Ming’s attainments in the Concept of Fire had been at the sixth level; he had been stuck at this boundary for an extremely long time.

No matter what Law it was, the further one’s comprehensions were, the more difficult it was to comprehend more. But now, as Lin Ming made love to Xiao Moxian and their energies joined together without reserve, Lin Ming was able to deeply experience the true meaning of Xiao Moxian’s phoenix flames. His Concept of Fire pressed up against the threshold of the seventh level!

Ka ka ka!

Meanwhile, beneath Lin Ming, Xiao Moxian’s inner world was experiencing earth-shattering changes. The boundaries of her inner world broke apart and endless starlight and boundless energy rushed in, nourishing this world!

This energy formed origin energy clouds in the skies, followed by origin energy rain!

Underneath the revitalization of this origin energy rain, all the myriad lives began to regenerate. All sorts of spirit trees and spirit grasses grew with glee. In just several short breaths of time, lingzhi and ginsengs grew to the ages of tens of thousands of years. There were even some spirit grasses that developed their own spirits, forming plump fruits like little porcelain dolls that fell to the ground and began racing and hopping about in joy.

Xiao Moxian had finally broken into the Divine Lord realm!

Moreover, she was a Divine Lord that far surpassed others at her step. In terms of the essence gathering system alone, Xiao Moxian was no worse than Lin Ming.

In the breakthrough process, Xiao Moxian’s body became increasingly hot. This type of heat transmitted through Lin Ming’s loins, giving him an indescribably pleasurable feeling. Finally, with a loud roar, he released his life essence into her.

Xiao Moxian stubbornly held onto Lin Ming’s back. At this time, her entire body was flushed red as if she were burning up. She opened her eyes, her vision blurry, as if she found all of this extremely satisfying and yet extremely painful.

“Lin Ming, I’m hot, so hot…”

Xiao Moxian clutched onto Lin Ming in the throes of passion. This tempting scene nearly caused Lin Ming’s blood to surge again, making him want to take hold of her and make wild love to her once more.

However, Lin Ming still retained a certain clarity in his mind. He could feel that something was off with the current situation. Xiao Moxian had just broken into the Divine Lord realm so she should be radiating energy and joy, with her strength soaring to the heavens. Yet why was her body releasing such a burning heat that even her consciousness was blurred?

As he probed Xiao Moxian’s body with his divine sense, Lin Ming was immediately shocked. Within Xiao Moxian’s inner world as well as her meridians, she was flooded with flames. This power of fire became increasingly wild and intense, as if it wanted to burn her to the ground.

Lin Ming also came from the Ancient Phoenix Clan and had pure phoenix blood essence fused into his body. Although it was much weaker than his Azure Dragon blood within him, Lin Ming was considered relatively knowledgeable about phoenixes. He immediately understood just what Xiao Moxian’s situation meant.

“Nirvana… this is a phoenix’s nirvana…”

Lin Ming was dumbfounded. At this time, Xiao Moxian was actually experiencing her phoenix nirvana!!

Chapter 1537 – Fighting Tian Mingzi

Tian Mingzi’s complexion changed as he saw that Lin Ming’s strength had greatly increased. Although he had overdrawn his blood vitality and his boundary had dropped, a skinny camel was still larger than a horse. This sword strike of his was able to instantly kill a peak Holy Lord, but Lin Ming with his early Divine Lord realm cultivation had been able to easily block it!

Although Tian Mingzi had only used 30% of his strength there, didn’t Lin Ming also not use his complete strength?

“You…” Tian Mingzi’s lips shook as he spoke. An inconceivable possibility appeared in his mind, but only this possibility could reasonably explain what just happened!

“You… you broke through the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace!?”

As Tian Mingzi looked at Lin Ming now, his eyes were filled with fear and dread!

Lin Ming was far too fearful, fearful to the point that it suffocated him!

Originally, Tian Mingzi with his Great World King cultivation had joined forces with an ordinary World King, two half-step World Kings, some guides and underlings, and later even a half-step Empyrean. This amazingly mighty lineup of martial artists had been used to hunt down a late Divine Transformation realm martial artist through the God Burying Ridge. That could simply be called the most ludicrous joke in the world. If news of this were to ever spread out then they would all be laughed at as idiots who tried to kill a chicken with an oxen knife.

Not even hunting down a strong World King would require such a luxurious lineup!

However, this amazing lineup of individuals, in hunting down a single junior, had met an unexpected result!

First, they had forced Lin Ming into Tragic Death Valley, a land that no one had ever emerged from for 10 billion years. However, not only did Lin Ming leave unscathed but he had also obtained massive benefits, benefits that allowed him to break into the Divine Lord realm!

Even a Divine Lord realm martial artist still wasn’t worthy to be chased by such a strong group. Once they found him they could instantly crush him to death!

But following that, Lin Ming had lured them all into a danger zone, using all sorts of traps and methods in addition to his own terrifying combat strength to kill them all off one at a time!

If Ash Murder, Mister Zhou, and all the others who came before had made the grave mistake of underestimating their opponent, then Tian Mingzi could be said to have treated his with the utmost sincerity, stopping at nothing to ensure victory. He hadn’t even hesitated to use up his own blood essence and even then he had only caused Lin Ming to receive heavy wounds and be forced back into Primordius Heavenly Palace. Afterwards, he had even used his heart demon blood curse so that Lin Ming’s heart demons would burst out during his breakthrough and he would perish.

But, the reality was that Lin Ming had closed up in Primordius Heavenly Palace and had broken through to the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, allowing his strength to reach unprecedented heights!

This Lin Ming had been set in death trap after death trap but had found the path to survival, making it so that no one could summon the courage to face him!

Even if Tian Mingzi were a Great World King, he was also the same.

However, now that matters had come to this step it was impossible for him to retreat. He had severely damaged his life source and if he didn’t kill Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian now then it was likely he would fall to the boundary of an ordinary World King in the future. Not just that, but his lifespan would be damaged and it would be nearly impossible to progress a single inch forwards in his future cultivation. To Tian Mingzi, this was a fate worse than death!

Now, in this sealed off space, it was either he would perish or they would die!

“Good! Very good!” Tian Mingzi’s eyes were dignified. Although his words seemed confident, he lacked any assurance in his heart. If he were in his peak state then no matter what breakthroughs Lin Ming made he could still easily suppress him. But now, he had lost all grasp of the situation because he simply didn’t know how strong a martial artist would become after reaching the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace!

There was simply no reference target for this. This was because the saints didn’t cultivate the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace; their race had a body transformation technique that was easier and suited them more. Thus, it could be said that within the current universes of the 33 Layered Heavens, only Lin Ming had reached the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. His achievements could not be replicated!

Facing this enemy that he didn’t understand at all, Tian Mingzi could only try his best!

Tian Mingzi spread out his arms. Behind him, the phantom of a demon god formed. All of the surrounding heaven and earth origin energy gathered towards this demon god!

A Great World King was still a Great World King. Even after being reduced to such a state he could still display such a powerful technique.

Tian Mingzi shot out the black sword in his hands. This sword seemed to turn into a black snake, winding through the air before falling into the hands of this demon god phantom.

Tian Mingzi had given his sword to the demon god phantom!

Seeing this, Lin Ming was startled. He could faintly feel that Tian Mingzi’s sword was extremely unusual. Its shape was strange, with the blade being longer than an adult male was high, and yet the blade was as narrow as a flower petal. It was difficult to apply any sort of force with this sword and thus difficult to understand why any refining master would design a sword like this.

But seeing this demon god phantom gradually take shape in the air, Lin Ming was able to speculate that this demon god phantom wasn’t summoned by Tian Mingzi, but had always been sealed within the sword!

Then, Tian Mingzi struck his chest with his fist and spat out a mouthful of blood into the demon god phantom. As this demon god phantom absorbed Tian Mingzi’s blood, it became increasingly real and its expression became increasingly fierce!

Witnessing this scene, Lin Ming felt his heart skip a beat. Tian Mingzi had actually used his own blood to raise this demon! In the legends, there were witches and shamans that raised poisonous bugs in their body, feeding them with their own flesh and blood. This demon that Tian Mingzi released was in a similar situation.

“Hahaha! Lin Ming! This demon slave that I carefully raised is for when my true self has been severely wounded! It can display 50% of my peak strength! You can die now!”

Tian Mingzi raved. Then, the demon god phantom hurtled forwards, billowing demonic energy that surged all about it, condensing into ash gray pythons that twisted above the sword before cutting straight down!

“A demon slave with 50% of your combat strength?”

Hearing Tian Mingzi’s wild laughter, Xiao Moxian was shocked. A Great World King truly did have endless methods to use; she never imagined Tian Mingzi would have such a backup plan. Just from looking at the billowing demon energy of that demon god phantom, she could see just how strong it was!

A demon slave with 50% of Tian Mingzi’s peak combat strength? How could she and Lin Ming block it?

And as Xiao Moxian’s mind wavered, the demon slave roared out loud and rushed towards Lin Ming. A terrifying demon will turned into a beam of dark light that shot into Xiao Moxian’s spiritual sea. This was the heart demon seal that Tian Mingzi had used before!

Without being weakened by Primordius Heavenly Palace’s array formation, this heart demon blood seal was over ten times more powerful than before!

“Be careful!”

Just as this heart demon was about to enter Xiao Moxian’s mind, Lin Ming’s voice cracked in her ear like a shocking thunderclap!

In his voice, he had fused the Divine Mist Heart Mantra, using the Laws of the soul forging system to block the heart demon blood seal that was trying to drill into Xiao Moxian!

“Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel!”

Lin Ming’s spear swept out and drew a dao diagram in the air. This dao diagram had countless demons sealed within it, all of them fierce and dreadful!

Rumble rumble rumble!

The dao diagram revolved, suppressing and smashing apart the heart demon blood seal like a massive grinding pan!

Xiao Moxian’s mind shook. Only then did she free herself from the shackles of the heart demon.

She was startled by what had just happened; she had almost fallen into Tian Mingzi’s trap.

“He’s lying to you!” Lin Ming quickly said to Xiao Moxian with a true essence sound transmission.

Xiao Moxian eyebrows shot up. She immediately understood what Lin Ming was saying!

Perhaps Tian Mingzi might have really raised a demon slave so he could bring it out whenever his true self was injured. But, the strength of this demon slave wasn’t as formidable as Tian Mingzi had described.

The reason for this was that Tian Mingzi had to face the iron-armored spectral soldier array and had repeatedly burnt his blood essence to defeat them. If this demon slave really did possess 50% of his peak strength then why would he need to burn his blood essence now?

In other words, Tian Mingzi had already used this demon slave to deal with the iron-armored spectral soldier array, causing the origin energy of the demon slave to be severely damaged and its strength to have lowered.

But no matter what the truth was, Tian Mingzi was simply making empty claims about this demon slave.

And there was only one reason he did this. He wanted to produce a brief moment where Xiao Moxian’s mind wavered so he could use a heart demon blood seal to invade her spiritual sea and stoke her heart demons!

“Guard your mind. This Tian Mingzi wants to deal with you first so he can suck up your phoenix blood essence to recover his own strength and then deal with me!”

Lin Ming quickly said. Xiao Moxian grimaced. This Tian Mingzi was far too sinister!

But, one couldn’t blame Xiao Moxian for being too careful in thinking this. Tian Mingzi’s acting was far too real, and in addition to his Great World King boundary, it was easy to believe that he had some ultimate hidden card in his hands.

Bang!

At this moment, the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel released an explosive sound. After it crushed the demon heart blood seal to dust, it began grinding down on the demon slave!

Lin Ming stepped on space. As he raised his hands, tremendous supernatural powers rushed forwards with overwhelming momentum!

He grasped the Phoenix Blood Spear and pointed it straight between the demon slave’s eyebrows. “All demons in this world, be received into the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, never to enter samsara, forever and ever imprisoned to be used by me!”

“Uwooo!”

The Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel flew forwards like a horrifying spinning saw wheel. The demon slave released heart-rending screams as the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel tore into its body!

Xiao Moxian’s thoughts were right. This demon slave, in its peak state, might have had 40-50% of Tian Mingzi’s strength. However, because Tian Mingzi needed to break through the iron-armored spectral soldier array as soon as possible so he could hinder Lin Ming’s breakthrough, he had summoned the demon slave, greatly consuming its energy. Now, it was far inferior to how it was in the past!

Xiao Moxian watched as the demon slave was cut apart. Lin Ming’s words were like the proclamation of heaven, seeming as if he were ordering the slave demon to be sucked into the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. She couldn’t help but feel admiration at Lin Ming’s combat strength.

Xiao Moxian had broken into the Divine Lord realm and had completed her first phoenix nirvana; currently, her strength wasn’t too far off from Lin Ming’s. But, in terms of true combat experience, the Xiao Moxian who grew up in Demondawn Heavenly Palace was far inferior to the likes of Lin Ming and Tian Mingzi, who wandered the world in search of adventures, experiencing countless dangerous life or death situations. Even if their strength was similar, the combat strength that Xiao Moxian could display on the battlefield was far inferior to Lin Ming’s.

As she admired Lin Ming, Xiao Moxian also felt an indescribable affection towards him. Even though she was a proud daughter of heaven who possessed a nearly unrivalled talent and had even completed her first nirvana during the Divine Lord realm, or even if she were to become a True Divinity in the future, when she was with Lin Ming she knew that he would always stand in front of her, forever protecting her and giving her an inexplicable sense of safety.

Chapter 1540 – The Dust Settles

Seeing Tian Mingzi’s head roll to the ground, Xiao Moxian still felt that all of this was unreal. She recalled the last 10 years she had spent with Lin Ming, experiencing all sorts of drastic changes and upheavals, ups and downs that they crossed through with repeated life or death dangers. Finally, their strength rose by a large degree and they slowly killed those that had hunted them down. All of this was like an eternal dream.

Xiao Moxian even felt that these last 10 years were far more rich and passionate than all her life experiences before that. All of those dangers and hopes had become unforgettable memories etched into her bones.

And throughout all of these dangers, Xiao Moxian had only played a supporting role. But even so, she had obtained a massive harvest. It wasn’t just her cultivation and strength that had risen, but her mentality and will had evolved.

Looking at Lin Ming once more, he was the one who had helped lead her through all of this. In terms of how his mentality and strength had been a steady constant this entire time, there was no need to mention it.

Xiao Moxian could approximately guess that most of Lin Ming’s near 60 years of life had passed in such an environment. He had grown to where he was by experiencing endless adventures, battles, and life or death slaughters.

Xiao Moxian suddenly thought that it wasn’t strange for Lin Ming to have such achievements at his young age.

Lin Ming was only a martial artist from the lower realms and as he trained in martial arts he had to overcome all sorts of unfavorable conditions. Compared with the Empyrean descendants of the Divine Realm, Lin Ming was no different from an ant to an immortal being. However, it was these layers upon layers of difficulties that led to Lin Ming’s myth. Lin Ming’s experiences and his near 60 years of hardships were his most precious treasures! A treasure sword was sharpened through tempering and the fragrance of a plum blossom came with the freezing cold. All of these things that Lin Ming experienced were far from what any Empyrean descendant could compare with.

For instance, in these last ten years, if it weren’t Lin Ming who had undergone these experiences but some ordinary Empyrean descendant, even if their strength was the same as his they would have died countless times already.

Of course, Xiao Moxian was also well aware that Lin Ming’s current achievements were impossible without lucky chances and fortuitous encounters. She immediately remembered the sudden response that Tian Mingzi had displayed after seeing the Magic Cube.

Just what was that thing? Xiao Moxian was suddenly filled with curiosity.

At this time, Lin Ming had walked near Tian Mingzi’s corpse. He took Tian Mingzi’s spatial ring and then formed seals with his hands, summoning a vicious-looking dao diagram to his front.

“Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel!”

The Asura Heavenly Dao was not some orthodox cultivation method. The Asura Road Master’s life was also filled with slaughter and death. While this Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel could be used to attack an enemy, it could also be used to absorb an enemy’s essence energy for oneself.

Then, all of the essence energy in Tian Mingzi’s body was drawn out by the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel!

Even Ash Murder’s essence energy that had scattered into the air after his death was gathered by the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel!

These essence energies were Tian Mingzi and Ash Murder’s life essence. If Lin Ming didn’t gather them with the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, then after several tens of thousands of years, these essence energies sealed within Bai Qi’s tomb would slowly evolve into existences without any thoughts of their own. They would only be ghosts that knew to swallow others. In many mystic realms, these types of ghosts would be a source of grave danger.

Now that Lin Ming had sealed all of this essence energy into the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, this situation naturally wouldn’t happen.

“Essence energy of all living beings, be used by me!”

Lin Ming flicked his finger and the essence energy within the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel rerouted towards the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone!

Drawn out essence energy was more suitable to cultivate avatars. If it were Lin Ming’s true self then although absorbing these essence energies could increase the cultivation of his body, too much would leave behind hidden dangers within him. But, the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone was nourished from the infinite essence energy gathered by the God Beast Tomb array formation, thus there was no need to be careful with it.

Hu - !

In that instant, all of the essence energy poured into the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone. The Essence Spirit Embryo Stone’s entire body emitted crackling sounds as its muscles and organs wriggled about. All of this blood vitality was completely absorbed by it, and the strength and astral essence within the avatar continued to grow!

The body of the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone was similar to the saints’. In other words, it was an existence especially bred for body transformation.

Its cultivation method was also similar to the saints’. If one had to describe the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone’s cultivation base, then using the saint race’s Saint Lord boundary was more appropriate.

And after absorbing the essence energy of a Great World King and a half-step Empyrean, the astral essence within the avatar wildly circulated through its body, joining with the energy that was already within it to begin with. Without any hindrance, its cultivation rose by a small boundary.

This was something Lin Ming already expected.

The Essence Spirit Embryo Stone could easily rise in cultivation boundaries. Let alone a small boundary in the Saint Lord realm, there wouldn’t be a bottleneck even when entering the Holy Lord realm from the Saint Lord realm.

The only restriction to the avatar’s cultivation was Lin Ming’s own cultivation. In other words, if Lin Ming’s own cultivation was lacking then the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone would encounter a bottleneck. Moreover, if Lin Ming was much weaker than his avatar then he simply wouldn’t have the strength to control the much stronger Essence Spirit Embryo Stone.

Lin Ming let out a long sigh of relief as he finished. For Tian Mingzi and Ash Murder’s essence energy to be used by him after their death, they had truly died miserable.

“Lin Ming!”

Just as Lin Ming finished, Xiao Moxian blinked over and looked towards Lin Ming.

As Lin Ming met her playful eyes, his thoughts stirred. He was able to approximately guess what she was thinking of. He laughed, saying, “You want to ask me what the Magic Cube is, right?”

“What I want to know is… just what sort of thing allowed my lover to grow from a common martial artist from the lower realms into the number one talent of his race?” Xiao Moxian said, her eyes filled with curiosity. But, she suddenly changed the topic and said a bit contradictorily, “But, I don’t think you should tell me… this should be your life’s greatest secret, and if you tell me…”

Xiao Moxian dragged out her words, looking at Lin Ming all the while.

Lin Ming thought for a moment. Then, he straightened up and solemnly said, “This is indeed my greatest secret. But, the reason I was able to reach this step is not just the Magic Cube. The Magic Cube accompanied me during my youth when I first stepped on the road of martial arts and helped me traverse that most difficult period of my early road.

“Since I was willing to take out the Magic Cube during my battle with Tian Mingzi, I have no intentions of hiding the truth from you. Moreover, during this adventure through the Asura Road, I will slowly gain the power to protect the Magic Cube!”

Lin Ming’s current strength was high enough that he could defeat an ordinary World King. But, his trial through the Asura Road had yet to end. Lin Ming intended to continue to train here until he reached at least the late Divine Lord realm or half-step Holy Lord. Perhaps he would even wait until he broke through to the Holy Lord realm and was able to kill a Great World King before considering leaving.

At that time, Lin Ming would be able to fully refine the Primordius Gate and fully control Primordius Heavenly Palace. Then, by relying on this Empyrean spirit treasure, even if an Empyrean were to chase after him they still might not be able to kill him.

Only in that state would Lin Ming truly be able to freely wander the Divine Realm and display his skills in the upcoming great calamity!

Lin Ming raised his right hand and an ash gray cube floated into his palm, slowly revolving around, filled with a mystical aura.

He said, “Xian’er, this is the Magic Cube. I accidently obtained it when I was 15 years old, in a restaurant. At the time, I was working for the restaurant and –”

As Lin Ming was speaking, Xiao Moxian suddenly covered his mouth with her hand.

She grinned, “You don’t need to say anything. If you trust me enough to tell me your greatest secret, I am more than satisfied with that. Although I am curious, I don’t really need to know.

“When we leave the Asura Road I will have to return to Demondawn Heavenly Palace. If my parents, grandfather, or the Monster Emperor find out about what happened between us, then they will become enraged… moreover, there is my engagement with the Good Fortune Saint Son. If this matter were to become a problem then I would be confined to my quarters and not even the heavens know what would happen after that. If I know the secrets of your Magic Cube, then even if I don’t willingly reveal them, that doesn’t mean someone won’t use an arcane technique to learn information about you from me…”

Xiao Moxian had already considered this for a long time. As Lin Ming listened to this, he was silent for a while. “You… do you plan on returning to the monster race and demon race no matter what?”

If Xiao Moxian didn’t return to the monster and demon races and instead stayed within Lin Ming’s inner world, then no one would know about it.

Xiao Moxian lightly sighed. She nodded, “Yes. I will return, because they are my people…”

Xiao Moxian was a very independent and free-thinking woman. She was bold and brave, and if she favored something then she would recklessly pursue it no matter what others thought or said.

But at the same time, she would not degenerate into becoming a servile dependent of any man. She had her own martial art’s goal, her own pursuits, and her own faith in herself.

Just like Lin Ming who would never betray humanity, Xiao Moxian would not discard her own race. Although the future was filled with unknowns and uncertainties, she wouldn’t evade her future but face it head on.

“I understand.” Lin Ming gently embraced Xiao Moxian. “Let’s leave this place.”

Chapter 1550 – Undying Medicine

In order to prevent any more problems occurring, after Lin Ming bought his item he took a few more circles around and then bid his farewells to Yue Liuxing and Yue Qifeng. Together with Xiao Moxian, he left the Divine Runic Masters Guild.

“Lin Ming, what is that thing you bought?” Xiao Moxian couldn’t help but ask Lin Ming with a sound transmission as soon as they left. Her curiosity had gotten the better of her.

“If I’m not wrong then this should be something left behind by the Asura Road Master.” Lin Ming honestly replied. Xiao Moxian was startled upon hearing this. The Asura Road Master!

In the Asura Road, the Asura Road Master was the true divine god. Anything related to him, even if it was only a tiny fragment, was astoundingly valuable. No wonder Lin Ming had tried so hard to buy this piece of broken jade.

“What use does this have?”

“I have no idea at present. But no matter what, we’re headed back to Heaven’s Secret for now!”

“You want to return to Heaven’s Secret?” Xiao Moxian asked, surprised. They had just left from there not too long ago. “What do you want to go to Heaven’s Secret for?”

“There’s some information I need. This information is extremely important for me to learn the divine runic arts.”

The divine runic arts were broad and all-encompassing. In order to study them, one needed to invest a massive amount of time and energy while accumulating a tremendous amount of knowledge and experience. What Lin Ming lacked the most now was time. Even if he had the Asura Sutra supporting him, it was impossible to do all of this overnight, and if all of this took too much time then it was meaningless to Lin Ming.

After several hours, Lin Ming arrived at Heaven’s Secret once more. This time, Lin Ming had chosen to change his appearance.

Although Heaven’s Secret sold all sorts of information, what they wouldn’t reveal was what sort of information their guests had inquired about. This was one of the most basic rules of an intelligence network, otherwise there would be no guest that would be able to ask for information in confidence, lest they be looked up by others.

Even so, Lin Ming felt it was safe to change his appearance. After all, the information he was seeking now was highly sensitive.

“Sir, what would you like to inquire about?” The doorman asked Lin Ming at the entrance to Heaven’s Secret.

“Divine runic masters.”

“What rank?”

“Fifth rank and above.”

“Then please go to the fifth floor.” The doorman respectfully said. This was the same floor as last time.

After reaching the fifth floor with Xiao Moxian, Lin Ming took up the wooden sign marked with ‘people’ and then was led to the corresponding room.

In this room, there was a blue-clothed old man waiting for Lin Ming.

The old man sat in the back of the room, separated from guests by a hanging curtain. He spoke to Lin Ming through this curtain.

“What would you like to know?” The old man’s voice was hoarse and gritty, as if he were in the waning years of his life.

“I want information on divine runic masters and alchemists. I do not want any divine runic masters from the Divine Runic Masters Guild. They must live outside of Divine Rune City and should preferably have strange and eccentric personalities. They need to be people who have committed all sorts of sinful and evil deeds. I need their location, their cultivation methods, their cultivation boundaries, an approximation of their strength, what influences support them, and all other related information! Moreover, the divine runic masters should be at the fifth grade or above. At the very least they must be at the fourth grade!”

The blue-clothed old man was surprised as he listened to Lin Ming. “The information you want is extremely detailed so our price will be very high. This is also because if we betray the information of these individuals, our Heaven’s Secret might offend them.”

Heaven’s Secret was an intelligence network and thus they inevitably collected information on great influences and important figures. If they sold this information to others they were likely to offend them, especially if they sold this information to their enemies or other hostile groups. Thus, Heaven’s Secret would be very careful with what sort of information they sold. If they couldn’t offend the individual, then they would never sell the information no matter how high the price. As for those that they could offend, the price would be exorbitantly high.

An intelligence network was involved in all aspects of the world. If their background wasn’t deep enough and they aroused the anger of some people, it was possible that they would be dug up and eliminated!

“Information on divine runic masters is sensitive to begin with. There are often many complex relationships behind these divine runic masters. Luckily, you don’t want any information about divine runic masters that are a part of the Divine Runic Masters Guild, otherwise no matter how many origin energy runes you offered we still wouldn’t sell it to you. If you want information on divine runic masters that have been exiled outside of Divine Rune City, then I can actually provide some information to you. There are a few pieces of information I have which aren’t too involved with the greater influences. Each piece of information will be charged according to the detail as well as the grade of the divine runic master and they will be around 500 million to 700 million origin energy runes each.”

As the blue-clothed old man said these words, even though Lin Ming had already been prepared for this, he still felt his heart drip blood.

This was indeed ridiculously expensive! Although he was wealthy, during all his years in the Asura Road, he had never earned money, only spent it, and he had spent a great deal of it too. Lin Ming didn’t have too many nine sun jades left on him.

Lin Ming took out a piece of white jade and poured his divine sense into it, further detailing his requests. He wanted to know their strength, cultivation, moral behavior, temperament, and so forth. He also only wanted those evil and demonic people. As for divine runic masters that were highly respected and noble characters, he didn’t want them at all.

After the blue-clothed old man looked through the white jade, he said, “There are a total of three individuals that match your request. The total price will be 1.6 billion!”

“Mm…”

Lin Ming took a deep breath and fished out some nine sun jades from his spatial ring. After he lined them up, he said, “Tell me everything.”

“Alright!”

The blue-clothed old man wrote down three sections of information on a jade slip.

Lin Ming took the jade slip and recorded all the information in his mind. Then, he and Xiao Moxian left Heaven’s Secret…

……………….

100,000 miles southeast of Divine Rune City, there was a remote mountain. People rarely visited this mountain, and deep in a valley of it was a lake that stretched for ten miles, named Star Lake.

As night arrived each evening, Star Lake would be filled with the night winds. The reflection of starlight would shine down on the lake, making it seem like a stretch of liquid silver, beautiful to the eyes.

On one side of Star Lake was an ancient castle.

This castle was built with obsidian, and had already stood here for 100,000 years. A part of the castle extended into the lake, leaving a black reflection on the surface. Looking at this black reflection, one felt a sense of peace and quiet.

However, no one imagined that such a beautiful and wondrous place was in truth a den of darkest evils…

Within the castle, there was a completely sealed off space. The floors were made of pale red tiles and the walls were dark gray. Pill furnaces and divine runic tables were scattered all about, making it seem messy and chaotic.

On these stone tables and on the walls, there were black stains. These stains were left by dried up blood.

In the center of this space, there was a row of metal frames, dozens of them altogether. But, what was startling was that on every metal frame, there was a young girl tied up.

These young girls were in rags and some were even naked. The oldest of them were in their twenties, and there were even those that were 16-17. The youngest among them looked to be around 11-12, with a few 13-14 year olds placed throughout.

Every girl was covered with scars. These scars were found on their necks, thighs, chests, stomachs, and wrists. There were knife wounds, scratches, and even bite marks.

Some wounds were intentionally afflicted, and some seemed specifically designed to let out blood.

After suffering for such a long time, all of these girls were in the depths of despair, their eyes without light, like dying embers. If it weren’t for their faint heartbeat and breathing, one might even think that they were dead.

Although they had been tortured into such states, one could still the beauty that hid behind their dirty faces and disheveled hair. It was clear that these were once proud beauties of different races.

There were humans, monsters, demons, and even saints!

In fact, not only were they beauties of different races, but there were those amongst them with relatively high levels of martial talent! Some had special physiques, variation bloodlines, or variation dantians.

Some girls were martial artists. There were those at the Xiantian realm, and even some at the Revolving Core realm.

But now, their cultivations had been sealed away; they were no different from ordinary mortal girls.

If one were to send these girls to large influences, then although they might not have been peak geniuses, they should still have become inner court disciples. If one raised them with enough effort, then there were high chances that they would reach the Divine Lord realm in the future!

But now, all of that was impossible. Their lives would be buried in the horrendous and despairing castle.

Some of these people had been kidnapped, and some had been bought as slaves.

Of them, most were mortals that had never cultivated before. They were simply unable to withstand the inhuman torture. Without a doubt, they would die from suffering in just several months.

But those who cultivated had already been trapped in this castle for several years. After being tortured night and day for several years, the average person would have suffered mental collapse or died. But, the master of this castle was an alchemist, and with all sorts of miracle pills and medicines, wanting to die was nearly impossible. This castle master would even use dangerous pills to heighten the cultivation boundary of these girls, digging out their life potential and then stealing it away.

What awaited them was a lifetime of endless suffering and pain. Only when their essence energy and blood vitality was sucked dry, only when their youth and strength had faded, would they be abandoned and buried in the back gardens of the castle. Seemingly because of the presence of their skeletons, the flowers in the back gardens bloomed especially bright.

At this time, the space barriers of this hidden space suddenly shook violently. A man’s roar echoed out within it!

“Trash! Trash! Damn it all!”

Bang!

With an explosive sound, something seemed to detonate. Stone tables were flipped over and pill furnaces were tossed away, bouncing all over. A pale man with grayish white hair rushed in like a rabid beast.

This man wore tattered robes and he looked to be middle-aged, but, there was not a trace of blood on his face and a faint death aura percolated around his body.

This meant that his life was nearing its end.

“I failed, I failed again! The Life Lifting Undying Pill, just how many times have I failed!?” The man’s eyes were blood red, seeming as if he were about to go crazy! He was a spiritas, but the faint soul glow that symbolized the soul race had already vanished. This was a sign that his fires of life had diminished and his life was nearing its end… he would have at most another hundred years to live.

He dreamed to refine an Endless Life Immortality Pill. For this pill, he had refined for 10,000 years already. He thought that he would never be able to successfully complete the refining of this pill before he died, thus in the last several hundred years, he had been refining the lower quality Life Lifting Undying Pill. He wanted to lengthen his life, even if it were only by several hundred years!

Chapter 1552 – Divine Runic Master Shortcut

“Who are you?”

To be ambushed just as he was about to rape someone, Torchriver was burning with rage. His eyes were blood red, as if he wanted to devour Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian.

But at this time, he noticed Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian’s cultivations.

They were only at the Divine Lord realm!?

Were they hiding their cultivation?

No, that wasn’t right… they were extraordinary young elites!

Torchriver had raped countless women in his life, and he usually only preyed on young girls. Thus, he was very sensitive to the life auras that surrounded young girls so he could confirm that Xiao Moxian wasn’t very old.

So young, and yet they had reached the Divine Lord realm; just how had they cultivated!?

This discovery caused Torchriver’s eyes to shine brilliantly.

“A variation bloodline! She must possess a variation bloodline! A proud daughter of heaven and she also has a variation bloodline! If I can use her blood as medicine and eat her up every day then perhaps I really might be able to heal the wound to my divine soul. I will be able to live for thousands more years and complete my immortality pill!”

Torchriver suddenly cackled, “The heavens haven’t abandoned me, they haven’t abandoned me! What I lack is a proud daughter of heaven for my alchemy, and yet you have delivered yourself right to my door! Good! Very good! You will become my living furnace. We shall dual cultivate every day and I will bring you to paradise!

As Torchriver spoke, he lewdly stared at Xiao Moxian.

This caused Xiao Moxian to nearly burst apart with rage!

“Lin Ming, dig out his eyes, slice out his tongue, and cripple his cultivation! I want to slice off his flesh and slowly torture him for a hundred years, a thousand years with every slice!

Xiao Moxian came from a demon and monster bloodline to begin with; she was no blindly puerile and benevolent person. How could she allow herself to be insulted in such a way!

“Haha, if I haven’t misunderstood then you are only two martial artists at the Divine Lord realm. Your talent is a bit better than those of your generation, and yet you think you can kill me? You are insane! Even though my cultivation boundary has dropped I am still a half-step World King! Catching you two is the same as catching two chickens!”

Torchriver raved. He turned to Lin Ming and chortled again and again, “Is this your little lover boy? Very well, then I shall use him for my alchemy right in front of you!”

Before Torchriver finished speaking, his complexion suddenly changed. He could feel a vast and deep killing intent cover him. Then, the surrounding world changed. The world fell away, the stars vanished, and everything was isolated from him. He was completely trapped in a sealed off space!

“Force field!?”

Torchriver immediately realized that this black-clothed youth had surrounded him with a force field. For such a genius, it wasn’t a surprise if they had a force field. But, what astonished Torchriver was that this force field formed an incomparably stable space, far surpassing the limits of any Divine Lord realm martial artist. There were even many Holy Lords who couldn’t compare to this!

“Interesting, such talent even causes me to be more inspired to turn you into a pill!” Torchriver said, brilliantly staring at Lin Ming.

Lin Ming coldly sneered, “The information that Heaven’s Secret gave me said that you have already fallen to the brink of madness, but now it seems that not only are you mad but you are also stupid. Your cultivation has fallen to a half-step World King, and with your fires of life nearly extinguished, even among half-step World Kings you are the weakest. A talented late Holy Lord martial artist would already be able to brutally murder you and yet you continue to dream on! Now die!”

As Lin Ming spoke, he hurtled himself forwards. Although his speed wasn’t fast, his figure was as calm and stable as a mountain!

Nine Stars of the Dao Palace – Purple Temple Dao Palace!

Lin Ming revolved his strength to the limit and smashed his spear down at Torchriver!

Because the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace had been lost for far too long a time, and in addition to the changes that occurred in the Heavenly Dao Laws, it had become extremely difficult to practice. But, this difficulty meant that it had become even stronger than before. Although there was no text that stated how the different levels of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace corresponded to the different ranks in the essence gathering system, Lin Ming could approximately confirm that opening a single star in the Nine Stars of the Dao palace far surpassed the early Divine Lord realm of the essence gathering system.

In other words, although Lin Ming appeared to be an early Divine Lord, the truth was that when he combined the cultivation of his body transformation and essence gathering systems, he already far surpassed that.

Torchriver naturally couldn’t understand Lin Ming’s Nine Stars the Dao Palace. He simply grinned, saying, “Since you want to die, allow me to help you along.”

Torchriver took out a deep red sword from his spatial ring and then slashed out at Lin Ming. He wanted to crush Lin Ming’s spear light and cut apart Lin Ming’s body at the same time!

However, just when his sword light came into contact with the Phoenix Blood Spear, Torchriver’s smile froze. The spear light he thought he could easily tear apart actually contained a horrifying strength beyond description. It was like this spear light was formed from heavy stars, able to collapse space and cut through galaxies!

Kacha!

With an explosive sound, Torchriver’s sword light shattered. The red spear thrust towards Torchriver’s chest!

This spear had locked down Torchriver and locked down the space around him. It was impossible to dodge!

Even Torchriver’s blood vitality rebelled, as if it wanted to break free from his body.

…What?

Seeing this spear light rush towards him, Torchriver immediately paled. He thought that killing a junior like Lin Ming would be as easy as turning his hand; he never imagined that this would be the result!

This youth’s strength was powerful beyond understanding. Although this spear hadn’t pierced him yet, what he knew was that even if he didn’t die, this spear strike would still severely wound him and cause him to lose all combat strength!

In this life or death moment, Torchriver punched his own chest and spat out a mouthful of blood essence. This blood essence formed a mysterious symbol in the air!

At the same time, Torchriver pulled out two divine runic symbols from his spatial ring. He thrust them outwards, causing them to burn in the air!

After these two divine runic symbols burned, they turned into a protective barrier that received Lin Ming’s spear strike!

Kacha!

With an explosive sound, Lin Ming’s Phoenix Blood Spear smashed into this translucent barrier.

In a brief moment, the barrier exploded and the spear continued thrusting ahead, driving into the blood symbol that Torchriver spat out.

And at this time, Lin Ming finally felt a tremendous existence. The Phoenix Blood Spear suddenly slowed down, startling Lin Ming. He had used an arcane technique to strengthen himself, causing the might of this strike to reach the power of five dragons, and yet he hadn’t been able to kill this Torchriver who had fallen in cultivation boundary and had nearly lost all his blood vitality!

Without a doubt, this was the work of the divine runic arts.

Torchriver had thrown out two divine runic symbols to lessen Lin Ming’s spear potential and had then used a divine runic symbol formed from his own blood to resist Lin Ming’s all-out strike. The divine runic arts could be used for more than assisting in alchemy; they could be used in combat.

However, relying on this alone was not enough to change Torchriver’s fate. As the Phoenix Blood Spear was blocked by the blood symbol, Lin Ming’s thoughts moved and a shadow rushed out from his inner world, hurtling towards Torchriver. This was Lin Ming’s Essence Spirit Embryo avatar!

It dwelled in Lin Ming’s inner world and could rush out at any time to fight.

After absorbing Tian Mingzi and the others’ blood energy, the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone had broken through yet another boundary. In terms of mortal bodily strength, it far surpassed Lin Ming!

Ca!

The Essence Spirit Embryo Stone thrust a spear towards Torchriver, aiming to take his head.

“Ahhh!”

Torchriver cried out in alarm, scared out of his mind. A single Lin Ming was already as terrifying as a life-reaping ghost. Only by sacrificing a great portion of his remaining life was he able to form this divine runic symbol of blood to barely resist the attack, and now another Lin Ming had appeared!

Peng!

With a cracking sound, Torchriver’s protective energy was unable to withstand the terrifying strength of the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone. In just a moment, Torchriver’s defenses collapsed and the avatar’s spear pierced through his chest.

The long spear penetrated through Torchriver’s body. In front of the horrifying strength of the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone, the frail mortal body of a spiritas was no different than paper.

A massive amount of flesh and bones were twisted by this dreadful strength. Torchriver’s body was pierced through like a water bag, blood leaking out from all over him.

“How is this possible…”

Torchriver’s eyes filled with despair and disbelief. He had been easily defeated by a mere Divine Lord junior and would die here… how could he accept such a ridiculous result?

Pulse Cutting Palm!

Lin Ming smashed his hand into Torchriver’s chest. A savage and wild true essence rushed through Torchriver’s body, tearing apart every single meridian within him and severing the power of his blood vitality.

In that moment, Torchriver’s body fell down from the air like a ragdoll. In a strange coincidence, he fell into the sealed space where the young girls were imprisoned.

Puff!

As the crippled Torchriver plopped to the floor, his blood splashed out. The young girls who were imprisoned stared helplessly on. This unbelievably powerful Torchriver had fallen to the ground like a dead dog, leaving all of them stunned.

Was this a dream?

Torchriver still had a single breath of life remaining. Lin Ming had intentionally kept Torchriver alive, because the shortcut for him to become a divine runic master was in Torchriver’s body.

Chapter 1553 – Refine the Soul

These girls that had been tortured by Torchriver over so many years had already anticipated that they would die here. They had lost themselves to despair long ago and there was nothing left that could stir anything in their hearts.

But at this moment, they saw that cruel and god-like Torchriver fall onto the floor in a completely inhuman mess, on the verge of death. Then, a faint spark of hope ignited in their stunned eyes.

After being beneath the agonizing abuse of Torchriver for so many years, even if they saw him about to die, they still couldn’t believe it. They were afraid that this was all a dream.

At this time, Lin Ming floated down with his long spear in hand. Seeing Lin Ming descend like a god from heaven, the young girls were left in a daze.

“You’re free…”

Lin Ming flicked his fingers and several true essence arrows shot forth, cutting the chains that shackled these young girls. Even the energy seals within their bodies were lifted.

The moment that their shackles were cut, because many of the girls were weak and their muscles had atrophied, they fell onto the floor. The pain from this fall finally made them believe that this scene in front of them was real and not a dream!

As they felt the rough ground, they also felt the freedom that they hadn’t had for such a long time. Their bodies shivered.

It wasn’t known who started crying out first, but the girls couldn’t help but weep one after another.

They didn’t know who this young man was, but in their hearts, this young man was their god and their savior. Even if they had to take care of him for their entire lives they were willing to do so. Even if this youth wanted them all to die here they would still comply without blinking. This was because when they were imprisoned by Torchriver, they didn’t even have the ability to commit suicide. They had lived a life worse than death!

Looking at these young girls, Lin Ming sighed in pity for them, lamenting their fates. Many of them had a decent talent for cultivating martial arts, but their lives were mostly destroyed.

Lin Ming flicked his fingers again and dozens of pills flew into the hands of these young girls. Lin Ming had given them miracle pills to make up for their lost blood vitality and to wash their marrow.

These young girls were abused by Torchriver and their blood vitality had been mostly sucked dry. Each of them had a pale white face and their yin energy was lacking. If they wanted to continue cultivating martial arts in this sort of condition, it would be impossibly difficult to do so.

Normally, the lower cultivation a martial artist was, the worse their bloodline was, the easier it was to make up for lost blood vitality. The higher one’s cultivation was, the greater one’s bloodline, and the more one’s talent defied the heavens, then the more difficult it would be to make up for lost blood vitality.

But as for martial artists with low cultivation, although it was relatively easy to make up for lost blood vitality, they were simply far too weak to find the necessary blood tonics and pills to do so. Thus, for a martial artist at a low cultivation to make up for lost blood vitality was extremely difficult. For these young girls, it was simply impossible.

However, this was a simple task for Lin Ming. To him, these pills weren’t precious at all, but to these starry-eyed girls, these were unrivalled miracle medicines!

Most of these young girls were common mortals. Even if they were to walk down the road of martial arts, they would only be able to reach the Pulse Condensation, Houtian, or Xiantian realms. To them a Heaven Opening Pill would be a priceless treasure, much less these miracle pills that Lin Ming handed out.

“Take these. These are all pills with moderate properties. Even though your bodies are weak, there won't be any side effects.”

Lin Ming gently said. As these girls held the miracle pills in their hands, their fingers began to shiver.

Although they didn’t know what grade these pills were, they could approximate their value from the rich medicinal fragrance wafting off them.

Because of this, there were some girls that held the pills tightly in their hands, not willing to swallow them.

Lin Ming sighed again as he saw this. This was the life of low level, mortal martial artists. To a high level martial artist, things that they casually tossed to the side of the road were incomparably precious treasures to these low level martial artists.

Lin Ming waved his hand once more and shot out some more pills. This time, the pills were thrust right into these girls’ mouths.

“Rest well. You all may leave whenever you wish, or you may also stay here. Three days from now, I will bring you to the nearest mortal city. I suggest that you wait, because the nearest mortal city is 10,000 miles away. Here is something to tide you over for the next few days.”

Lin Ming tossed out a bottle of fasting pills. This was the limit to which he could help these young girls. Their future days and the paths they chose to take would rely on themselves. After thinking some more, he said, “You all possess talent to cultivate the martial arts. In the future, if you can walk far down that road, then perhaps the bitter and painful experiences of your youths might not be a bad thing.”

As Lin Ming finished speaking he no longer delayed. He picked up the nearly dead Torchriver and flew away.

Left behind, the many young girls watched Lin Ming’s fading back, their eyes lost in thought. The fragrance of the medicinal pills was still in their mouths, and the warm medicinal efficacy nourished their bodies, soothing their pain. In their lives, this was probably the happiest moment they had experienced…

Sometimes, setbacks and frustrations weren’t bad. These experiences could allow a person to mature at the fastest speed possible. If a person grew up without experiencing any problems, then it was hard to temper their personality and will. Xiao Moxian was similar; only in the nine years within Tragic Death Valley had she matured in mind.

Lin Ming brought the near-dead Torchriver and went to the deepest depths of Star Lake. Here, he summoned Primordius Heavenly Palace and entered it along with Xiao Moxian.

“Lin Ming, what do you plan on doing?”

Xiao Moxian was confused. Why would Lin Ming spend so much money to purchase information on divine runic masters from Heaven’s Secret. Moreover, he had especially chosen evil and sinful divine runic masters. Could it be that he wanted to save the common people and eliminate future scourges? However, no matter what was said, they had indeed performed a good deed today.

“You’ll know in a bit. This is the first time I’ve tried this so I don’t know whether or not it will succeed.”

Lin Ming took a deep breath. He stretched out his right hand and then a cloud of darkness began to condense over his palm. In another several breaths of time, within this halo of black light, a dark gray cube slowly appeared, exuding a deep and mystical aura.

This was the Magic Cube.

After Lin Ming took out the Magic Cube, the dying and despairing Torchriver suddenly twitched like he had been bitten by a snake. His body immediately stiffened.

He stared at the Magic Cube with wide eyes that were filled with utter panic.

“This… what is this!?”

His voice shivered and fear discolored his face. Torchriver was a spiritas. Within their bodies, the soul was the most important and integral part of them. Thus, he was extremely sensitive to this divine soul artifact, the Magic Cube!

The saints refined their bodies, humans refined their energy, and the spiritas refined their souls. In a sense, the Magic Cube was the greatest and most precious treasure to the entire soul race, but at the same time, it was their supreme nemesis! This was because the Magic Cube was able to directly pull out a person’s soul from their body and swallow it!

Now that Torchriver was in front of the Magic Cube, he was in that exact situation. He felt a terrifying force latch onto his body, faintly trying to pull out his soul!

This strength left one drowning in helplessness, filled with fear!

Torchriver had originally been on the verge of collapse. His life was at its end, and with his cultivation being crippled by Lin Ming, there was nothing in his heart but anguish. But now that he faced the Magic Cube, another emotion overcame all else. This feeling was fear. In front of the Magic Cube, he felt as if he was being thrust into the deepest pit of hell, forever unable to reincarnate!

Torchriver struggled to retreat, leaving a trail of blood on the ground. For a spiritas to see the Magic Cube was like a mouse seeing a cat, a frog seeing a snake; this was an instinctual, inborn suppression!

However, he had been locked onto by a strength and was left unable to struggle at all. He could only watch helplessly as the Magic Cube came closer and closer. This feeling was truly bloodcurdling!

“You… what are you trying to do!?”

“I am going to refine your soul.” Lin Ming smiled. But at this moment, his smile was extremely fierce. “This is a divine tool that can refine souls. Its name is the Divine Crystal Magic Cube. You might have heard of it before or you might not have, but none of that matters, because you will soon feel its strength.”

“You… what do you want to know, I will tell you anything you want, do not swallow my soul!”

Torchriver was paler than white, his voice trembling the entire time.

“I’m sorry. The things I want to know are not things you can tell me.”

Lin Ming fiendishly grinned. Then, he poured his origin energy into the Magic Cube. The Magic Cube began to spin, sucking up all of the nearby divine soul energy!

With the Magic Cube as the center, a black vortex appeared, seeming as if it could swallow the world!

“Ahhhhhh!”

Torchriver issued a heart-piercing scream. His body was twisted apart in this vortex and crushed to pieces. A deep blue divine soul was forcefully torn out from his ruined body before being sucked into the Magic Cube!

“No - !”

Torchriver’s last cry seemed to stretch to infinity within this vortex, completed distorted.

After that came pain, a pain that couldn’t be described.

A terrifying energy struck his soul form!

And forcefully tore away his spirit mark!

The souls of the spiritas were strong to begin with and their spirit marks were extremely deep. For their spirit mark to be torn out, the pain was excruciating beyond compare.

Torchriver felt as if time had slowed down to a crawl. Each breath of time seemed to last as long as a year. This endless and inexhaustible pain made him want to die but he simply didn’t possess the ability to kill himself.

Torchriver cried out again and again. Lin Ming was able to extinguish his soul from the start, but he didn’t do so. Instead, he slowly grinded away Torchriver’s spirit mark. Towards this scumbag divine runic master who had caused so much suffering, only this sort of fate could slightly make up for all his sins.

A person’s soul was composed of pure memories and their spirit mark. This was a person’s ‘characteristic of life’. If they lost either half then the person would lose all sense of self.

A person’s spirit mark was like endless tiny filaments that thoroughly penetrated into every nook and cranny of a person’s soul. Wanting to completely erase them without damaging the memories was impossible. But, the Magic Cube could actually do this. It had the ability to pull out these tiny, imperceptible threads.

And as this ability was reflected on Torchriver’s body, it was more painful than being slowly flayed alive!

Lin Ming slowly and carefully removed Torchriver’s spirit mark from his memories. This was also because Lin Ming had never used the Magic Cube in this manner before. It was his first time using the Magic Cube to produce memory fragments on his own initiative.

In order to maintain the full body of Torchriver’s memories, Lin Ming used a full day and night to complete this laborious work. And as he was nearing the end, Torchriver’s soul had already dimmed down to nothing but an ember. His consciousness had been slowly tortured and destroyed by Lin Ming.

Chapter 1554 – Heavenly Extreme Bliss

This day and night of pain was simply indescribable. Even Xiao Moxian who swore she would cut Torchriver to pieces still felt her heart skip a beat as she saw his fate. The echoes of pain that transmitted from Torchriver’s soul were far too brutal and agonizing. It was hard to imagine just what he had experienced in this day.

“Finished…” Lin Ming let out a long sigh of relief. He looked towards the complete ownerless memory fragment that floated within the Magic Cube and a happy expression crossed his lips. He had spent a great sum of money at Heaven’s Secret to purchase information and then had cut down Torchriver with all of his strength. Everything he did was for this ownerless and complete memory fragment, the memories of a divine runic master!

Of the three divine tools, the Divine Magic Cube, Grandmist Spirit Bead, and that secretive and mysterious Purple Card, each one was the highest level of treasures.

For the Purple Card, Lin Ming had no idea what its function was.

But as for the Magic Cube and Grandmist Spirit Bead, he had more or less dug out their secrets.

Of the Grandmist Spirit Bead and the Magic Cube, one was focused on the body and the other on the soul!

The Grandmist Spirit Bead could forcefully wrest away and swallow the blood vitality of all life. Moreover, it possessed the ability to condense all of this blood vitality into Grandmist Spirit Bead essence. The effects of the Grandmist Spirit Bead essence even surpassed a transcendent divine pill that was refined by an Empyrean!

When Lin Ming broke through the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, if he didn’t have the help of the Grandmist Spirit Bead essence, then even if he had the strength from the Essence Spirit Embryo stone and Xiao Moxian’s primordial yin blood, it still wouldn’t have been enough for him to achieve his breakthrough!

The reason that the Good Fortune Saint Son had the strength to suppress an ordinary World King with his peak Divine Lord realm cultivation was all because of the heaven-defying support of the Grandmist Spirit Bead!

In a sense, the Grandmist Spirit Bead suited the saint race far more than any other race.

If a human were to obtain the Grandmist Spirit Bead then the use of it would be extremely minor for them. This was because the road of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace had been blocked!

In the past when Empyrean Primordius obtained the Grandmist Spirit Bead, his essence gathering system cultivation had already reached the World King boundary. But, he hadn’t started body transformation yet at all; he had started everything from zero.

Not only was this road of martial arts one that defied the heavens, but Empyrean Primordius had also missed the best opportunity for him to cultivate body transformation. The difficulty of the road he took afterwards could be imagined.

Even so, Empyrean Primordius had finally relied on the heaven-defying effects of the Grandmist Spirit Bead and his own prodigious talent to break into the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. But, Empyrean Primordius hadn’t opened too many Dao Palaces. At that time, his essence gathering system cultivation was the extreme Empyrean realm, but his Nine Stars of the Dao Palace had only opened four or five palaces. His body transformation cultivation was far inferior to his essence gathering cultivation and his body transformation technique only had a limited ability to enhance his combat strength.

In comparison, Lin Ming had a Divine Lord realm cultivation and had opened a single star of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. Currently, his body transformation cultivation was higher than his essence gathering system cultivation. It was similar to giving a child a well-crafted and accurate crossbow, making that child’s lethal killing ability to rise to an all new level. Even a strong and robust man could still be severely wounded or shot dead by an accurate arrow.

Therefore, Lin Ming was able to cross two large boundaries in the essence gathering system and contend with an ordinary World King!

As for the Magic Cube, its abilities seemed to surpass even those of the Grandmist Spirit Bead. It was able to ignore the protection of the flesh and directly exterminate an enemy’s soul.

But, the true strength of the Magic Cube wasn’t its ability to directly extinguish a person’s soul and increase Lin Ming’s combat strength. Rather, the true strength of the Magic Cube lay in its ability to cleanse a person’s soul of its spirit mark, turning it into pure memories that could be freely absorbed without needing to worry that one would fall into madness! This heaven-defying effect was perfectly suited for plundering the cultivation methods of others!

The cultivation methods of the martial world couldn’t be passed on orally but had to be passed on through cultivation method jade slips. This was because cultivation method jade slips were far too complex and couldn’t be fully explained in words alone.

However, with the Magic Cube, Lin Ming was able to completely accept and inherit any martial artist’s cultivation methods. This even included their attainments and experiences in those cultivation methods!

Thus, Lin Ming could cultivate at an astronomical speed. When combined with his superior perception, the speed of his progress could only be described as rising 10,000 miles in a single day!

Besides cultivation methods, almost everything else was applicable. This included divine runic arts, alchemy, array formations, refining technique, any many other skills. Not only could he inherit all of their knowledge but he could inherit all of their experience!

And what Lin Ming needed to do was to constantly practice, thoroughly mastering this knowledge and reviewing these experiences, fusing those memories into his body until they became instinctual. This method of studying and speed of learning was simply mind-boggling, truly heaven-defying!

The divine runic arts that took others dozens of years to learn would only take Lin Ming several months of practice!

It could be said that when Lin Ming had reached the Divine Lord boundary and gained the ability to activate the Magic Cube, he had silently undergone a dreadful transformation, one that no one knew about!

As Lin Ming grew stronger he would be able to kill stronger masters and swallow their memories!

And the more memories Lin Ming swallowed, the faster his cultivation would rise and the stronger he would become!

As long as he had enough time, Lin Ming’s strength would grow like a snowball rolling down a snowy mountain, rapidly growing! He would eventually become a perfectly versatile genius, skilled in all aspects!

Thus, although the Grandmist Spirit Bead was also a priceless treasure to Lin Ming, during his youth, the use of the Grandmist Spirit Bead was far inferior to the help of the Magic Cube.

From what he knew, the Grandmist Spirit Bead focused on the mortal body and was able to produce endless medicines that surpassed the rank of transcendent divine pills. But, transcendent divine pills were still something that Lin Ming could find if he went searching for lucky chances, wandering through danger zones, or he might even be able to purchase them.

However, soul fragments from the Magic Cube were different. This would save a massive amount of cultivation time for Lin Ming, and what Lin Ming needed the most right now was time.

Lin Ming closed his eyes in meditation, restoring his divine soul to its peak state. Then, he began to swallow Torchriver’s ownerless soul.

These were the complete memories of an ordinary World King. The amount of information stored within it reached unimaginable levels!

When Lin Ming was in the lower realms, he had only absorbed small soul fragments. Moreover, the past masters of these soul fragments didn’t surpass Holy Lords before they had died. Even so, to the Lin Ming of that time, these soul fragments placed a tremendous burden on his divine soul.

Swallowing these ownerless memories was like cutting open his head and stuffing in a massive amount of information. Because there was too much information and it was far too complex and diverse, Lin Ming had felt as if his head would explode. This wasn’t something that the average person was able to withstand.

Fortunately, during Lin Ming’s nine years in Tragic Death Valley, he had cultivated the Divine Mist Heart Mantra and his soul force was no longer comparable to how it was in the past. Although abruptly absorbing the memories of an ordinary World King was extremely difficult, it wasn’t to the degree where it would instantly shatter his spiritual sea.

It had to be known that Torchriver had lived for nearly a million years. Moreover, a World King had an extremely sharp memory and they were able to memorize things very clearly and in much detail. As these memories accumulated over time, the total quantity of them was simply unimaginable!

When Lin Ming let open his spiritual sea, these memories rushed into him like endless waves from a dam that broke apart. Even though Lin Ming was already prepared, he was nearly washed away in this deluge of memories and his divine soul almost lost!

He hurriedly guarded his mind, summoning a battle spirit sword and sending it howling out!

Kacha!

Torchriver’s ownerless soul was chopped to pieces by Lin Ming’s battle spirit!

Lin Ming swept through these soul fragments at a frightening speed, immediately discarding large numbers of useless soul fragments.

These included Torchriver’s life experiences, his dealings with others, his friends, foes, and so forth.

There were also a great number of memories from when Torchriver lured, raped, and intimidated young girls. All of these were discarded by Lin Ming.

However, upon seeing these memories, Lin Ming thought more and more that this Torchriver died a deserving death. He had simply ruined far too many young girls. After being raped by him, many of these young girls had been savagely tortured to death. He had even gone into the world of mortals, disguising himself as a bandit rapist and violating young girls from all over. The youngest of these was even 12-13 years old.

For such a disgustingly immoral despoiler to reach this level, it was truly a rare sight.

Different people had different pursuits in life. What Lin Ming pursued was the peak of martial arts and to stand on par with the heavens and earth. But this Torchriver pursued immortality so that he could enjoy new young girls forever, tasting them all whether it was now, a thousand years from now, or a million years from now.

Torchriver’s ownerless memories were quickly chopped into hundreds upon hundreds of pieces. Like this, 99% of the memories were thrown away by Lin Ming.

The only remaining memories were those related to cultivation method inheritances, divine runic arts, and alchemy.

But upon reviewing Torchriver’s cultivation methods, Lin Ming was stunned. Torchriver had over 100 different cultivation methods and even a complete transcendent divine might.

With the status of an ordinary World King, it was very difficult to ever hope of learning a complete transcendent divine might. But, as a divine runic master, Torchriver was wealthier than some Great World Kings. By spending a massive amount of wealth he was able to obtain this transcendent divine might. And, what left Lin Ming speechless was that this transcendent divine might was called Heavenly Extreme Bliss; it was a dual cultivation method.

Out of Torchriver’s 100 some cultivation methods, over 70 of them were related to dual cultivation. He had really taken the road of obscenity to the limit.

Lin Ming threw away most of these cultivation methods. He simply couldn’t be bothered with looking at these low level ones. But, it was too wasteful if this complete transcendent divine might was lost like this.

Thinking about this, he kept the Heavenly Extreme Bliss.

At this time, Lin Ming seemed to realize something. He momentarily stopped absorbing Torchriver’s soul fragments.

Then, Lin Ming took the spatial ring from Torchriver and crushed it. A massive amount or bottles, jars, pill boxes, and all sorts of things came flying out.

Among the mess was a pink jade slip that Lin Ming grabbed. This pink jade slip was the complete cultivation method jade slip for Heavenly Extremely Bliss!

Torchriver had used several hundred thousands of years of time accumulate a massive amount of wealth through his career as a divine runic master. Then, in addition to a mind-boggling lucky chance that he obtained in a mystic realm, he had traded all of that for this complete transcendent divine might jade slip!

This caused Lin Ming to sigh. In terms of obscenity, Torchriver had done everything in his power to reach the peak!

“Mm? What is that?” Xiao Moxian watched as Lin Ming temporarily withdrew from absorbing memories and then specifically took out the jade slip. She could immediately feel that this jade slip wasn’t ordinary.

“Uh… this is… a complete transcendent divine might…”

Lin Ming dryly coughed and awkwardly gesticulated.

“A complete transcendent divine might jade slip?” Xiao Moxian was startled. “An ordinary World King had this sort of thing!? Not even Tian Mingzi had one!”

Tian Mingzi only had two incomplete transcendent divine mights. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have entered Demondawn Heavenly Palace to study the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art.

“That’s right. Divine runic masters are ridiculously rich. This jade slip was obtained by another World King in a mystic realm, but after that World King tried practicing this cultivation method to 60-70%, he realized that it didn’t fit him too well. The World King took it out to sell, and in order to obtain this jade slip, Torchriver paid a heart-bleeding price, trading half of his lifetime savings for it.”

“I see… can I see what sort of jade slip that is?” Xiao Moxian laughed and took the jade slip from Lin Ming’s hands.

Chapter 1555 – Learning Skills

Xiao Moxian happily began to search through the contents within the jade slip, but after she saw what was inside she was left completely stunned. The descriptions of the cultivation method were extremely graphic and exceedingly pornographic.

This was actually a dual cultivation method.

Xiao Moxian blushed. She sputtered, saying, “Bleh, just what sort of Empyrean was this? I can’t believe that the summary of their lifetime’s studies is this sort of thing.”

Lin Ming awkwardly coughed. “This is a cultivation method formed by husband and wife Empyreans who took the sexual road… the two of them were peerless geniuses of their time and both became Empyreans together.

Lin Ming had scanned through Torchriver’s memories and knew what the origin of this cultivation method was.

For a husband and wife to cultivate to the Empyrean realm together was an extremely rare sight. Empyreans were already rare in the martial world; an Empyrean Holy Land might not even be able to train an Empyrean successor in tens of millions of years, and for a couple to reach the Empyrean boundary together was far rarer than that. For instance, Empyrean Demondawn and the Monster Emperor only had World Kings as wives.

“Cultivate into Empyreans together? Heh, Lin Ming, we must become True Divinities together!”

Xiao Moxian suddenly said, stating her goal. She wanted to become a True Divinity, and in her opinion it wasn’t difficult at all for Lin Ming to accomplish this. For him, the realm of True Divinity might even be underestimating him.

Xiao Moxian was filled with anticipation as she thought of cultivating into True Divinities with Lin Ming. Perhaps, they would leave behind an eternal story of love and adventure, one that would be spoken about by the future generations, just like Empyrean Divine Seal!

“Alright.”

Lin Ming chuckled. In truth, his goal surpassed that of a True Divinity. He wanted to surpass a True Divinity and reach the peak of all martial arts.

Xiao Moxian grinned and put away the Heavenly Extreme Bliss jade slip. This jade slip was only good as reference material for Xiao Moxian; she wasn’t satisfied with taking the path of others. When she had the ability to do so, she would carve out her own cultivation path. Only like this would she be able to surpass those who came before her.

At this time, Lin Ming had reentered the soul space and continued to absorb Torchriver’s memory fragments. Now he was about to absorb the most essential part – memories of the divine runic arts and alchemy!

This was the main reason that Lin Ming had killed Torchriver.

Torchriver had already reached the last years of his life and had fallen into a demented state, ready to die at any moment. He had lost all value, and in this situation, there was no one that would bother to provoke someone who had once been a World King and was even now a half-step World King.

As for him ruining the lives of countless young women, there were even fewer people that cared about this. When a martial artist began slaughtering, sometimes they would exterminate entire cities. They could destroy what they wanted and no one would chase after this; this was a brutal world where strength reigned supreme. Besides the Heavenly Dao, there were no laws that stood above martial arts.

For a time, images of runes and array formations rushed into Lin Ming’s mind.

Torchriver had been a divine runic master and alchemist for several hundred thousands of years. Although he was a sinful person, his accomplishments in divine runic arts and alchemy were truly worthy of respect!

After all, he had once been an Elder of the Divine Runic Masters Guild, and was a true sixth grade divine runic master!

It had to be known that in the Divine Runic Masters Guild, an eighth grade divine runic master was a legend and ninth grade divine runic masters were ancient myths that only existed billions of years ago. It could be said that a seventh grade divine runic master was the highest level there was, and if one had such ability, they could even become Guild President of the Divine Runic Masters Guild!

If one had to forcefully equate ranks of divine runic masters with the cultivation ranks of a martial artist, then a seventh grade divine runic master would be equal to an Empyrean. And in fact, there were many divine runic masters that had the strength of an Empyrean!

A sixth grade divine runic master was equal to a World King. Outstanding sixth grade divine runic masters were similar to Great World Kings.

Torchriver was a sixth grade divine runic master, and 100,000 years ago, his cultivation had been that of an ordinary World King.

A fifth grade divine runic master was equal to a Holy Lord.

A fourth grade divine runic master was equal to a Divine Lord.

A third grade divine runic master was equal to Divine Transformation.

Even so, the truth was that a third or fourth grade divine runic master was far more precious than a comparable martial artist of that boundary.

Divine Transformation realm powerhouses could be found everywhere, but third grade divine runic masters had a considerable amount of status. If a third grade divine runic master were a bit younger than average, proving that they had a bright future ahead of them, there would be many great influences that would try to win them over.

Yue Liuxing’s senior-apprentice brother was in this type of situation. He had studied the divine runic arts for only several dozen years, and now he had become a third grade divine runic master. Although he was only at the third grade, there were many leaders of large influences that were polite to him, because there was a chance that he could become an Elder of the Divine Runic Masters Guild in the future.

That was a truly incredible person.

As Lin Ming scanned more and more memories, a huge amount of information piled up in his mind. He felt as if a massive steel weight was wildly smashing into his spiritual sea!

Lin Ming grit his teeth, resisting this mind-tearing pain as he slowly reorganized Torchriver’s memories.

These memories contained a massive amount of experiences concerning alchemy and divine runic arts that Torchriver had accumulated over hundreds of thousands of years.

Although Torchriver was a lustful villain, there was no doubting his specialized skills. One could even say that he was considerably talented in divine runic arts and alchemy, otherwise it was impossible for him to have become a sixth grade divine runic master, eighth grade alchemist!

Torchriver was also well aware that the divine runic arts were the foundation for his pursuit of comfort, women, and immortality!

Torchriver had an amazingly sharp memory. He was able to clearly remember every young girl that he had abused in the last several hundred thousands of years. But, beyond that, he was also able to clearly remember the process, details, and experiences of all the alchemy and divine runic arts he had done!

Countless experiments, whether they had been failures or successes, had consumed a massive amount of precious materials or hard work. This was the summary of all his experiences and the experiences of his predecessors. It was all invaluable data!

It had to be known that although a divine runic master made a great deal of money, they also burnt through money just as fast. The materials they used often cost several hundred million origin energy runes. If they failed, all of that would vanish into nothing, completely wasted!

To raise a single divine runic master would require a large influence to invest the entirety of their financial resources. For a single person to become a divine runic master alone, that was simply far too difficult.

Every divine runic master had their own unique take on the divine runic arts, and every now and then they would suddenly have strange and bizarre ideas. If they wanted to put these ideas into practice they had to undergo countless revisions and deliberations, because every new idea meant new investments of materials. And of these ideas, over 99% would fail.

But, even failure meant that they would gain more experiences and knowledge from these defeats. And once they succeeded, even if they only succeeded a little bit, this would mean an astonishing new amount of wealth. This success would become some divine runic masters’ ultimate secret skill, something they would never pass onto anyone else!

This was inevitable. After all, researching new ideas simply cost far too many resources.

In addition, the Divine Runic Masters Guild was not a single, unified obelisk. Within the guild, many divine runic masters would compete against each other for resources. They would invest their resources into new studies, and whatever new information they gained, they wouldn’t pass it on to anyone, not even their own apprentices. In this case, the hundreds of thousands of years of memories that Lin Ming absorbed, and all of the experiences and knowledge that went with them, was simply unable to be measured with mere wealth!

In particular, unlike other divine runic arts apprentices, Lin Ming learnt all of this in a short period of time. Other apprentices would take dozens or hundreds of years, flattering and helping their master and having to also show a great deal of skill before they were taught anything worthwhile. Even then, only when their master retired and had a foot in the coffin would they decide to pass on the essence of their life’s studies. But at this time, their apprentice wouldn’t be young either.

And those that had the qualifications to flatter their masters and learn true abilities were all direct disciples of divine runic masters, like Yue Liuxing’s senior-apprentice brother, Luo Yubai. As for brother and sister duo Yue Liuxing and Yue Qifeng, they wouldn’t even see their master more than five times in a month, so what guidance could they possible seek?

Every divine runic master would have more or less a dozen or even dozens of ‘unique skills’. And now, all of Torchriver’s unique skills had been completely learned by Lin Ming!

What Lin Ming had to do was thoroughly digest all of these experiences and attainments, practicing them until they became natural movements to him. No matter how much knowledge he had, it was useless if his hands and feet couldn’t follow his mind.

Xiao Moxian activated Primordius Heavenly Palace’s time enchantment, increasing the flow of time to a 20:1 ratio. Within this time enchantment, Lin Ming constantly recalled Torchriver’s memories.

After a month passed, Lin Ming had fully carved the hundreds of thousands of years of Torchriver’s memories into his spiritual sea, making them completely his.

After finishing all of this, Lin Ming let out a long breath of relief. He hadn’t rested for a single moment in this entire month and his temples were pained, he had deep headaches, and his entire body was soaked with sweat.

Lin Ming then rested in meditation for a full 10 hours, slowly restoring himself.

As he opened his eyes, his vision gleamed with a bright light, shining with intelligence!

He knew that the step he took had been the right one. By absorbing the memories of a divine runic master, the advantages he obtained could be imagined!

This had saved Lin Ming dozens and hundreds of years of back-breaking work!

All of this was thanks to the heaven-defying abilities of the Magic Cube. Otherwise, it would have been unimaginably difficult for Lin Ming to study divine runic arts and alchemy!

But, just Torchriver’s divine runic arts were not enough.

Lin Ming wasn’t satisfied with this alone. He studied the divine runic arts and alchemy in order to pave the road for his Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. After all, unlike Empyrean Primordius, Lin Ming didn’t possess the endless essence of the Grandmist Spirit Bead. Lin Ming could only refine pills through alchemy, and the pills required for the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, in particular the last several stars, would be far too difficult for a mere sixth grade divine runic master. He would need to be at least a seventh grade divine runic master!

Torchriver had only been a sixth grade divine runic master. In the future, he would only serve as reference to Lin Ming. Since these memories would all be reference materials, Lin Ming didn’t mind having too many of them.

“Come, let’s go to where Heaven’s Secret said the second divine runic master is.”

As Lin Ming spoke, a thick killing intent sparked in his eyes. The second divine runic master was even easier for him to kill. He couldn’t help but admire the work of Heaven’s Secret. If it wasn’t for their information then he would never have been able to find so many skilled divine runic masters that had also lost the protection of any great influences.

After receiving Primordius Heavenly Palace, Lin Ming brought along the many young girls that had been imprisoned by Torchriver and flew straight to the southeast. His destination was only a million miles away; it wouldn’t be long before he arrived.

Chapter 1557 – Thorough Mastery

“Let me show you what true fire is.”

Xiao Moxian spread out her hands and ghostly black flames leapt between them, beating like a heart and peacefully burning. Although these flames didn’t seem too hot, the surrounding void began to distort because of these flames, showing just how hot they were.

Chifeng’s complexion changed as he saw this. “You’ve already approached the seventh level Concept, to bring Virtual Fire into reality!”

These flames contained virtual flames and true flames. Once these flames reached the limit in their fusion, the Concept of Fire would enter into the seventh level!

Currently, Xiao Moxian had yet to step into the true seventh level Concept, but even so, this was an extremely exaggerated accomplishment. There were many fire-attribute cultivation method World Kings that couldn’t compare with Xiao Moxian.

Kacha!

Chifeng’s icy armor was blown away by Xiao Moxian’s black flames, with half of his body being charred black in the process. However, he still struggled to the end. He reached out, wanting to pull another divine runic symbol from his spatial ring and bet his life, but at this time, the grandmist space came shrouding down over him, locking down his movements once more.

Meanwhile, Xiao Moxian’s whip vanished into dozens of afterimages that formed a cone as they came slashing down!

“Ahh!”

Chifeng was frightened out of his mind. He desperately tried to summon true essence to break free from Lin Ming’s force field shackles, but beneath the phantoms of these dozens of whip attacks his protective true essence instantly collapsed as dozens of bloody holes were pierced through him!

And at this time, only then was Chifeng able to pull out a second set of divine runic symbols from his spatial ring. But then, his face paled and he fell downwards with a scream!

Beneath the joint attacks of Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian, the originally far weaker Chifeng simply didn’t have the ability to resist. The ending to this battle had already been doomed to be one-sided from the start.

In terms of strength, Chifeng was still slightly worse than the completely exhausted Torchriver.

“Take him away!”

Lin Ming indifferently said. Xiao Moxian flicked her hand and her whip tightly wrapped around Chifeng.

“What do you want to do with all these followers?” Xiao Moxian asked as an afterthought.

Lin Ming replied, “Don’t bother with them. If they can’t tell right from wrong then there will be no future for them in the Asura Road. They will all die sooner or later.”

As Lin Ming spoke, his body turned into a beam of light that hurtled into the skies, with Xiao Moxian following right behind.

This was the second divine runic master they had captured: the sixth grade divine runic master, seventh grade alchemist Chifeng!

Although this person was weaker than the cruel and sinful sex fiend Torchriver, in terms of sinisterness, he actually far surpassed him. He had secretly killed his own master in a mystic realm for mere treasures. This sort of heartless decision was almost the same as Tian Mingzi killing the old Verdant Feather World King; this was something Lin Ming hated the most.

And even worse was that after his master had died, Chifeng had married his master’s daughter in order to consolidate authority around him. As her heart had been breaking over the death of her father, Chifeng had appeared and comforted her, even propping up the sect by himself. In this sort of situation, it was simple for Chifeng to capture the heart of his master’s daughter.

Afterwards, Chifeng had made up all sorts of lies to trick the people and establish his own religion, absorbing the power of faith from his followers to cultivate his devil arts. Although these were heinous actions, they weren’t comparable to what he had done before.

In short, this person was deserving of death!

And most important was that killing Chifeng wasn’t difficult at all. This sort of genius actually wanted to establish his own sect and had refused all outside help. On this alone, Lin Ming greatly admired Heaven’s Secret. For them to have such accurate information was truly remarkable. Lin Ming even suspected that perhaps the cultivation method manual that they used to gather information was on the level of a transcendent divine might.

Lin Ming quickly exterminated Chifeng’s soul and erased his spirit mark. Then, he swallowed down Chifeng’s soul.

Chifeng wasn’t too old. In terms of total amount of memories, he had far less than Torchriver, so it was easier for Lin Ming to absorb them. In Primordius Heavenly Palace’s time enchantment, Lin Ming used only a single month to absorb all of these memories.

The reason that Chifeng was able to become a sixth grade divine runic master at the peak Holy Lord realm was all due to his own outstanding talent. However, in terms of the experiences he had accumulated, he was inferior to Torchriver. Even so, Chifeng had many unique ideas and a very wide range of thoughts that provided a great deal of inspirations to Lin Ming.

After Lin Ming killed Chifeng, he had killed two of the three divine runic masters that Heaven’s Secret had told him about.

And, the last one was the simplest one.

This person was only a fifth grade divine runic master with an early Holy Lord cultivation. Killing him was extremely easy.

This person had originally been given a death sentence by a Divine Kingdom from the outer Ausra Road. To avoid being hunted down, he had fled into the inner Asura Road. He was a solitary person with a strange and eccentric personality. He was cruel and diabolical, and didn’t join any influence, not even the Divine Runic Masters Guild.

Lin Ming flew another 500,000 miles to the southwest. He placed the young girls that had been tortured by Torchriver in a mortal city, and then flew for several more hours before he found the third divine runic master.

There wasn’t any difficulty in finding this person and Lin Ming also easily cut him down. Like this, the memories of three divine runic masters had been gathered up by Lin Ming!

Then, Lin Ming used three months within Primordius Heavenly Palace’s time enchantment to complete a thorough mastery of all three divine runic masters’ memories!

The divine runic arts and inscription technique were essentially the same thing, but the divine runic arts were far more complex.

Moreover, the uses of the divine runic arts were far wider than those of inscription technique!

The function of inscription technique was divided into four types: one was object inscription symbols that increased the power of weapons and armors, one was medicinal inscription symbols that increased the efficacy of pills, one was body inscription symbols that increased the might of the body, and the last were soul inscription symbols that increased the intensity of the soul.

Of these four inscription symbols, Lin Ming had only seen the first three; he had never studied the last kind.

However, divine runic arts not only had all the effects of inscription technique but their usage far outstripped it.

To turn stone into gold, water into oil, all of this was changing the structure of matter. Even changing the shape of a life form could be accomplished by the divine runic arts. A seventh grade divine runic master could even produce divine runic symbols that transformed a martial artist into a pig or dog.

In the Divine Runic Masters Guild, there was a type of punishment where one was transformed into a pig or dog for a thousand years. The martial artist being punished would even retain their original intelligence the entire time.

To have the intelligence of a sentient being while having the body of a pig or dog, this was a truly sickening experience.

In addition, divine runic symbols could even be used in battle.

For instance, Torchriver and Chifeng had both used divine runic symbols to create barriers. They could have even formed offensive fireballs, wind blades, ice arrows, and so forth.

The divine runic symbols produced by a grandmaster could even be used multiple times as long as one poured enough true essence into them.

The divine runic arts were extremely broad in their use; this was because they were the manifestation of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws.

“Xian’er, I must close up for a period of time to practice my divine runic arts and alchemy. Let’s return to Divine Runic City first!”

After Lin Ming killed the three divine runic masters he had also obtained their spatial rings. These divine runic masters were considerably wealthy to begin with, and this was especially true for Chifeng; he had accumulated a great deal of wealth through his religion.

Origin energy runes were useful, but the most important thing was that these spatial rings held a massive amount of alchemy materials and divine runic arts materials. These materials were perfectly suited for Lin Ming to practice.

However, the grade of these materials was a bit high for the current Lin Ming. Lin Ming had to start practicing with the most basic of materials before he advanced, and these materials were easily found in the bustling Divine Rune City.

Lin Ming controlled Primordius Heavenly Palace to immediately fly back to Divine Rune City.

Divine Rune City had markets that were dedicated to selling divine runic arts materials. But, if one wished to purchase a massive amount of divine runic arts and alchemy materials, the Divine Runic Masters Guild was the most convenient place to do so.

If one was a divine runic master that was registered to the Divine Runic Masters Guild then they could receive a 10% discount. However, Lin Ming wasn’t registered.

As Lin Ming was purchasing materials at the Divine Runic Masters Guild, he pulled out a long list of materials he needed and then bumped into someone he had met before.

A fat old man in white robes with black patterns rounded the corner, wearing a strange eight-cornered hat.

“Uh…”

Lin Ming’s expression stiffened and he subconsciously turned away. However, the old man had caught sight of him. The old man had extremely good memory and was able to instantly recognize Lin Ming.

This old man was the spiritas divine runic master vendor who had sold Lin Ming the broken jade during the first time he had come to the Divine Runic Masters Guild.

The spiritas vendor was extremely knowledgeable and shrewd, someone that could squeeze oil from sand. But, he had still been robbed blind by Lin Ming. That broken jade was far too special; besides Lin Ming himself, no one would have been able to recognize it.

As Lin Ming saw this old man, he was a bit suspicious. “This old geezer, he shouldn’t have noticed something strange afterwards, right…?”

The truth was that the transaction had already been completed, and even if the old man regretted it there was nothing he could do. Moreover, Lin Ming was strong in his own right and didn’t fear this old man.

“Oh, it’s you!”

The spiritas old man smiled at Lin Ming. From his expression, Lin Ming couldn’t tell whether or not he had regretted selling that broken jade.

“So it’s Senior, this is such a coincidence.”

Lin Ming hollowly laughed, pretending he had just seen this old man.

“Are you buying materials…?”

The spiritas old man glanced at the list in Lin Ming’s hand. He could make out the massive amount of low level materials. These were things that only low level inscription masters, apprentice divine runic masters, and low level alchemists would use.

Normally, when one first started out as a divine runic master, inscription master, or alchemist, they would buy these materials to practice. Of course, these materials were all relatively expensive, and without certain finances, it was impossible to afford them.

The materials on Lin Ming’s list alone were worth several hundred million origin energy runes. Although many of these materials were used by novices, they were still considerably expensive. They weren’t something that an ordinary divine runic arts apprentice would use. But, Lin Ming didn’t care about this. What he cared about the most was their effects in helping him practice, and whether or not they could help him quickly raise his skill in divine runic arts and alchemy. Price was a secondary consideration.

The spiritas old man thoughtfully traced his chin. Then, he recalled the words that Lin Ming had said before, that he had wanted to become a divine runic master. The old man chuckled.

“You want to study divine runic arts and alchemy? Commendable spirit, commendable!”

A strange color appeared on Lin Ming’s face. No matter how he heard it, these words were clearly ironic…

In particular, this spiritas old man was smiling so brightly that it appeared far too self-satisfied. Anyone who saw this would think his heart wasn’t matching his words, and he was simply joking about…

Chapter 1560 – Leaving Seclusion

Compared to not having a transcendent divine might rank dual cultivation method, if Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian were to try dual cultivating themselves, the effects and speed would naturally be very different.

Heavenly Extreme Bliss focused on training and recuperation. There was absorbing yang to restore yin and absorbing yin to restore yang; both of these were greatly beneficial to both the man and woman. As for the third focus, that was the essence of Heavenly Extreme Bliss.

In short, the main role of Heavenly Extreme Bliss was to consolidate one’s foundation and stabilize one’s cultivation; the speed of training was terrifyingly fast, especially for geniuses like Xiao Moxian and Lin Ming.

But, if one looked at these and thought that Heavenly Extreme Bliss was not too amazing in the aspect of direct combat, then they would be mistaken. Heavenly Extreme Bliss had offensive martial skills, but these abilities required the man and woman to work in unison in order to display their true striking power. And upon using them, the effects wouldn’t be as simple as one plus one.

Thus in the past, although this husband and wife Empyrean couple were only middle to upper rank Empyreans, when they joined forces they were able to contend with a peak Empyrean. This allowed them to have a nearly unparalleled status within the Asura Road!

After dual cultivating with Xiao Moxian for several hours, Lin Ming’s originally overdrawn soul force had faintly returned. And during this dual cultivation process, it was Xiao Moxian helping Lin Ming – Lin Ming had barely moved at all. This was a thoroughly enjoyable experience.

This was also reasonable. Although Lin Ming had inherited Torchriver’s memories, he hadn’t practiced Heavenly Extreme Bliss after all. If he were to try using it then he would inevitably find it a bit strange and unfamiliar.

Slowly, Lin Ming felt his soul force recover by a great deal as he came into perfect harmony with Xiao Moxian. After their repeated rounds of lovemaking, Lin Ming became increasingly radiant, with a significant upturn in the energy circulating through his body.

Lin Ming even felt himself becoming increasingly close to reaching the middle Divine Lord realm!

When Lin Ming had broken through to the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, his cultivation had risen straight to the peak of the early Divine Lord realm. Now, he was confident that with several more years of training he would be able to make another breakthrough!

If so, then before Lin Ming was 60 years of age he would be able to break into the middle Divine Lord realm. This was a truly incredible achievement.

As for Xiao Moxian, her cultivation speed far surpassed Lin Ming’s.

Xiao Moxian was several years younger than Lin Ming to begin with, and after completing her first phoenix nirvana she had also reached the peak early Divine Lord realm. She might even break into the middle Divine Lord realm before Lin Ming.

“This cultivation method has even better effects than I imagined.”

Sitting up on Lin Ming’s body, Xiao Moxian dripped with fragrant drops of sweat, still immersed in the blissful pleasure of love. Not only were her cheeks red but her body glowed with jade perfection as if she had been soaking in a hot spring for a long time. She seemed so soft and flushed that one could even pinch out water from her skin.

“This is indeed wonderful. It is rare to find a complete transcendent divine might to begin with, but this dual cultivation method transcendent divine might can only be created by a husband and wife Empyrean. It’s impossible for a single Empyrean to create something like this.”

Lin Ming had many top cultivation methods, even ones that surpassed the rank of a transcendent divine might. For instance, the Asura Sutra was one such cultivation method, and even the Divine Seal Art was faintly superior to a transcendent divine might.

However, these two cultivation methods were extremely incomplete. Although he could use a part of their strength, wanting to cultivate from the beginning and raise his foundation to make breakthroughs with these cultivation methods was extremely difficult.

In this aspect, Heavenly Extreme Bliss was able to show its true advantages. From the start, Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian could feel each other’s origin energy surging just by holding hands. And now, with the two making love, the effects of this were naturally unparalleled.

After dual cultivating with Xiao Moxian, Lin Ming felt his state of mind be much improved. Thus, he began to tirelessly practice the divine runic arts once again.

After another period of time, as Lin Ming was drawing up another divine runic symbol, he felt the proficiency of his skill had clearly increased to another level.

Closing his eyes, all sorts of finger movements flashed through his mind. These finger movements originated from the ownerless soul fragment memories and were as natural to Lin Ming as if they were his own.

Grasping the divine runic pen, Lin Ming began to draw up another divine runic symbol.

The divine runic pen was filled with the juice of materials. One by one, gorgeous runes were formed beneath Lin Ming’s hand. At the start, Lin Ming would successfully draw one complete rune every seven or eight tries, but now he could succeed after two or three tries.

Each time there was a mistake, Lin Ming would reference the memories of the three divine runic masters to find out where he had gone wrong. This sort of analytic ability far surpassed anything an ordinary divine runic apprentice could hope to achieve.

Slowly, Lin Ming corrected his mistakes. Rune after tiny rune was drawn up by Lin Ming, whereupon they floated in the air.

All sorts of rare and precious materials were turned into runes or wasted in Lin Ming’s hands.

Lin Ming didn’t care about what results he achieved with these divine runic symbols; all he cared about was the process. By repeating these processes again and again, Lin Ming steadily advanced his skill in the divine runic arts.

Tenth day –

With a forehead coated in sweat, Lin Ming drew up one last rune. In that moment, a thousand floating runes shimmered in the sky, fusing together beneath a strange halo of light. Finally, these runes formed a complete divine rune that floated in the air.

Lin Ming’s expression was one of complete focus. He took out a god rune of the Asura Road’s Heavenly Dao from his spatial ring. Then, by fusing this god rune with the divine rune he drew up, Lin Ming had produced his first divine runic symbol.

Judging by Lin Ming’s memories, this divine runic symbol had many imperfections; it could be called very rough or even useless. But, this was still the first divine runic symbol that Lin Ming had created. In the future, as his skill continued to rise, the effects of the divine runic symbols he created would have better and better effects.

In fact, Lin Ming could even change and improve the structure of divine runic symbols through his own understanding of the divine runic arts.

Training passed without sense of time. Days passed, one after the other. Lin Ming continued to practice drawing divine runic symbols every day, and after his soul force was overdrawn he would dual cultivate with Xiao Moxian. Like this, a year passed.

During this year, Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian’s cultivation became increasingly close to the middle Divine Lord realm. At the same time, Lin Ming’s skill in drawing up low level divine runic symbols had reached near perfection.

He had thoroughly fused the memories of the three divine runic masters into his own divine runic arts. Now, what Lin Ming needed to do was to go to the Divine Runic Masters Guild and undergo the test for becoming a divine runic master. At the same time, he had to find a chance to approach the assassin organization Heaven’s Net and come into contact with Blood Moon, so he could obtain the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace portion of the Celestial Tyrant Manual.

As long as Lin Ming had a suitable cultivation method then his cultivation would rise. With enough strength, he would be able to firmly stand tall in the upcoming great calamity.

Chapter 1561 – The Divine Runic Master Examination

The Divine Runic Masters Guild held examinations for divine runic masters every year. In order to seek out talented individuals, the Divine Runic Masters Guild spared no effort.

For this examination there would always be a massive number of young martial artists that entered into Divine Rune City every year, hoping that they would be able to obtain the recognition of the Divine Runic Masters Guild and bring back the divine runic master badge that they could proudly display to the world.

These youths came not just from Divine Rune City but from many other places all over the Asura Road. For instance, Yue Qifeng and Yue Liuxing were such examples.

In the early morning of the examination, Lin Ming stood in front of the gates of the Divine Runic Masters Guild, looking up at the dignified and weighty plaque. He took a deep breath.

After he became a divine runic master registered with the Divine Runic Masters Guild then it would be much easier for him to come into contact with the Heaven’s Net assassin, Blood Moon. With his status as a divine runic master, wanting to exchange for the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace section of the Celestial Tyrant Manual shouldn’t be a problem. Moreover, Lin Ming suspected that even though Blood Moon possessed the latter half of the Celestial Tyrant Manual, this cultivation method shouldn’t be too useful to him. Lin Ming didn’t believe that there had been anyone besides himself and Empyrean Primordius who had opened the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace.

“We’re finally here! It’s this place!”

As Lin Ming was lost in thought, he heard a soft woman’s voice behind him. He turned to see a young woman in a white divine runic master’s robe dragging along a gray-haired old man, seemingly in a hurry to enter the Divine Runic Masters Guild.

This young woman looked to be around Xiao Moxian’s age. Beneath her voluminous divine runic master’s robes, one could still see her winding curves. She was definitely a shapely young woman.

On the chest of her robes was a divine runic badge. This badge only had a single rune carved atop it without a single stripe; this was the badge worn by divine runic apprentices.

As for the old man that was being dragged along, he smiled as he was being pulled. “What are you in a hurry for, what are you so anxious for? The examination doesn’t even begin for another two hours and there aren’t many people on the martial field. As for those other old fellows, they definitely won’t appear until the last moment.”

As the old man spoke, Lin Ming glanced at the divine runic master badge on his chest. There were six stripes, indicating that he was a sixth grade divine runic master!

Moreover, the last stripe was embellished with three small runes. This meant that this old man was considered first class amongst sixth grade divine runic masters. He could even be called a superior sixth grade divine runic master!

This was an amazing accomplishment and it also meant that this old man’s cultivation had likely reached the Great World King boundary. Even if it hadn’t, he likely wasn’t too far away.

“The inner Asura Road really has many World Kings…”

Lin Ming was already mentally prepared for this. The Asura Road originally gathered all outstanding individuals from the 33 Heavens, and this was especially true for the inner Asura Road. Moreover, Divine Rune City was one of the most prosperous cities of the inner Asura Road. Here, Holy Lords and Divine Lords were far too common, and even World Kings weren’t a rare sight.

As this old man moved towards the gate, the two guards standing there immediately greeted him with great respect, bowing to him. This was the respect given to a sixth grade divine runic master. Even if this old man wasn’t a divine runic master of the Divine Runic Masters Guild, this etiquette could not be ignored.

However, as Lin Ming walked closer he clearly wasn’t treated so well. The two guards didn’t even glance at Lin Ming and allowed him to enter.

In order to join the examination, there were no strict requirements to register. However, there was one point: materials needed to be prepared in advance by the examinee or purchased through the Divine Runic Masters Guild. Only when one successfully passed the examination would they be reimbursed for these materials. This was to prevent some divine runic apprentices from showing up and participating while not caring if they passed or not.

As Lin Ming walked into the hall, he traced his spatial ring. He had prepared five sets of materials today. Two were for the first grade divine runic master examination and three were for the second grade divine runic master examination.

Lin Ming wanted to raise his grade as a divine runic master as soon as possible. This was because even if he obtained the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace section of the Celestial Tyrant Manual, he still required a massive amount of exceedingly rare and precious materials to refine the medicine. However, these rare and precious materials were nearly impossible to collect unless he had the status of a high grade divine runic master!

As he arrived in the examination hall, 11-12 youths were already waiting there.

Lin Ming saw the young girl he had bumped into at the gates. In addition, he saw Yue Liuxing and Yue Qifeng, the brother and sister duo he had met when he first arrived at the inner Asura Road. They were also entering the divine runic master examination this year.

“Eh? Lin Ming!”

“What a coincidence to run into you here.”

This wasn’t as much of a coincidence as it seemed. The last time he saw Yue Liuxing and Yue Qifeng, they had only been divine runic apprentices and now was the appropriate time for them to try out for the diviner runic master examination.

“It’s been a while.” Lin Ming smiled in greeting.

“Lin Ming, what are you doing here?” Yue Liuxing asked, curious. She didn’t think that Lin Ming had come here to take the divine runic master examination with them.

Lin Ming awkwardly coughed. But, just as he was about to answer, the wooden door of the hall opened and another examinee arrived.

As Lin Ming turned, a strangely interested look came over his face.

The newly arrived examinee was also a young girl in her prime, She wore a blue robe and her hair was like a shawl that spread down her back. Her entire body exuded a light and sprightly feeling.

However, what caused the strange expression to come over Lin Ming’s face was not the young girl but the master following behind her. This master was a bit short and fat, with small and bright eyes. From his looks, he resembled an extremely large and fat mouse. This was the Old Man Xue that Lin Ming had accidently encountered in the Divine Runic Masters Guild a year ago.

This Old Man Xue had been tricked by Lin Ming. The emperor jade fragment had been sold to Lin Ming as if it were a mere spirit treasure fragment. Although he hadn’t noticed anything afterwards, Old Man Xue still thought he could con Lin Ming once more and take him in as a disciple. In the end, he failed.

“This stingy old geezer would actually accept an apprentice?” Lin Ming looked at the young and beautiful girl standing in front of Old Man Xue. Although he felt it a bit unbelievable, she was clearly his apprentice. He felt that any apprentice of his was surely unlucky.

Old Man Xue was all smiles as he entered. After passing through the doors, his eyes locked onto another high grade divine runic master. This was the sixth grade divine runic master that Lin Ming had seen at the entrance.

“Old Su, haha, to think I’d see you here today!”

“Hehe, this isn’t something normal. But, let me give you a warning. I brought Clearshadow here today not to become a first grade divine runic master, but to take the test for a second grade divine runic master! At that time, make sure you don’t bully me, haha!”

“Oh! What a coincidence! I also brought my apprentice Dreampearl here to take the second grade divine runic master test.” Old Man Xue responded in sharp opposition. The young girl called Dreampearl behind seemed much more modest. She smiled and said, “Teacher, you think too highly of me. I only have 30% confidence that I can successfully draw up a second grade divine inscription symbol.”

30%!

Although Dreampearl spoke humbly, Old Su still felt his heart skip a beat once he heard this. A divine runic master examination would last for around 10 hours, and during this time an examinee was allowed to attempt drawing up a divine runic symbol several times. Even if one failed once, they still had a second attempt and a third attempt. If she could guarantee a 30% success chance then there really might be a possibility she could pass the test.

Old Su couldn’t help but glance over at his own apprentice Clearshadow. He could faintly feel that Clearshadow didn’t have a 30% chance of success.

“Don’t worry, Teacher! Just because she says 30% doesn’t mean it is 30%. I would like to experience her skills myself!”

Clearshadow wasn’t too anxious or panicked. Old Su nodded in satisfaction. But at this moment, Old Man Xue halted. As soon as he passed through the door he had come into conflict with Old Su and hadn’t noticed the other people in the room. But now that he glanced over everyone else, he discovered there was someone he was acquainted with – Lin Ming, a little pig that he had wanted to butcher for money but that had managed to escape.

“Hey brat, you’re here because…” Looking at Lin Ming’s posture as well as the divine runic pen in his hand, a ridiculous complexion flashed over Old Man Xue’s face. “Brat, don’t tell me you’re here to participate in the divine runic master examination!”

Lin Ming spread out his hands, saying, “It’s a bit regrettable, but… that is the reason I am here.”

“Hahaha!” Old Man Xue heartily smiled, waggling his fat finger at Lin Ming. “You, you must be teasing me! In any case, why don’t you consider my earlier suggestion and become my apprentice? If your talent was too low and you were unfit for the divine runic arts then I wouldn’t think of receiving you to begin with.”

Lin Ming helplessly shrugged and sighed, saying, “I’m really not teasing you.”

Like this, Old Man Xue’s laughter suddenly stopped. He looked at Lin Ming with the eyes of a stranger. He was well aware that a year ago, Lin Ming had been nothing but an interested outsider to the divine runic arts. Now, he wanted to take a go at the divine runic master examination. It seemed this young man really liked to waste his time away.

Well, what’s done was done. This was Lin Ming’s materials and money to begin with so there wasn’t anything he could do.

“Well, keep thinking about it. I think it's best if you were my apprentice.” Old Man Xue said, giving Lin Ming ‘advice’ one more time.

Lin Ming responded, “Senior’s price for taking in an apprentice is too high. This junior truly can’t afford to enjoy such luxuries.”

As Lin Ming spoke, he glanced at the Dreampearl behind Old Man Xue. This young woman was clearly Old Man Xue’s best apprentice, someone who might inherit his complete legacy in the future. Otherwise, there was no way that someone like Old Man Xue would accompany her here for the divine runic master examination.

It was hard to say what was so special about this young woman that someone so stingy like Old Man Xue would see in her.

After listening to Lin Ming joke about Old Man Xue’s tuition fees, Old Su laughed, “Old Xue, just what do you want me to think of you? You would even con a little junior out of his money!”

Old Su naturally wouldn’t relinquish a chance to mock Old Man Xue. However, Old Man Xue’s skin was thick enough for the both of them. After being seen through he said, “All goods come at a cost. If I dare to put out such a price then I naturally have confidence in my worth. Boy, if you don’t believe me then you can come and study with me. I guarantee that it will be much faster than you studying alone.”

Old Man Xue struck his chest in guarantee. But, just as he was about to say something else, the doors to the hall opened once more and another young heroic elite entered.

This person was a spiritas youth that seemed to be just over 20 years old. He walked with mighty strides, like tigers and dragons. His eyes were bright, and there was no teacher following behind him. He had come here alone!

Chapter 1562 – Soul Emperor Divine Void

The spiritas youth was tall. His eyes were cold and bright, like a warm spring at the summit of a 100,000 foot snowy mountain. His hair was quite special; it was long and wrapped around his waist, supple enough to attract the envy of any woman. It flowed with a silver light, as if it were liquid mercury.

This sort of man had a noble and untouchable charismatic atmosphere, as if he were born to be an emperor.

His sudden appearance immediately attracted the attention of everyone present. Even Lin Ming was surprised; this youth was just far too unusual.

The youth chose a divine runic table to stand at. He watched without touching the ground, only stepping on the air instead. This was because he had released his soul force, turning it into tangible essence that floated beneath his feet. Thus, he simply didn’t need to touch the ground.

This was a method of cultivating soul force. By using this method to remain floating all year round, one’s soul force would slowly be tempered.

As Old Man Xue and Old Man Su saw this youth, they glanced at each other. They saw a trace of fright appear in the other’s eyes.

From this youth’s body, they could feel an aura that was difficult to describe. Moreover, the clothing that this young man wore as well as the temperament brought about by his cultivation method reminded them of something.

Old Man Xue thought for a moment, saying, “Young man, are you from Divine Void Divine Kingdom?”

Old Man Xue’s words caught the attention of everyone present. Everyone looked towards the young man, their faces filled with anticipation. This was because most of the martial artists present were spiritas, and Divine Void Divine Kingdom had an extraordinary significance to their soul race.

The young man slightly nodded, acknowledging his background. With this, everyone present, including Yue Liuxing and Yue Qifeng, all looked at this spiritas youth with fear and awe in their eyes.

Divine Void Divine Kingdom – that was a spiritas True Divinity Holy Land!

Although Divine Rune City had astonishing influence and power, that was only in terms of alchemy and divine runic arts. In terms of military force alone, Divine Rune City naturally couldn’t compare to a True Divinity level influence like Divine Void Divine Kingdom.

“Divine Void Divine Kingdom?”

Lin Ming thought out loud, faintly recalling something.

Old Su sighed with emotion, “Really, heroes come from the youth. We spiritas had two great Divine Kingdoms in the Asura Road – Divine Void and Divine Mist Divine Kingdoms. But because Empyrean Divine Mist strangely disappeared without any trace at all, everything relied on the support of Divine Void Divine Kingdom. But afterwards, when his majesty the Soul Emperor broke through the True Divinity boundary, that made my soul race truly invincible! Looking at you, your foundation is solid and your soul force has managed to condense into substantial essence. It seems you are also a leader amongst the juniors of Divine Void Divine Kingdom.”

The spiritas martial artists of Divine Void Divine Kingdom, when compared to the other spiritas, were like the royal family members of the imperial capital compared to the aristocratic families; the difference in status was obvious. Although the silver-haired youth was young, he would definitely become an important figure in the future. Thus, he couldn’t be considered a common junior. Even divine runic masters with considerable status like Old Su and Old Man Xue had to treat him with respect.

The silver-haired youth lightly said, “I’m no leader at all. Divine Void Divine Kingdom is filled with extraordinary people. I am merely one of the successors of Divine Void Divine Kingdom’s King Qin. 15 years ago, I was taught under Imperial Scholar Lord Pao and learned a little bit of the divine runic arts. When I left the Divine Kingdom to adventure through the world, I heard that Divine Rune City’s divine runic arts were without parallel. Thus, I came here to experience just how wonderful they are!”

The silver-haired youth casually said, confidence tinting his voice. In terms of divine runic arts, Divine Void Divine Kingdom was naturally inferior to Divine Rune City. But, the difference wasn’t too great. Many top masters of Divine Void Divine Kingdom were divine runic masters.

So, the silver-haired youth had only come to Divine Rune City to ‘experience’ this place. He wasn’t like Yue Qifeng and Yue Liuxing who hoped to study and grow here.

This divine runic arts examination was only a means for this silver-haired youth to prove himself. He didn’t really want or need the badge of the Divine Runic Masters Guild.

“So it’s the heir to King Qin! How disrespectful of us!” Old Xue had a stern expression as he heard the name of King Qin.

In Divine Void Divine Kingdom, those that earned the title of King were Empyreans. Although Divine Void Divine Kingdom’s ‘Kings’ were only weak Empyreans, an Empyrean was still an Empyrean. Compared to a World King, their status was as different as the heavens and earth.

“Hahaha! This examination truly has so many astonishing people! One Clearshadow, one Dreampearl, those two are already outstanding elites amongst their generation. I thought that these two would be the main leads in the examination, but I should have realized that there is always a higher mountain. As the examination is about to start, someone even more amazing actually appears. Young man, what is your name?”

Old Su asked the silver-haired youth, laughing.

The silver-haired youth cupped his hands across his chest and said, “Qin Yi.”

As he spoke, the two proud daughters of heaven, Clearshadow and Dreampearl, both looked at him, a brilliant fighting spirit in their eyes. Indeed, as Old Man Su had said, this examination had far surpassed their expectations.

Although they couldn’t make out how skilled this Qin Yi was in the divine runic arts, they could approximate it from his background. If he didn’t have true ability then he wouldn’t have come to the Divine Runic Masters Guild to lose face. Divine Void Divine Kingdom could be called the spiritual leader of all spiritas within the Asura Road!

Qin Yi would eventually become their greatest competition!

As Old Su and Old Xue were talking to Qin Yi, a peculiar light flashed in Lin Ming’s eyes.

Divine Void Divine Kingdom!

Divine Mist Divine Kingdom!

The so-called Divine Mist Divine Kingdom was the Divine Kingdom that Empyrean Divine Mist had founded!

Millions of years ago, Empyrean Divine Mist had already been an extreme Empyrean. However, he had been unable to step into the realm of True Divinity. Afterwards, because of some reason, he was hunted down by his own older brother and was forced into Tragic Death Valley.

Like this, Empyrean Divine Mist had been stranded in Tragic Death Valley for millions of years. In Tragic Death Valley, this was tens of millions of years. Only at the end did he meet Lin Ming.

This older brother of Empyrean Divine Mist, without a doubt, was Empyrean Divine Void! Or, as some others called him, True Divinity Divine Void!

Now, the spiritual leader of the Asura Road’s soul race was the so-called Divine Void Divine Kingdom. And this Divine Kingdom’s ruler was the culprit ultimately responsible for bringing about Empyrean Divine Mist’s ruin!

Lin Ming rapidly realized all of this.

In the past, when Lin Ming asked Empyrean Divine Mist why he had been chased into Tragic Death Valley, Empyrean Divine Mist had only responded with a single word – enmity.

It was only just before he left Tragic Death Valley that Empyrean Divine Mist revealed more about his past. The one who had chased him down had been his blood brother. Moreover, because of some strange telepathic connection between the brothers, as long as Empyrean Divine Mist left Tragic Death Valley his older brother would be able to sense him. Thus, it was impossible for Empyrean Divine Mist to leave.

All of this occurred in just several breaths of time. It was at this moment that he thought of something…

After a moment of thought, Lin Ming spoke, wanting to confirm his guess. “I have something I would like to ask…”

“Mm?”

In a situation where everyone was gathered around Qin Yi, it was extremely abrupt for Lin Ming to ask a sudden question. In this hall, Lin Ming had a very humble and common status. Besides Old Man Xue, Yue Liuxing, and Yue Qifeng, there had been no one else that took notice of him. If there was anything noticeable about Lin Ming then it might be that he was a human. In this hall, besides him, everyone else was a spiritas martial artist.

There were simply far, far too few human divine runic masters.

Qin Yi, Old Man Su, Clearshadow, Dreampearl, and the others only glanced at Lin Ming before ignoring him. Old Man Xue smiled, kindly asking, “What is it, boy? Are you trying to rain on his parade?”

In Old Man Xue’s eyes, Lin Ming had come here to play games and cause chaos. But, there were simply far too many talented individuals that had shown up. Perhaps instead of causing chaos, Lin Ming might be made a joke instead.

Lin Ming said without any hurry, “I want to ask, when did Senior Divine Void break into the True Divinity realm?”

Lin Ming’s question aroused an immediate frown from Qin Yi. Qin Yi’s eyes were swift and fierce as he glared at Lin Ming, “What insolence. The name of his majesty the Soul Emperor is not something someone like you can speak out loud!”

With this shout, killing intent surged out from Qin Yi’s body and locked onto Lin Ming, forcefully and menacingly. This sort of feeling was like a fight could break out at any moment.

The atmosphere became tense for a time. Old Man Xue hurriedly laughed as he tried to defuse the situation, “Lin Ming, the given name of his majesty the Soul Emperor cannot be spoken out loud so casually. But because you are not from the soul race you probably don’t know about this matter, so we’ll make an exception for you just this once. However, there won’t be a next time…”

Sometimes, the name of an emperor was a taboo term. In mortal nations, there were emperors that couldn’t be referred to by their name. And beyond even speaking out the name, sometimes even writing the name on paper was forbidden. One would need to replace the name of the emperor with other illustrious words instead.

Even so, Lin Ming had received the grace of Empyrean Divine Mist. Towards this Empyrean Divine Void who had forced Empyrean Divine Mist into a hopeless dead end, Lin Ming had no favorable impressions at all.

Lin Ming looked at Old Man Xue. Although Old Man Xue was a stingy and tricky fellow, the truth was that he had a good heart. Since Old Man Xue had tried to resolve the situation for him, Lin Ming didn’t want to make matters more difficult. He faintly said, “This junior truly didn’t know.”

“Mm, just make sure you pay a little bit more attention next time. Then, you asked when his majesty the Soul Emperor broke into the True Divinity realm?” Old Man Xue looked at Lin Ming, a little puzzled. He didn’t know why Lin Ming would suddenly ask such a question.

“Yes.” Lin Ming replied.

“Well… the current Soul Emperor broke through to the True Divinity realm 3 million years ago!” As Old Man Xue spoke he cupped his hands together across his chest, clearly showing his respect for Soul Emperor Divine Void.

3 million years?

Lin Ming’s eyes widened. He felt his speculations were much more likely to be correct. “Do you know the exact time?”

Lin Ming kept chasing for answers. This confused Old Man Xue; just what was Lin Ming asking these questions for?

However, Qin Yi arrogantly replied, “The exact time is 3.47 million years ago. When his majesty the Soul Emperor broke through to True Divinity, nine colors of heavenly tribulation descended from the skies, the winds and clouds changed, and all worshipped him. This matter was permanently written down in the holy texts of the soul race and is the most grand occasion to occur in the last 100 million years of my people! Your curiosity runs far too deep; just what does his majesty the Soul Emperor breaking through to the realm of True Divinity have to do with you?”

“Mm, I understand now…”

Lin Ming took a deep breath, his vision solemn.

When Divine Void broke into the realm of True Divinity, that was about the same time Empyrean Divine Mist was forced into Tragic Death Valley!

Chapter 1564 – Divine Runic Master Qualifications

The examination had already been underway for several dozen breaths of time and Lin Ming had drawn up 10 tiny rune structures. Although his speed was very slow, his strokes were steady and it was impossible for anyone to find a flaw in them.

However, besides this sort of proper and orderly method astonishing Old Man Xue, who knew of Lin Ming’s background, there was no one else that noticed him.

The attention of the people present was mostly concentrated on the two beautiful girls, Dreampearl and Clearshadow.

Their drawing of the divine runic symbol could be called as beautiful as flying dragons and dancing phoenixes, wonderful to the senses. Their ten slender fingers waved like lush plants in the wind, and when joined together with the divine runic pen that had absorbed the juices of all sorts of materials, the beautiful rainbows of lights they painted in the skies were as illusive and wonderful as a dream.

This exquisite and smooth technique left many people who had come to watch the examination, including some deacons, crying out in praise.

To watch these two young girls draw up divine runic symbols could be called a type of enjoyment.

“They are indeed apprentices taught by Old Su and Old Xue! From their appearances it shouldn’t difficult for them to obtain the qualifications for a divine runic master at all.”

Several deacons discussed amongst themselves with true essence sound transmission. The white-robed old man smiled, saying, “Yes, there shouldn’t be any problems for them to obtain the divine runic master qualifications, but perhaps the main play today might not be them. That main lead, has yet to begin…”

As the white-robed Elder spoke, he glanced towards the side. Everyone followed his vision. The one that he had been speaking about was the successor to the Divine Void Divine Kingdom’s King Qin, Qin Yi.

The examination had already been in progress for 20 some breaths of time, but Qin Yi’s hands were still calmly resting by his side. He had yet to do anything.

“What is he doing? Is this his attempt at being humble?”

As the deacons saw Qin Yi’s calm and idle appearance, all of them frowned. In truth, although they held some awe towards this talented youth from Divine Void Divine Kingdom, they didn’t believe that he would blossom in glory and drown out the light of Divine Rune City’s local examinees.

The competition had been going for such a long time but he hadn’t even moved yet. Whatever he was planning, it seemed a bit too theatrical.

“This fellow is too arrogant!” A deacon said, a bit disgusted.

“What is the meaning of this? Does he want our people to complete their drawings first so he can then display his high and mighty skills?”

The white-robed Elder shook his head, “You have misunderstood what he is doing. Although this Qin Yi is arrogant, that arrogance is within his bones and he won’t normally show it. The reason he has yet to move is not because he is intentionally demonstrating his strength, but because he is carefully analyzing and feeling out the structure and characteristics of all the materials. He is drawing up a divine runic symbol plan diagram in his mind. Once he is finished, he will draw it, and draw it all at once.”

When a top artist was drawing up a painting, they would have a complete image in their mind of what their painting would be like before they even began. This was what it meant to have a well thought out plan and one would be able to proceed with absolute confidence; to be forewarned was to be forearmed. A divine runic master was the same when they drew up divine runic symbols. If they first outlined the divine runic symbol in their mind, they would be able to draw up the complete symbol.

And just as the white-robed Elder finished speaking, Qin Yi began to move.

He casually picked up a handful of materials and tossed them in the air. He revolved his soul force, manifesting it into a sharp blade that chopped up these materials.

These divine runic symbol materials were all quite expensive. A normal divine runic master would process them with care, lest they make any mistakes and waste them. But, Qin Yi’s actions were bold and brave, because he had already become familiar with the structure and characteristics of these materials. Even the tiniest differences in the materials had been thoroughly probed by him earlier. This was the ability brought about by Qin Yi’s strong soul force.

With a series of slicing sounds, the batch of materials was processed by Qin Yi. Some had their juices drawn out, some were ground into powder, and some were sliced into parts.

Then, all of the materials gathered within Qin Yi’s palm.

This caused the white-robed Elder’s eyes to brighten. What wonderful hand work! At such a young age this Qin Yi was able to control several types of materials at once!

Normally, when a divine runic master drew up a divine runic symbol, they would handle materials one at a time in order to guarantee the highest chance of success. This was because one couldn’t split their mind in two, and the difficulty of controlling several materials at once could be imagined! It would make the process far, far more difficult!

Of course, the advantage of this was that the speed at which one drew up the divine runic symbol would be that much faster. Even so, these weren’t actions that a young divine runic master would dare to do.

“This boy is far fiercer than I originally thought! From the materials he has gathered, I think he is drawing up a divine runic symbol called the Fire Melting Symbol. This divine runic symbol is considered quite difficult amongst the first grade divine runic symbols!”

“He is an outstanding character to begin with, so it isn’t a surprise for him to choose the Fire Melting Symbol.”

Compared to Qin Yi manipulating a dozen plus materials at once, drawing a Fire Melting Symbol wasn’t difficult at all.

As everyone was speaking, Qin Yi began drawing. Without using the divine runic pen, he fused his finger with true essence and used it as a pen, pulling up the material juices to begin his drawing.

His speed was extremely fast. In just several blinks of the eye he drew up one tiny rune. Then in another several blinks he drew up a second. Then a third, fourth… soon he had dozens of them drawn up.

These tiny runes floated in the air, supported there by some invisible power. They were kept a good distance from each other as they faintly resonated with some mysterious Laws. Of course, these Laws were the Asura Road Laws.

Although Qin Yi hadn’t started until some time into the examination, with just a little bit of work, he had caught up to everyone else, and had even begun surpassing them.

“What amazing speed!”

The complexions of many people changed. Even Lin Ming glanced to Qin Yi more than once. This Qin Yi was clearly a talented young elite that was carefully raised by Divine Void Divine Kingdom. Although his cultivation might not be the highest, in terms of divine runic arts he was likely the top junior of his generation in the Divine Void Divine Kingdom.

However, Lin Ming only glanced at him twice before refocusing his thoughts and devoting his attention to the Overwhelming Rune. Even within the divine runic arts system, the Overwhelming Rune could only be considered a low difficulty rune as well as a low level rune.

However, Lin Ming had still chosen this rune because of the memories it recalled for him. Moreover, what Lin Ming was in now was the divine runic master examination and not a divine runic master competition. He would pass as long as he drew up any first grade divine runic symbol.

As Lin Ming calmly and steadily drew up the Overwhelming Rune, he heard two explosive sounds behind him. Two partially drawn divine runic symbols had burst into smoke and flames in the air. This was because some divine runic apprentices had been distracted by looking at Qin Yi and their soul forces had gone out of control, thus their divine runic symbols had blown up.

These two divine runic apprentices suddenly seemed as if they would begin crying.

Although they still had plenty of time remaining, the chances of them crossing the examination were small to begin with. At the start, when their soul force was at its peak, they still had some hopes that they would succeed. But as more time passed and their soul force weakened, their chances would naturally diminish.

Besides these two nearly hopeless divine runic apprentices, there were many others that were having trouble controlling their soul force. Even Yue Liuxing was focused on her work with an extremely tense expression on her face, as if she didn’t dare to allow anything to distract her. One could only say that Dreampearl, Clearshadow, and Qin Yi were far too different from them.

But, in this intense and exhilarating competition between divine runic apprentices, there was someone that didn’t pay much attention to Qin Yi at all, no matter how shocking his performance was. Rather, 99% of his attention was focused on Lin Ming. This person was Old Man Xue.

From the start of the examination until now, he had been staring at Lin Ming throughout.

He didn’t even glance at his own apprentice more than a few times. Although Qin Yi’s appearance had slightly diverted his attention, he had only looked at him for a moment before turning back to Lin Ming.

This sort of situation didn’t escape the eyes of Old Man Xue’s good friend, Old Su.

“I must say… Old Man Xue, why do you keep staring at that boy? Is there something strange going on?”

Old Su asked from beside Old Xue. His attention had originally been placed on his own apprentice, Clearshadow, so he thought that Old Xue should also be focused on his apprentice, Dreampearl. But, he discovered that Old Xue kept his eyes on Lin Ming from the start of the examination until now, not even blinking. It was like there was something quite interesting on Lin Ming’s face.

“He…”

Old Xue wryly smiled, not sure what to say.

Seeing the forced smile on Old Xue’s face, Old Su was even more interested. “You don’t care about your own apprentice, you haven’t looked at Clearshadow, and you aren’t even interested in that Divine Void Divine Kingdom genius, Qin Yi. Instead, you are focused on that boy alone? What secrets does he have?”

“Secrets…” Old Xue shook his head. “If I were to tell you that this boy had only studied the divine runic arts for one year, would you think I was stupid?”

“Only a year!?”

Old Su’s eyebrows leapt up. Before, he had heard Lin Ming and Old Xue squabbling. Old Xue had been mocking Lin Ming and saying that his chances of becoming a divine runic master were low, but Old Su only thought this was because Old Xue wanted Lin Ming to become his apprentice and pay tuition fees. He never imagined that Lin Ming had only studied the divine runic arts for year… no wonder Old Xue had thought that Lin Ming had come to the divine runic master examination to cause trouble.

“Are you sure he’s only studied for one year? The first year of practicing the divine runic arts could be called unimaginably difficult, but if you look at his drawing technique, do you really think that is possible from some novice who has only been studying for a single year?”

Old Su shook his head repeatedly, not willing to believe this.

Old Xue said, “That’s why I’ve been watching him. Qin Yi comes from the True Divinity Holy Land, Divine Void Divine Kingdom. In terms of divine runic master inheritances, although they are inferior to us, that is only in scale and quantity. In terms of the number of top divine runic masters, they have no fewer than we do. If Qin Yi is hand-taught by them then the skills he has displayed aren’t strange at all. But, this Lin Ming… I really cannot figure him out. He is far more amazing than Qin Yi is.”

“Are you sure you didn’t make a mistake?” Old Su said, still unable to believe this.

Old Xue said, “I also doubted it. I thought, did this boy really not start practicing the divine runic arts until a year ago? Perhaps he was playing with me at the time? But what would be his motive in doing so?”

Chapter 1569 – Perfect Pill Symbol

“He’s directly starting the third step!?”

A deacon remarked with surprise as he saw Lin Ming not going through any adjustments beforehand. If Lin Ming took out a gold god rune now then it was clearly because he was preparing to start the fusion process.

After a divine runic master completed the main form of a divine runic symbol, they would have consumed a great deal of soul force. And, the third step was the most essential step. If one didn’t rest then their chances of success would be much lower.

“Not everyone has the ability to maintain the main form of a divine runic symbol for such a long time without incurring some errors in the tiny runes. If he cannot calmly control the main form of the divine runic symbols and the order of the thousand some tiny runes, then the longer he continues the more soul force he will use up instead. Lin Ming might not have the ability to rest at this time so completing the drawing in a single continued attempt might be better.”

Another deacon said to the previous one.

The last deacon nodded, saying, “Yes, if he has the ability to rest at this time then he should be considered a teacher within the ranks of a second grade divine runic master.”

As these two deacons were speaking, Old Xue, Old Su, and the white-robed Elder were all staring at Lin Ming. They wanted to see just what this young man would do at this step.

Lin Ming’s right hand moved and the gold god rune slowly decomposed in a halo of golden light, turning into countless mystical lines that gathered onto the main form of the divine runic symbol. These laws were the Heavenly Dao Laws of the of Asura Road.

Without a doubt, Lin Ming’s understandings of the Asura Heavenly Dao far exceeded those of anyone present. In this aspect, after he thoroughly enlightened himself on the emperor jade as well as having studied the first volume of the Asura Sutra, although Lin Ming couldn’t control the Asura Heavenly Dao, wanting to borrow its strength was actually an extremely simple matter.

The Law lines soon fused into Lin Ming’s divine runic symbol. With Lin Ming’s familiarity with the Asura Heavenly Dao, he could complete the fusion process in a mere incense stick of time.

However, Lin Ming didn’t choose to do this. After all, completing the third step in a mere incense stick of time would have been far too shocking, and it might even arouse certain suspicious in those present.

Thus, Lin Ming decided to slow down his speed. This was only an examination and not a competition; as long as he finished then he was fine.

A quarter hour soon passed. Clearshadow and Dreampearl both completed the main forms of their divine runic symbol and began the third fusion step.

They were weaker than Qi Yi, so they couldn’t rest before the third step like he could. For them, this last fusion step would be filled with difficulties.

After half a quarter hour passed, beads of sweat began to appear on Qin Yi’s forehead. He had entered into a completely absorbed state. The Law runes were slowly pushed into the divine runic symbol. With his soul force, lasting until now was not easy.

Finally, Qin Yi fused the last Law line into the divine runic symbol. His Heart of the Medicine Furnace drawing was finally complete!

As Qin Yi felt the power of Laws gushing forth from the Heart of the Medicine Furnace, he grinned.

He had succeeded! Moreover, the process had been relatively easy. With overwhelming superiority he had obtained the qualifications to become a second grade divine runic master and was also the most extraordinary individual in this examination.

In that moment, beams of multicolored light blossomed from the Heart of the Medicine Furnace. Qin Yi reached out for the divine runic symbol, but just as he was about to touch it, his expression froze. With disbelief thick on his features, he turned to see Lin Ming. At some unknown time, Lin Ming had also completed his Pill Resting Symbol.

After taking his divine runic symbol, Lin Ming placed it on a tray in preparation for the proctor Elder to examine it.

Lin Ming had used less than half an hour to complete this third step fusion process. It was nearly half the time that Qin Yi had spent.

Old Su and Old Xue watched Lin Ming complete the third step. The entire process was completed without any kind of thrilling, soul-struggling scene at all. Rather, he had completed the third step easily and pleasantly, the entire drawing of the divine runic symbol having been completed in a single go.

No one had expected that Lin Ming’s third step would be completed in such a manner. The most difficult part of the second grade divine runic symbol was the third step, but in Lin Ming’s hands, there didn’t seem to be any difficulty at all.

“Is it… over?”

Old Xue and Old Sue glanced at each other. They had originally hoped that there would be some difficulties for Lin Ming in the third step and they wanted to see just how he resolved the situation, but, what truly happened had far outstripped their expectations. This inevitably caused a peculiar feeling to form in their hearts. Was Lin Ming’s third step really the same as everyone else’s third step?

Two deacons picked up Lin Ming and Qin Yi’s divine runic symbols, handing them over to the white-robed Elder.

The white-robed Elder looked deeply at the two examinees. The first divine runic symbol he chose to examine was Qin Yi’s Heart of the Medicine Furnace.

With a single sweep of his sense, the white-robed Elder approximately understood the situation. As a sixth grade divine runic master he could nearly instantly judge a second grade divine runic symbol and what the quality was like.

“Good!”

The white-robed Elder said from the depths of his heart. Although Qin Yi’s Heart of the Medicine Furnace couldn’t be called perfect in every aspect, every part of the drawing process had been above average. This was truly a commendable accomplishment. This Heart of the Medicine Furnace was a considerably well done divine runic symbol that could be sold at a decent price.

“Congratulations Qin Yi, you are now a second grade divine runic master!”

Qin Yi faintly smiled after having his results confirmed by the white-robed Elder. This assessment was well within his expectations; he was confident in his divine runic symbol. What he cared about was what Lin Ming’s evaluation would be like.

At this time, the white-robed Elder looked at the Pill Resting Symbol that Lin Ming had drawn up.

The white-robed Elder also wanted to see if there were any problems in this Pill Resting Symbol. Lin Ming had simply fused the Asura Heavenly Dao into this divine runic symbol far too easily.

The Pill Resting Symbol that Lin Ming drew up was three inches long and two inches wide, just like a rectangle. The charm’s surface was filled with countless mystical lines; it didn’t seem like something that was drawn up by a person. Even an amateur would see that this divine runic symbol was beautiful and symmetrical.

The white-robed Elder soaked his soul force into the Pill Resting Symbol and took a mental swim through its lines. After confirming the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws that were within the symbol, the white-robed Elder took a deep breath.

Not only was the Pill Resting Symbol that Lin Ming drew up completely up to standards, but it was extremely valuable.

“Perfect…”

The white-robed Elder whispered this evaluation to himself. This Pill Resting Symbol, whether it was the processing and handling of materials, structure of tiny runes, distribution of energy, or even the final fusion of the Asura Heavenly Dao rules, everything could be called the absolute peak of perfection that a low level divine runic master could accomplish.

It was hard to imagine that this divine runic symbol had come from the hands of a human youth. Just how did this boy study? And who was his teacher?

As the white-robed Elder was appraising Lin Ming’s Pill Resting Symbol, Qin Yi was noticing the expression on the old man’s face. As Qin Yi saw the awe on the old man’s face as well as the perfect evaluation, Qin Yi felt a surge of frustration. Without a doubt, the quality of the Pill Resting Symbol that Lin Ming drew up had been superior to his own Heart of the Medicine Furnace!

“Let me take a look!”

Old Xue impatiently walked over, nearly grabbing the Pill Resting Symbol from the white-robed Elder’s hands. After sweeping through it with his divine sense, his eyelids jumped up. This boy, his abilities were truly deep…

Old Xue even suspected that the Lin Ming he saw a year ago was a different person from the Lin Ming he was staring at now.

Old Xue passed the divine runic symbol to Old Su.

As Old Su looked at it, he too was left dumbfounded.

“What a great Pill Resting Symbol. Even a fourth grade divine runic master is inferior… I have no idea how he did the fusion process. There must be some sort of trick inside.”

Old Su speculated. Old Xue thought for a moment, then said, “This boy, he isn’t a part of my Divine Runic Masters Guild…”

“We must bring him in, we have to bring him in! We definitely cannot lose such talent! If we do things right then he might even become the next Guild President!”

The Divine Runic Masters Guild was always eager to bring in more talented individuals. The Divine Runic Masters Guild was originally a loose organization, and only by bringing in more talented people would Divine Rune City become more powerful. The previous Guild Presidents of the Divine Runic Masters Guild had all been extremely noble and renowned seventh grade divine runic masters that had been fairly elected by the guild.

“Lin Ming, I want to ask you, would you like to join my Divine Runic Masters Guild?” Without Old Su and Old Xue speaking, the white-robed Elder had already asked Lin Ming.

“Do I want to join the Divine Runic Masters Guild?”

Lin Ming traced his chin, making his decision seem as theatrical as he could.

He definitely wanted to join the Divine Runic Masters Guild, after all, this was the entire reason he had come to take this examination. Joining the Divine Runic Masters Guild would make everything far more convenient for him.

First, if he joined the Divine Runic Masters Guild then he would be able to obtain their protection. This would make him relatively more safe. Next, if he joined he would have sufficient status to contact Blood Moon and obtain the Celestial Tyrant Manual. Third, materials would be much easier to obtain in the Divine Runic Masters Guild and there would even be a discount. This was necessary for him to find the ancient pill recipes and materials needed for the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace.

Although Lin Ming had already come here with this plan, he knew that truly peak geniuses would have far more advantages if they joined the Divine Runic Masters Guild. This was because this sort of talented individual would have many other influences seeking to take them in. The inner Asura Road was an incomparably vast land and there were multiple divine runic master organizations besides Divine Rune City. For instance, Qin Yi’s Divine Void Divine Kingdom, in terms of divine runic arts skills, wasn’t that different from the Divine Runic Masters Guild.

Thus, Lin Ming didn’t mind trying to obtain more benefits from joining the Divine Runic Masters Guild.

Thinking of this, he said, “Can I wait before making this decision? When I passed the first grade divine runic master examination I was able to continue to the second grade divine runic master examination. So, since I’ve passed the second grade divine runic master examination, can I continue to the third grade divine runic master examination?”

As Lin Ming asked this, Old Xue, Old Su, and the white-robed Elder all froze, their expressions stiffening. Lin Ming wanted to take the third grade divine runic master examination?

“You’re saying that… you want to take the third grade divine runic master examination?”

Old Xue looked at Lin Ming with amazement. Not only were the three old men shocked but even the other examinees in the resting area, including Yue Qifeng and Yue Liuxing, were startled. It was already incredible for Lin Ming to pass the examination for a second grade divine runic master, but he wanted to continue to the third grade examination? Really, people never gave up until they failed!

Chapter 1570 – Third Grade Divine Runic Master Examination

Normally, before a martial artist became a third grade divine runic master they would study for dozens of years or even over a hundred years of time.

The reason that the time fluctuated so much was because even as a young martial artist studied the divine runic arts, they still had to put time into cultivating. And, different people would divide their time in varying proportions. If someone invested more time into the divine runic arts then they would learn it faster than others, but no matter how much time they invested it would still take 20-30 years.

But compared to Lin Ming, who wasn’t even sixty years of age, Old Xue could go crazy and still not figure out how Lin Ming had allocated his time.

How could he dual cultivate body and energy, opening the complete Eight Inner Hidden Gates and even achieving a Divine Lord realm cultivation as he even practiced the divine runic arts to such a degree?

“Are you sure you want to take the third grade divine runic master examination?”

Lin Ming nodded. “Yes, this junior only wishes to try; I am not fully confident that I will pass.”

Lin Ming was indeed unable to ascertain whether or not he would be able to successfully draw up a third grade divine runic symbol. Even if he failed somewhere he should still be close to reaching the third fusion step, and once he truly began the third step, then completing a third grade divine runic symbol shouldn’t be too difficult.

The third step of the divine runic arts was Lin Ming’s greatest advantage.

If Lin Ming could become a third grade divine runic master and then join the Divine Runic Masters Guild, his status would be completely different from that of a second grade divine runic master.

Young second grade divine runic masters like Qin Yi were rare in the inner Asura Road, but they existed. Every influence was always raising a new generation every ten years, and after so much time there were bound to be some extraordinary individuals that appeared.

The reason that Qin Yi seemed so splendid here was because the Divine Runic Masters Guild would hold examinations every year, year after year. Because of this, it was not possible to concentrate the number of geniuses together. If the geniuses of the last thousand years of the Divine Runic Masters Guild were added up then that would be a dreadful number.

However, for Lin Ming, if he could become a third grade divine runic master at his young age then that would be something that might not happen in a thousand or even ten thousand years.

In this sort of situation, Lin Ming would be highly valued by the Divine Runic Masters Guild. With this status, everything would be much easier for him to do.

As for what others would do such as suspecting him or conspiring to ruin him, Lin Ming wasn’t afraid of this. In terms of individual combat strength he could already fight an ordinary World King. And with Xiao Moxian’s help as well as the life-saving card of Primordius Heavenly Palace, Lin Ming could calmly retreat even if he faced a middle level World King.

And if he had to face a spiritas, then Lin Ming also had the fatal divine tool that was their ultimate nemesis!

Lin Ming didn’t fear middle level World Kings and World Kings weren’t like cabbages spread everywhere. Looking at the entire Divine Runic Masters Guild, a World King was at the rank of an Elder. There were even some sixth grade divine runic masters with a half-step World King cultivation.

Thus, Lin Ming had the ability to protect himself in the Divine Runic Masters Guild.

And most importantly, no one knew of his true strength. This provided an extra layer of protection for him.

“Since you passed the second grade divine runic master examination, then according to the rules of the Divine Runic Masters Guild you can choose to continue onwards to the third grade divine runic masters examination. Besides Lin Ming, does anyone else wish participate in the third grade divine runic master examination?”

The white-robed Elder looked at Qin Yi. Out of everyone else present, only Qin Yi had completed the second grade divine runic master examination, thus he also had the qualifications to join Lin Ming.

Qin Yi’s complexion changed, becoming extremely ugly.

He had nearly no hope of successfully drawing up a third grade divine runic symbol.

In fact, at the start, Qin Yi had been planning to join the third grade divine runic master examination. But, this was not because he thought of passing it but because he wanted to show off his dazzling skills.

In drawing up a third grade divine runic symbol, Qin Yi could complete 70-80% of it. It was only the final step of fusing together the Asura Heavenly Dao that he could not succeed at.

But now, he had been grouped together with this freak Lin Ming. Lin Ming clearly had plans of joining the third grade divine runic master examination, so how could Qin Yi possibly join him just to act as a foil and make him shine brighter?

He grit his teeth, remaining silent. This was the same as admitting he was withdrawing from the third grade examination.

“Mm… then it’s only Lin Ming who will take the examination? Alright then, Lin Ming, you come with me to the side room… I will allow you to rest for 10 hours in a time enchantment. Then, you can choose the materials you need. If you can complete any third grade divine runic symbol then you’ll have passed.”

The white-robed Elder said. Giving Lin Ming 10 hours to rest was more than enough.

Lin Ming didn’t want to rest for such a long time but he didn’t decline the offer. After giving his thanks, he walked towards the side room.

Allowing Lin Ming to change environments and undergo the examination in the side room was to reduce external disturbances to the lowest amount.

This was also to increase Lin Ming’s chances of passing the third grade divine runic master examination.

The white-robed Elder was secretly hoping that Lin Ming would pass the third grade divine runic mater examination. To the Divine Runic Masters Guild this would be a cause worthy of great celebration. Once this matter was passed on to the other divine runic master organizations then they would earn considerable face.

Moreover, Lin Ming would inevitably have amazing achievements in the future. After Lin Ming became some powerful and mighty figure, then this white-robed Elder would also be able to boast that he was the one who personally oversaw his third grade divine runic master examination.

………..

Lin Ming followed the white-robed Elder to a side room. After he left, Clearshadow and Dreampearl also finished their own second grade divine runic master examinations. Unfortunately, they had both failed to complete their divine runic symbols by the tiniest amount.

In ordinary times, if Clearshadow and Dreampearl had been able to display their usual skill then they would have been able to complete a second grade divine runic symbol. But today, seemingly because the appearance of Lin Ming and Qin Yi placed a considerable amount of pressure on them, they hadn’t been able to display their highest level of skill. After failing twice, this meant they had failed their examination.

Upon failing the examination, the two young women looked forlorn and depressed. Old Xue and Old Su quickly cheered them up with some words, but at this time they also discovered that Qin Yi, who had completed his second grade divine runic master examination, had an extremely ugly complexion.

What happened?

Did Qin Yi also fail?

If Qin Yi failed then that would have provided a little bit of comfort to Clearshadow and Dreampearl. But, this didn’t seem likely.

“Teacher, what happened to Qin Yi? He shouldn’t have failed his examination, right?”

Before this, Clearshadow and Dreampearl had both been in a completely focused state so they didn’t know what had happened around them.

“Qin Yi…” Old Xue forced a smile. “He indeed passed the examination and he did so extremely splendidly. But what a pity, there is always someone stronger than the strong. Lin Ming completed his second grade divine runic symbol even more perfectly, and, what is most perturbing of all is that after Lin Ming finished his second grade divine runic master examination he wanted to carry on to the third grade divine runic master examination. As for Qin Yi, he gave up. He likely knew he didn’t have the ability to pass… this is the same as admitting that he is inferior to Lin Ming, so how could his complexion be any good?”

In Old Xue’s opinion, Qin Yi’s talent in the divine runic arts should be the best amongst the juniors of Divine Void Divine Kingdom. For him to be frustrated like this by one of his peers, this was definitely an attack on his mindset.

After listening to Old Xue’s words, Clearshadow and Dreampearl’s mouths fell open. They weren’t able to respond for a long time.

“Teacher… are you saying that Lin Ming, he… he is continuing on to the third grade divine runic master examination?”

“That’s right. Lin Ming should have already started his examination by now.”

Lin Ming had rested for 10 hours within a time enchantment. Now that half an hour had passed, he should have started his examination by now.

“This is… the third grade divine runic master examination…”

Clearshadow and Dreampearl were both in a muddled daze. The two of them hadn’t even been able to complete the second grade divine runic master examination and yet Lin Ming went straight to the third grade examination!

How could they live like this!

For a time, both of them were immensely frustrated.

Old Su saw the emotions plain on their faces, and said with a comforting tone, “Lin Ming won’t necessarily pass the third grade examination. His chances of passing the third grade examination might not be higher than your chances of passing the second grade examination. Your problems were that you weren’t able to display your true skill today, but that isn’t something you should be discouraged by. Instead, that Qin Yi was likely struck harder by this than you two were.”

Old Su said, nudging his head towards Qin Yi.

At this time, Qin Yi was sitting in the resting area, his face grim and cloudy as if someone in his family had died.

Although he looked like he was calmly sipping tea, his eyes were glued to the doors of the side room. It was obvious that he cared a great deal about Lin Ming’s results.

Time slowly passed. In the blink of an eye, another two hours passed.

Lin Ming’s examination was already halfway over.

Chapter 1572 – Entering the Guild

“Hey little fellow, how about we talk for a bit.”

After Lin Ming obtained the qualifications to become a third grade divine runic master, he knew that these several old geezers would have many questions they would want to ask him; this was something he couldn’t avoid.

Lin Ming nodded, “Well, that’s fine, we can speak in another room.”

“If you will.”

The white-robed Elder, Old Su, and Old Xue brought Lin Ming to a different room. After passing through the door, Old Xue turned and said to his apprentice Dreampearl, “The lot of you can wait outside.”

Dreampearl scratched her head, curiously looking towards the room. She also wanted to know what Lin Ming’s status was but she had been blocked by Old Xue.

She pursed her lips, muttering, “It’s like they are trying to keep everything a secret, what’s so great about knowing anyways.”

Dreampearl sat on a stone chair, not feeling very happy. She was filled with curiosity towards this human youth that was around her age and in fact really did want to know where Lin Ming came from and how he practiced to become so formidable.

“That fellow should have a powerful master.”

Clearshadow said from beside Dreampearl.

“Definitely… and they are probably much fiercer than our masters…”

Dreampearl said without mincing her words. As Old Xue heard this just as he was closing the door, he nearly choked on himself.

“This rascally girl!”

Old Xue awkwardly coughed. He could only pretend that he didn’t hear this. But, this was the truth. As he measured his own level, he felt that it was impossible for him to teach an apprentice like Lin Ming. Even an extremely good piece of jade would need a grandmaster to cut and polish it into a perfect piece of art. The level of a master was extremely important in determining the level of an apprentice.

The three old men sat in front of Lin Ming. The white-robed Elder took out a divine runic master’s robe and a divine runic master badge.

“This is for you. This badge will serve as your third grade divine runic master certificate and this divine runic master robe is also the uniform of the Divine Runic Masters Guild. In the Asura Road, the styles of badges and robes differ between the varying great influences that offer them, but they are mostly the same besides some minor differences…”

“Mm, thank you.”

Lin Ming nodded. He waved his hand and this robe appeared on his body.

The divine runic master robe produced by the Divine Runic Masters Guild was in essence manifestations of energy produced by runes. Whether it was putting it on or taking it off, one only needed to think it.

As Lin Ming put on the robe he could feel the surrounding heaven and earth origin energy as well as the Laws being dragged towards it. Even his soul force was being faintly nourished. It was clear that this robe wasn’t some ordinary piece of clothing.

As for the badge, it was a carefully crafted magic tool that made one’s soul force and mental focus more concetrated. The two objects were above the level of a medium-grade spirit artifact.

“Seniors, if you have any questions then this junior will try to answer to the best I can.” After Lin Ming put on the dressings of a divine runic master, his tall figure perfectly accented his new clothing, making him seem ethereal and elegant.

“There are a few questions I would like to ask. What I am very curious about is just who is your teacher? No matter how much I think of it, I cannot think of anyone in the entire inner Asura Road that would be able to secretly and quietly teach an apprentice like you.”

Without Lin Ming saying anything first, the white-robed Elder directly asked Lin Ming about his teacher.

The inner Asura Road had many divine runic master organizations and they fiercely competed against each other. If they could pull a top master to join their guild, that was an event worthy of great celebration. It would be far greater than bringing in a junior like Lin Ming.

Lin Ming said, “My teacher has been living in seclusion for many years, and is unwilling to disclose his identity…”

Lin Ming had already thought up a good answer. As for the white-robed Elder, a look of deep disappoint appeared on his face. But in truth he had already anticipated this. Such a divine runic grandmaster would receive the greatest standard of reception and respect from any influence. If this person wanted to make themselves public they would have already done so. Moreover, this person might not want to join the Divine Runic Masters Guild to begin with.

Still, the white-robed Elder didn’t give up. He continued to ask, “Then let me venture another question: just what grade of a divine runic master is your teacher?”

The white-robed Elder already guessed that Lin Ming’s teacher was at least a seventh grade divine runic master. He might even surpass the current President of the Divine Runic Masters Guild.

Lin Ming said, “I apologize. It isn’t that I don’t want to say it but because I do not know what the level of my teacher’s divine runic arts has reached. According to what I know, teacher has already been in deep seclusion for 100-200 million years. Even if he were to come out of hiding, I fear that not many people would recognize him…”

Lin Ming concocted a wild story. But in this specific situation with his awe-inspiring performance just now, no matter how ridiculous his words were, those present still might believe him. This was because they truly did think that Lin Ming had such a heaven-shaking teacher.

“Seclusion… for 100-200 million years!” The white-robed Elder’s eyebrows jumped up. He looked at the two other old men, fear and awe coloring his complexion.

Old Xue gulped. Even though he had expected that Lin Ming’s teacher was extremely terrifying, if Lin Ming’s master had gone into seclusion for 100-200 million years then wouldn’t that make his true age around 200-300 million years old?

Such an age already far exceeded the 100 million year lifespan limit of an Empyrean.

Then, it was either that Lin Ming’s teacher had used some secret technique to go into deep hibernation, or that he was a True Divinity level powerhouse!

And in Old Xue’s opinion, the latter possibility was a bit more likely…

Thinking of Lin Ming’s master, Old Xue forced a smile. “I must say kid, you tricked me well. You were clearly under the guidance of a divine runic grandmaster and yet you acted like you didn’t know anything about the divine runic arts. It seems you really wanted to play around with an old man like me… by the way, when you bought that jade from me…”

Old Xue’s eyes widened. He felt that he had been hoodwinked by Lin Ming once again! That jade piece of indeterminable origin might have been some sort of extraordinary treasure.

“Hey little fellow, you were quite particular in buying that little piece of jade. Why don’t you tell me more about it so that I can widen my horizons…”

Old Xue puckered his lips, feeling sad. He was now 99% sure that he had sold that broken jade for a major loss!

“Jade?” Lin Ming pretended to be surprised. “Oh, I remember. A year ago I found that broken jade in your stall and thought it was some amazing ancient treasure, but after I took it to be appraised by my master the result was that I had been mistaken. Sure enough, there were no advantages for me…”

Lin Ming flippantly said. But, Old Xue didn’t believe this at all. With a pained expression he said, “Come on, just tell me honestly what the jade was. I’ve already been conned by you so you can tell me what it is right? Since my eyes were poor I can only blame myself for that. I just want to know what use that little trinket had.”

“Senior… you’ve really… thought too much about this…” A cunning light flashed in Lin Ming’s eyes but he concealed it well. No matter what Old Xue said, Lin Ming definitely wouldn’t disclose the origins of that jade piece. This caused Old Xue to feel even more depressed. He was more and more sure that he had been bamboozled by Lin Ming, and as a divine runic master who was proud of his appraisal ability, the most painful and aggrieving matter was to be swindled by others and not know how.

Old Xue seemed to want to ask something else, but at this time the white-robed Elder dryly coughed a few times and said, “Lin Ming, let’s speak about formal matters now. I want to ask you – do you have any intentions of joining my Divine Runic Masters Guild?”

This matter was the most important question that the white-robed Elder wanted to ask Lin Ming.

He originally inquired about Lin Ming’s teacher because he still had hopes that there was a one-in-a-million chance he could win over Lin Ming’s teacher and have him join the divine runic masters guild.

But as he expected, that wouldn’t be possible. So, his most vital task now was to win Lin Ming over to join their Divine Runic Masters Guild.

For an organization like the Divine Runic Masters Guild, the most essential factor of their strength was the quantity and quality of their divine runic masters.

The reason that Divine Rune City was able to develop to its current scale was because they relied on their many divine runic masters as well a decent number of alchemists.

The more powerful and the greater number of divine runic masters there were, the more influential the Divine Runic Masters Guild would become. In particular, seventh grade divine runic masters had a great appeal, one that drew in many others. This sort of divine runic grandmaster would always be able to draw in divine runic masters from nearby regions so that they would join the Divine Runic Masters Guild out of their admiration.

At the same time, a great number of influences would rush here to cooperate with the Divine Runic Masters Guild, providing all sorts of favorable conditions for them.

Over time, Divine Rune City would become increasingly prosperous. In terms of all sorts of transactions, access to talented individuals, possession of rare and precious resources, everything would rise exponentially.

Thus, it could be said that the influence and strength of the Divine Runic Masters Guild was closely intertwined with everyone’s benefits in Divine Rune City.

If the Divine Runic Masters Guild ever declined, then Divine Rune City would exist in name only.

“You don’t have to be in a hurry to respond. First, let me tell you about the advantages of joining the Divine Runic Masters Guild…” The white-robed Elder took out a handbook and handed it to Lin Ming.

“This is the internal handbook of the Divine Runic Masters Guild. It has the rules and conditions that members must abide by. If you join the Divine Runic Masters Guild then if you purchase materials in Divine Rune City, we can offer you a 15% discount. This is the highest discount and not even Elders have a better deal. Of course, new divine runic masters definitely do not receive this treatment.

“You will also possess the authority to browse the jade slips in the Divine Runic Masters Guild’s library. Even if it is the most core jade slip inheritances, you will still have the ability to apply for viewing.

“In addition, every month the Divine Runic Masters Guild will give you a fixed number of contribution points. In the Divine Runic Masters Guild, these contribution points are used to purchase all sorts of rare and precious materials and they are also much handier than origin energy runes. If you have points then you have rights to purchase materials before anyone else.”

The white-robed Elder immediately put forth so many good conditions. This was the kind of treatment that the Divine Runic Masters Guild would offer to an ordinary Elder, but now all of this was promised to Lin Ming. This was because with Lin Ming’s current achievements, becoming an Elder was just a matter of time. He would become a Red-Robed Elder or possibly even the future Guild President.

These conditions were also the limit that the white-robed Elder could offer. Lin Ming was satisfied with these conditions. He thought for a moment and then said, “Junior has a matter that he would like to consult with several seniors about.”

“Speak your mind.”

Lin Ming thought about his words for a moment and then said, “According to what this junior knows, there are several nearby influences that have long-term cooperation with the Divine Runic Masters Guild… and, there is an influence that this junior is extremely interested in. They are the assassin organization known as Heaven’s Net!”

Chapter 1577 – Life-death Seclusion of the Emperor

Eunuch Liang was one of the chief eunuchs of Marvel Blue Imperial Palace as well as a trusted subordinate of the Marvel Blue Emperor. In the past, Blood Moon had done a favor for Eunuch Liang and there was even some friendship between them. The reason that Blood Moon came to Marvel Blue Imperial Palace was also because Eunuch Liang brought both sides together. Although Blood Moon could be said to be on a mission, the truth was that this was more a form of asylum. In Marvel Blue Imperial Palace, Blood Moon would be able to obtain some protection. Even so, she would have to return to Heaven’s Net sooner or later. That was where she had placed so much effort in these years to establish her own business and foundation, and there was also something there she needed to retrieve.

Before Blood Moon entered the harem, Eunuch Liang had referred to her as ‘miss’. But now, he also referred to her as ‘Imperial Concubine’. Eunuch Liang was faintly aware that Blood Moon came from the Divine Realm and she also had a blood enemy there, one that she was absolutely irreconcilable with.

Blood Moon had hidden her identity and had come to the Asura Road alone to temper and gain experience. In the end, she had become one of the leaders of Heaven’s Net. All of this was because of this blood enemy of hers. She needed to take revenge for all her grudges, but, it seemed that Blood Moon’s enemy had a cultivation at the Great World King realm. With her current strength, she simply wasn’t his match.

In these years, Blood Moon had desperately cultivated, seeking all chances regardless of how dangerous they were. However, even though she made progress, her enemy also made progress. It was hard to say whether or not she would be able to catch up to him in her lifetime!

As this irreconcilable blood enemy of hers was mentioned, a thick and profound killing intent flashed in her eyes, only fading after a long time. In this world there were few things that could cause her to lose her composure, but, this enemy from the Divine Realm was one of them.

She calmed her mind and no longer thought about the hatred of the past. She said, “Eunuch Liang, I heard that His Majesty will be entering life-death seclusion in the next few days; is this news true?”

Eunuch Liang sighed as the topic of the Marvel Blue Emperor’s closed door seclusion was mentioned. “It is necessary seclusion… His Majesty follows the Heavenly Dao and has a great destiny upon his body. I only hope that during this seclusion, His Majesty will be able to make another breakthrough and live forever…”

Although Eunuch Liang said this, his tone and expression indicated that he wasn’t too optimistic that the Marvel Blue Sovereign would be able to successfully pass this closed door seclusion.

As for Blood Moon herself, she definitely didn’t expect that the Marvel Blue Emperor would be able to prolong his life. His fires of life had flickered out and he was at the end of his rope. If he were to make another breakthrough here then that would truly be violating the Heavenly Dao!

If the Marvel Blue Sovereign could have achieved this then he would have already broken through the shackles of a World King and become an Empyrean. He wouldn’t be like he was today, desperately struggling with his life on the line.

Blood Moon also knew that a hundred years ago, the Marvel Blue Emperor had realized he didn’t have much time remaining on the mortal coil. He had even attempted to open the final smelting trial of the Asura Road, but, he had been too old and wasn’t able to obtain the qualifications to enter. Then, the Marvel Blue Emperor had gathered a group of top masters to explore one of the forbidden death zones of the inner Asura Road – the Forbidden Divine Barrens. He had hoped to seek out some immortal medicines but in the end he remained disappointed.

By then, the Marvel Blue Emperor had done everything he could. His strength weakened by the day and his life’s essence energy continued to fade from him, even as his boundary dropped. Now, at death’s door, he had chosen to enter life-death closed door seclusion. There was simply no chance of him making another breakthrough. Without a doubt, his chamber would become his grave.

Blood Moon didn’t think that the Marvel Blue Emperor would be able to cross this tribulation. What she cared for now was with the Marvel Blue Emperor in life-death closed door seclusion, just who was managing the affairs of the nation?

“Eunuch Liang, with His Majesty in seclusion, who is managing the nation?”

“According to the laws and customs of the court, the Empress is the one wielding the imperial jade seal to serve as temporary manager of national matters. Once His Majesty leaves seclusion then the imperial jade seal will be returned to him. If there is some accident and His Majesty doesn’t leave seclusion, then the Empress will pass the imperial jade seal on to the new Emperor…”

Blood Moon frowned upon hearing this. If the Empress was the one holding power, then this wasn’t good news to her at all!

Eunuch Liang seemed to guess what she was thinking. He said, “Although the Empress is the one managing the national affairs, she still won’t act unreasonably. Miss, please feel relieved…”

“Mmm… I hope that is true…”

Blood Moon said. She rubbed her temples. There were far too many things that had happened in these last few years, making her feel exhausted as if she couldn’t keep up with it all!

………

After two days there was still no movement in the Imperial Palace. And on the third day, Lin Ming returned once more to Full Moon Hall.

During these two days, Lin Ming had kept himself busy. He had inquired about a great deal of news.

He knew now that the Emperor of Marvel Blue Nation had a Great World King cultivation. However, his life was nearing its end and he didn’t have much longer to live. He would die in his chambers soon.

With the old Emperor soon to die, this brought about the matter of establishing a new Emperor.

During the Marvel Blue Emperor’s long life, he had over a thousand children. When his grandchildren and great grandchildren were added on, this number rose exponentially higher.

Of these many descendants, only two of them had the qualifications to become the new Emperor.

These two people were Prince Marvel Shen and Grandprince Marvel Snow.

Prince Marvel Shen was older and his cultivation was at the peak Holy Lord realm. During these years, he had developed and amassed a considerable amount of influence and power.

As for Grandprince Marvel Snow, he was younger and his cultivation was at the early Holy Lord realm. He could be considered a promising young man, and his talent even surpassed that of Prince Marvel Shen. As for the power he had developed, it was much smaller. Now, both Marvel Shen and Marvel Snow had their supporters; it was hard to say whose hands the throne would fall into.

And, there was one piece of news that Lin Ming paid particular attention to…

Blood Moon, also known as Imperial Concubine Moon, had been gifted to the Marvel Blue Emperor by Grandprince Marvel Snow.

When Marvel Snow gifted Blood Moon to the Marvel Blue Emperor, the Marvel Blue Emperor’s lifespan was already coming to its natural end; he had no wants or desires to take in a new concubine. But even so, the Marvel Blue Emperor had given Blood Moon the title of Imperial Concubine Moon. Without a doubt, this was because the Marvel Blue Emperor wanted to help Marvel Snow increase his influence.

Lin Ming suspected that the Marvel Blue Emperor intentionally did this to blur the official choice of successors. He wanted the prince and grandprince to struggle for the throne so that the most qualified one would be able to occupy it!

This was also a reasonable matter. The reason that the Marvel Blue Emperor was able to sit steadily on his throne was his own strength. But, for the next emperor, they would either need a World King level of strength, or they would need to have the means and methods to rule as well as the ability to amass and develop their own influence! Only by accomplishing these two matters to their fullest extent could one rule their own nation!

“Lin Ming, what do we do now?”

Xiao Moxian asked. She was sitting on a bench in Full Moon Hall, her elbows resting on a table as she propped up her chin. She was a little bit worried. They had already been in Marvel Blue Nation for so many days and yet they hadn’t even seen a hint of the Celestial Tyrant Manual.

“There’s nothing we can do for now. We can only wait.”

Lin Ming replied simply. He didn’t seem to be in a hurry at all, but the truth was that even after he returned to Full Moon Hall, although Blood Moon had been willing to see him again, her attitude towards him had clearly been much more distant.

In Blood Moon’s opinion, although Lin Ming was an outstanding young elite worth befriending and who would also have a limitless future, that was something far off from now. He simply didn’t have the ability to help her solve her current troubles.

Right now, Blood Moon was within Marvel Blue Imperial Palace. She faced layers upon layers of pressure. Not only did she have to attend to the internal struggles within the Imperial Palace, she also had to be on guard against the turmoil that was rocking Heaven’s Net!

Moreover, because Blood Moon had been betrayed by a close subordinate of hers, she had received a wound that had yet to heal, making matters even worse!

In Blood Moon’s eyes, if Lin Ming’s master was willing to help then solving her problems would be as easy as lifting their hand. However, if Lin Ming’s master wasn’t willing to help, then just a junior like Lin Ming alone wouldn’t be of any assistance to her.

Thus, the second time that Lin Ming came to Full Moon Hall, she had only politely summoned him. She had a young eunuch lead Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian to a side hall and basically didn’t see him at all.

Like this, five days passed. Lin Ming still hadn’t seen Blood Moon.

And in Full Moon Hall, Lin Ming wasn’t even able to walk as he pleased. After all, there were women everywhere and if he wasn’t careful he would see far too much of their bodies.

Things continuing like this was not a plan.

However, Lin Ming was clear that if he couldn’t put out some sort of condition that could move Blood Moon, it was simply impossible for him to borrow her transcendent divine might for any period of time.

Thus, Lin Ming didn’t even mention the matter of the Celestial Tyrant Manual. He peacefully stayed at Full Moon Hall, either meditating, dual cultivating with Xiao Moxian, or practicing his divine runic arts.

Slowly, a dozen some days passed. In the blink of an eye, Lin Ming had stayed in Full Moon Hall for half a month.

In the early morning, a maid slammed the doors open to put down a basin of wash water. Her eyes narrowed as she looked at Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian. As she saw their lazy and fulfilled appearances in bed, her eyes flashed with contempt.

She didn’t have to be a genius to know what the two of them had been doing last night.

The young maid also acknowledged that Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian could be considered a dragon and phoenix amongst humans, a match made by the heavens. But, they had freely eaten and slept here without any meaning or intention of leaving Full Moon Hall, and they had done so for half a month. Since it was her job to manage their daily needs she naturally wasn’t feeling happy that she had to do these extra duties.

Moreover, she could see that her master didn’t care too much about this young man and woman. Thus, she had faintly regarded Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian as simple freeloaders.

“I must say… sir, miss, how long do you plan on living here?”

This young maid was quite interesting. If she managed to be chosen to enter the Imperial Palace, she naturally wasn’t ugly. Rather, with her teenage appearance, she seemed quite pure and naïve.

Lin Ming faintly smiled. He easily knew what this young maid was thinking. “What, are you in such a hurry to kick us out?”

After having her thoughts revealed, the young maid wasn’t embarrassed. She said, “This is the harem; men usually cannot enter here. Although Imperial Concubine Moon has a special status that gives her the privilege to bid you enter and leave, you cannot stay here forever. Aren’t these the common rules of a palace?”

“That makes some sense.” Lin Ming smiled and nodded, still having no intention of leaving. His actions seemed mildly antagonistic.

The young maid’s lips twitched and she unhappily threw a white towel onto the edge of the water basin, causing a large splash.

Just as she was about to stomp off in a huff, a sharp and long voice echoed through the air, “By the decree of the Empress, Imperial Concubine Moon must come out to meet her!”

This eunuch’s voice had a great penetrative power, one that reached into every inch of Full Moon Hall. As the young maid heard this, her body shook and she nearly fell to the floor.

Chapter 1578 – Summons of the Empress

The eunuch’s sharp and grating voice reverberated through all of Full Moon Hall. The young maid propped herself up against the carved wooden door. She gathered her wits, her hand held against her chest even as her complexion was left paled and stunned.

She had been shocked by that shout because she was far too young and her cultivation was far too weak. As for that eunuch’s voice, it was extremely vigorous. Although there wasn’t any true essence in his voice it was still filled with energy, making the eardrums shake.

And, another reason was that to a palace maid without any decent cultivation, the title of Empress was far too terrifying!

The Empress was the mother of the nation and the head of the harem. All palace maids, all eunuchs, all imperial concubines, everyone had to obey the summons of the Empress. Within the harem, the Empress had absolute power!

Now, a powerful chief eunuch had suddenly shouted out the decree of the Empress. This inevitably placed a great deal of pressure on a young maid!

“The summons of the Empress?”

Lin Ming rubbed his chin, some thoughts flashing through his mind. Now that the Marvel Blue Emperor was in closed door seclusion, if the Empress had issued a decree towards Imperial Concubine Moon then it was impossible that they would be chatting about old times. There was definitely some play involved concerning political and material benefits.

And according to what Lin Ming knew, Prince Marvel Shen was the son of the Empress!

Prince Marvel Shen had a prominent background. Although his talent was a great deal worse than Grandprince Marvel Snow’s, the influence and power he grasped in his hands was several times greater than Marvel Snow’s!

And Blood Moon was also known as Imperial Concubine Moon. She was the offering that Grandprince Marvel Snow had given to the Marvel Blue Emperor.

With a little bit of thinking, one could imagine just what sort of cooperative relationship they had.

Blood Moon was an imperial concubine in name only. In truth, she was actually a helper that Marvel Snow had brought in!

And the price that Marvel Snow paid was likely a promise to help Blood Moon stabilize her position in Heaven’s Net once he succeeded the position of emperor!

This was a mutually beneficial interaction, a win-win situation for the both of them. Of course, the basis of this was that Blood Moon was able to help Marvel Snow succeed the throne. Otherwise, if she failed, not only would she obtain no advantages but she might be dragged in without any ability to defend herself!

All of these thoughts raced through Lin Ming’s mind. He could feel that the Empress’ summons this time had no good intentions behind them!

The Empress would certainly support her son Marvel Shen, and as for Blood Moon, she supported Marvel Snow. Between Empress and imperial concubine, there was bound to be a fierce battle!

And at this time, Blood Moon had already exited to receive the decree.

This was a written decree with the seal of the Empress as well as the mark of the imperial jade seal; it wasn’t a verbal decree only.

Generally speaking, if the Empress wanted to summon someone she would only need to pass on a message. She normally wouldn’t need to do something as serious as sending out a written decree.

“Imperial Concubine Moon. In these past days, the Empress has been managing national affairs and now she wishes to clear out the harem. In these last months the Emperor has been unable to pay attention to the affairs of the state and in his absence, there have been many princes and imperial concubines that have been forming their own influences within the imperial palace, even gathering guests here and creating all sorts of trouble and commotion. Now, the Empress has decreed a cleansing. Imperial Concubine Moon, I hope that you do not mind if I search through Full Moon Hall!”

In front of Imperial Concubine Moon, a yellow-robed eunuch cunningly smiled. His voice was sharp and daggers were hidden in his smile. Although his face was old and covered with wrinkles his eyes were still as sharp as an eagle’s, as if he could see through people to their bones.

This was a peak Holy Lord eunuch. Those eunuchs that wore yellow robes were all leaders amongst the eunuchs. For the Empress to send a chief eunuch to pass on a decree, it could be said that she was taking this matter extremely seriously. Moreover, there was even another team of eunuch bodyguards behind him!

These eunuch bodyguards all had a Divine Lord realm cultivation. The leader amongst these eunuchs even had an early Holy Lord realm cultivation.

Even though Marvel Blue Nation was a peak Holy Land influence, it was still impossible for them to have Divine Lords everywhere. A true palace bodyguard normally had a late Divine Transformation realm cultivation. Now that a team of Divine Lords had been sent here, it was clear that they had sent their most outstanding individuals!

This uproar and threatening momentum was definitely not a good sign.

Blood Moon frowned. According to palace rules, the Empress was in charge of the harem and she truly did have the authority to issue such a decree. Moreover, the Empress was now temporarily managing national affairs so her authority was even greater.

If she were to disobey then that would be violating the decree. There would be charges pushed against her, giving the Empress a chance to punish her!

Blood Moon was in an extremely bad situation to begin with. If she stirred up more trouble then it would only be adding fuel to the fire.

She quickly said with a true essence sound transmission, “Lin Ming, you and your companion must quickly leave through the transmission array here. I will have Eunuch Liang meet you on the outside! Although I have a token that allows you to enter the palace, the Empress is currently managing affairs of the state, thus if you were to fall into her hands she would be able to call down charges on you. If that were to happen then you would be dragged into this mess!”

Blood Moon’s words were quick and succinct; everything was heard by Lin Ming.

These words left Lin Ming startled. He suddenly developed a much more favorable impression of Blood Moon.

In Blood Moon’s opinion, Lin Ming must have some amazing master standing behind him. In ordinary times, it would be impossible for her to request a favor from Lin Ming’s master.

But if Lin Ming were to fall into danger, that would be a completely different situation!

If the Empress rashly did something to Lin Ming, harming him or even killing him, then it would be possible that Lin Ming’s master would take revenge for him. The anger of an Empyrean was no trifling matter. It was possible that the entire Marvel Blue Nation would be destroyed for this reason alone!

But Blood Moon did not use this to her advantage. Instead, she bid Lin Ming escape as soon as he could. The Imperial Palace had numerous masters standing guard here. If a junior like Lin Ming was wrapped up in the palace disputes then there really was a chance he would die!

Although Blood Moon didn’t attach much importance to Lin Ming and had even placed him in a side room without seeing him for half a month, she had never intended to harm him nor did she plan to use his safety as a chip to gain more advantages for herself.

This caused Lin Ming to feel a bit more trusting of Blood Moon. Although Blood Moon came from an assassin organization she still had her own moral code, one that she wouldn’t break. This sort of person was worth knowing.

However, although Blood Moon had told Lin Ming to leave, the old eunuch that issued the decree wouldn’t stand by and let this happen. In fact, before the old eunuch even stepped into Full Moon Hall, he had already carefully probed every master inside!

Lin Ming only had a Divine Lord realm cultivation but his foundation was far more solid than an ordinary Divine Lord powerhouse’s. The position he stood at was naturally vibrant and out of the ordinary.

And besides Lin Ming, there was no other top male master in Full Moon Hall. Eunuch Liang was not in Full Moon Hall at the moment, and even if he were the old eunuch would still have recognized and ignored him. Because of this Lin Ming had become the focus of his attention!

The old eunuch didn’t wait for Imperial Concubine Moon to respond. He turned towards the side building where Lin Ming was and hurtled forwards!

Peng!

The wooden doors of the building were smashed apart!

The old eunuch rushed in like a wild bull!

“Ahh!”

The young maid that had been delivering washing water suddenly screamed. The powerful flux of energy that came with the old eunuch rushing over here suddenly surged towards the young maid!

The young maid only had a Pulse Condensation realm cultivation. If she were struck by this flow of energy then if she were lucky only all of her organs would shatter. If she wasn’t lucky then her entire body would explode to pieces and she would die a miserable death where she stood!

In the Imperial Palace, the life of a palace maid or eunuch was far too cheap. If they were struck to death they would simply be buried somewhere without even a tombstone to mark their grave.

Let alone these low level palace maids and eunuchs, even princes without status or talent were the same. After all, the Emperor had far too many descendants and the Imperial Palace had a limit to the number of people that it could hold. Those that lacked talent would be banished from the Imperial Palace, and as for whether they lived or died in the future, no one cared.

“Just what are you doing!?”

Xiao Moxian shouted out loud. Her apricot-round eyes widened and she waved her hand, her fast reflexes sending out a current of true essence that wrapped around the young maid and pulled her over!

Peng!

Where the young maid had been originally standing, all of the surrounding furniture was shattered by the terrifying currents of energy. Even the tiles began to crack apart like a spider web.

These floor tiles had been specially made. Although they weren’t constructed from something as precious as timeless god stone, they still used materials as hard as divine steel. Now that these tiles were struck by the old eunuch they almost exploded to pieces. It could only be said that this old eunuch was deliberately setting his momentum up so that he could suppress Lin Ming with lightning speed!

Without the orders of the Empress, there was no way that a mere peak Holy Lord chief eunuch would dare to be so rampant in Full Moon Hall!

For the old eunuch to rush in and then stop, this was to vividly display the Empress’ attitude towards Imperial Concubine Moon!

“Hehe, so there really are accomplices and one of them is even a man!”

The old eunuch looked at Lin Ming and then turned towards Imperial Concubine Moon, a sly and thoughtful smile stretching across his face! It was like he had caught Lin Ming and Imperial Concubine Moon in bed together!

Imperial Concubine Moon’s face darkened, a thick surge of killing intent flashing in her eyes. She never thought that this old eunuch would use such a method to accuse her of crimes. This was simply a grand humiliation to herself!

“You stupid old turtle, it seems you don’t want to live!”

Xiao Moxian was already enraged. She still had the young maid held to her chest. The young maid had been frightened pale. Just now she had walked up to death’s door. If it weren’t for Xiao Moxian pulling her back then her blood would have splashed everywhere and she likely wouldn’t even have had a complete corpse!

The young maid looked towards Xiao Moxian with gratitude and awe. She felt grateful that Xiao Moxian had rescued her, and she was awed that Xiao Moxian would call this chief eunuch an old turtle to his face!

These chief eunuchs had an extremely high status and they could execute young maids and young eunuchs as they pleased! To a low level maid like herself, these chief eunuchs were existences that they felt absolute fear towards. Moreover, this chief eunuch had a peak Holy Lord cultivation!

But Xiao Moxian had still called him a turtle. And for a eunuch, they especially hated and loathed being called a turtle!

The young maid already thought that these words were braver than the heavens. But even so, she never imagined that Xiao Moxian’s next words would be even more malicious!

Without caring for how angry this chief eunuch was, Xiao Moxian sneered and said, “How ridiculously strange. When farm beasts like donkeys and horses are wild, they become much more docile after they are castrated. It becomes much more enjoyable to ride them and they listen to orders obediently. But you, after you had your manhood severed your temperament became so much worse instead. Does this mean that you are inferior to even donkeys and horses?”

Xiao Moxian’s words were toxic to the extreme!

After the young maid heard this she nearly fell on the floor. This was the same as challenging the chief eunuch’s bottom line!

And indeed, after the chief eunuch heard Xiao Moxian’s words, thick killing intent flashed in his eyes!

Chapter 1581 – Blood Moon’s Crisis

“Protect the Empress!”

The moment that Blood Moon moved, 18 eunuchs and old maids had already been prepared. They stood atop an array formation, and the Empress and Blood Moon stood at the heart of it! Now that Blood Moon launched such a sudden attack, the runes beneath the 18 eunuchs and maids shimmered as they gathered their strength, forming a mighty raging river that rushed towards Blood Moon.

The floor tiles exploded to pieces as energy raced forwards like a tide, filled with killing intent!

Facing the onslaught of these 18 people, Blood Moon coldly sneered. “An 18 Clear King Array. Such a dignified Arid Peace Palace, as the ruler of the harem you can only display an array formation of this level?”

Arid Peace Palace’s 18 Clear King Array had to be laid down by array masters and divine runic masters. However, within the entire inner Asura Road, although array masters were somewhat easy to find, divine runic masters were not; they were exorbitantly expensive characters. If one wanted to ask one of them to help then they would have to pay a steep price. Moreover, there also had to be a certain friendship or they wouldn’t bother to begin with.

If it was the Marvel Blue Emperor then he could certainly request a peak sixth grade divine runic master to add divine runic symbols to this array formation. In fact, in Marvel Blue Imperial Palace’s Golden Imperial Throne as well as Heaven and Earth Hall, there was a peak sixth grade divine runic array. Once this array formation began, the effects would be extraordinary!

But in the harem, Arid Peace Palace was only the living quarters of a half-step World King Empress. For her, it was impossible to use such a grand array. This so-called 18 Clear King Array could barely be considered to be at the sixth grade, or in other words a quasi-sixth grade array formation.

A sixth grade divine runic array was far more expensive than a sixth grade divine runic symbol because an array formation required dozens of divine runic symbols of the same level to support it. For Arid Peace Palace to be able to lay down a quasi-sixth grade array formation was already extremely luxurious for a half-step World King Empress.

The 18 early Holy Lord eunuchs and old maids stood above 18 Clear King Array. With it, the might of their joint attack increased by dozens of times and one could fight a World King – on the premise that this 18 Clear King Array wasn’t broken!

But how could a true World King powerhouse stand there idly and let themselves be struck by these people?

In that instant, Blood Moon took out a shining gold talisman from her spatial ring. The design of a fierce ghost’s head decorated the talisman; this was a sixth grade divine runic symbol!

This divine runic symbol had been drawn up by the Divine Runic Masters Guild’s Old Su especially for Blood Moon. Old Su and Blood Moon had a very deep friendship, and the reason Lin Ming was able to come to Marvel Blue Nation was also because he had been introduced by Old Su.

Hu - !

As the divine runic symbol entered Blood Moon’s hands it began to burn brilliantly, turning into hundreds of dao patterns that rained down. These dao patterns didn’t attack the 18 eunuchs and maids, but attacked the array symbols beneath their feet!

This was a sixth grade array shattering symbol and that 18 Clear King Array was within the level of arrays that this symbol would break! As a high level member of Heaven’s Net, she would naturally gather sufficient information before she took on a mission. Before this, Lord Snow had paid a sufficient price to bribe enough eunuchs and maids into telling him that the great array formation within Arid Peace Palace was the 18 Clear King Array!

In response to this array, Blood Moon had asked for Old Su’s help to draw up a specific array shattering symbol. Now, the time had come to use it!

Ca!

A tooth-aching sound echoed out accompanied by a flash of golden light, blinding everyone in the hall. In that moment, the runes beneath the 18 eunuchs and maids shattered, turning into violent flows of energy that caused a backlash against them. Their bodies shook and they were nearly injured!

This was the moment Blood Moon had been waiting for. Her body turned into a beam of light that shot forwards. Powerful true essence poured into her sword.

As her sword slashed out, a round and bright moon rose behind Blood Moon. The cold moonlight sprinkled down, covering the entire Arid Peace Palace. As for Blood Moon, she was illuminated by this moon in the background. Her slender body stretched out like she was a goddess riding the wind, filled with infinite charm and grace!

However, this charm and grace was actually fatal!

Just what sort of strength did Blood Moon possess? Although she was wounded she was still a World King powerhouse, someone that a Holy Lord could not contend with!

With a flash of moonlight, a cold and chilling night seemed to descend. Beneath the cover of this endless night, everyone felt inexplicably oppressed. The bright moon in the skies attracted the eyes of everyone!

“This is bad!”

Empress Naye’s complexion changed. True essence erupted from her body as she rapidly retreated. She was well aware that in that moment she had been covered by Blood Moon’s domain!

This long night and bright moonlight, that was Blood Moon’s domain – The Endlessly Long Night!

As Naye drew back, two eunuchs and a maid bore the brunt of Blood Moon’s attack. Blood Moon’s attack struck them, decapitating them and sending their heads rolling to the floor!

Like this, the 18 Clear King Array was broken by Blood Moon!

As blood splashed out, the moonlight seemed to be dyed red. The bright moon in the skies began to take on a faintly reddish hue!

This was the sign of Blood Moon. Within her domain, every time she killed a person the moon would drink their blood, becoming increasingly red. Once she killed innumerable people, this bright moon would turn into a dark red blood moon. And at that time, the power of the Endlessly Long Night would reach its peak!

After the success of her first strike, Blood Moon didn’t stop there. Her sword changed direction as she cut towards another group of eunuchs and maids!

She wanted to quickly kill off these early Holy Lord powerhouses and use their blood to water the Endlessly Long Night!

Blood Moon was originally a high level member of an assassin organization. Even within Arid Peace Palace, she killed without mercy! She was well aware that in this situation, it was no longer a question of whether she was rebelling or not. Ever since ancient times, when the changing of a dynasty was coming, coups and rivers of blood were common, whether it was in the mortal world or the world of martial artists!

As long as one won, then one could still be king no matter how many people they killed. But if one lost, that would be a capital crime of rebelling against the nation!

The winner was king and the losers were villains; this was the simplest truth.

At this time, the Empress was taking advantage of the fact that the Emperor was in closed door seclusion to show her hand. With force, she wanted to subdue all others. How could Blood Moon sit around and wait for death?

But as Blood Moon attacked for a second time and was about to decapitate another eunuch, an alarm sounded out in her heart!

A killing intent was hidden within the atmosphere of chaos, like a viper hiding in the brush!

“Sneak attack!?”

Blood Moon was startled. At this time, there was actually a hidden ambusher that appeared from nowhere! Such hiding methods and assassination techniques left a strong sense of restlessness in her heart!

She no longer had time to think about who it could be; she rapidly drew backwards!

Chi!

With a light sound, the Endlessly Long Night domain was pierced through by a strange force. This power was incomparably ruthless and sinister, shooting straight towards Blood Moon!

“Be careful behind you!”

A voice suddenly rang out. This was Lin Ming’s warning!

Without thinking, Blood Moon slashed out behind her. With a loud cracking sound, she chopped apart a black flashing dagger!

Because the Endlessly Long Night domain had been broken, an immense amount of sharp and violent sword energy gushed out! Three coiling dragon pillars supported by array formations were sliced to pieces by this sword energy. The entire structure shook, nearly collapsing in on itself!

A battle between quasi World Kings could move mountains, fill seas, and even destroy some smaller planets. With this violent battle occurring deep in the palace, no matter how solid the building was, once it lost the protection of a domain then it simply wouldn’t be able to block the true essence currents rushing about!

“White Sky, is that you!?”

Blood Moon’s voice was cold, her complexion gloomy and dark like the bottom of a lake. Although that sneak attack hadn’t injured her, it had planted a parasitic domain seed within her domain.

This parasitic seed wasn’t able to harm her. With just a little bit of effort she would be able to remove the seed, but this process required some time. In the meantime, this seed would erode her true essence, making it so that she couldn’t activate her domain ability.

And at this time, a tall man in gray robes stepped out from behind a folding screen within Arid Peace Palace. This thin screen shouldn’t have been able to isolate the sense of a martial artist. If Blood Moon wasn’t able to discover this from the start, then this proved that this other person had an amazing concealing technique.

And the people that usually possessed this type of ability were assassins!

“Blood Moon, it’s been a while since we’ve seen each other!” A man hoarsely said, immediately calling out Blood Moon’s codename within Heaven’s Net. He wore a white and black mask with two fierce blood red lines running down from the eyes, looking fierce.

He clearly knew who Blood Moon was.

“Someone from Heaven’s Net?”

Lin Ming’s eyes narrowed as he immediately realized this.

Chapter 1582 – Assassin White Sky

As Blood Moon saw the masked man appear, her complexion turned grim. He was the same as Blood Moon in that both of them covered up their cultivations with secret techniques, making it so that one couldn’t see what level his cultivation boundary was at. In addition, his black and white mask was able to isolate out all senses so that no one could uncover anything about him at all.

This was a frequently used tactic of Heaven’s Net.

“Who is that?” Lin Ming asked with a true essence sound transmission.

“One of the three leaders of Heaven’s Net, White Sky, a World King powerhouse!”

Blood Moon replied, her eyes fixed on White Sky.

“World King…”

Lin Ming’s eyebrows shot up. He wasn’t surprised by White Sky’s cultivation boundary at all. Heaven’s Net was similar to the Marvel Blue Nation; both could be considered peak World King Holy Lands. And, the big boss of Heaven’s Net was likely a Great World King whereas the other leaders were ordinary World Kings.

Blood Moon herself was in truth at the early World King boundary. Amongst World King powerhouses, she was on the weaker end of the spectrum. The White Sky in front of her was similar to her.

But at this time, Blood Moon’s situation wasn’t good to begin with. White Sky’s appearance had suddenly brought about a massive crisis!

Facing White Sky, Blood Moon sneered and said, “I never thought you would chase me all the way here. In order to hunt me down you’ve involved yourself in the struggle for the Marvel Blue Nation’s throne?”

Empress Naye suddenly laughed out loud, “Imperial Concubine Moon… or, perhaps it’s better if I call you Blood Moon! Did you think that only Lord Snow would be able to invite people from Heaven’s Net, but I could not? The ones I bring are even stronger than you!”

As Naye spoke, she sat back upon her empress throne. Her expression turned idle and bored once again, as if everything was in her control.

At the start she hadn’t known what Blood Moon’s true identity was; it was Heaven’s Net that had approached her on their own initiative. They wanted to join in on the struggle for the throne, and their goal in all of this was Blood Moon.

This was a naturally happy occurrence for both sides. Thus, all of that led to Empress Naye summoning Blood Moon today.

She had already made all of her preparations in order to place Blood Moon in a death trap.

White Sky looked at Blood Moon from beneath the eye holes in his mask. His voice was indifferent as he said, “Blood Moon, if you thought you could find protection in the Marvel Blue Imperial Palace, then you were wrong to indulge in such whimsical fancies. If you can involve yourself in the struggle for the throne, then so can we! I know that you’re aware of what I’ve come here for. Is the item that Big Boss left behind in your hands? As long as you hand it over, I will not kill you! You and I are from the same organization so I naturally have some sentiment towards my fellow comrades. I don’t even care about the matters of authority in Heaven’s Net because none of it concerns me at all. If you want to leave and take someone with you then I won’t stop you.”

White Sky didn’t conceal his goal at all, nor did he care about the presence of the Empress or the others. His voice was harsh, bringing with it a faint killing intent that was forceful and aggressive.

As Lin Ming heard this, his thoughts stirred. Something that the Big Boss had left behind?

He originally found it strange that there would be an internal power struggle within Heaven’s Net. Lin Ming thought it was because they were competing for authority, but now it seemed that the original cause was some sort of treasure!

If this was a treasure that could cause a bloodbath among the high level figures of Heaven’s Net, then this must be something extraordinary!

“What you want is not in my hands!”

Blood Moon had no intention of bargaining for her life. She pointed her sword straight at White Sky’s throat.

Seeing this, White Sky chuckled, his laugh grating to the ears. “I thought you would give such a response, otherwise it wouldn’t be you at all. But, look around you, do you still think you can win in this situation?”

As the gray-robed man spoke, he took out a short sword from his spatial ring. This sword was two feet long without a hand guard. Moreover, the hilt was extremely short, just two inches long, making it difficult for an adult male to hold.

The short sword was deep blue and the blade as thin as paper. Without a doubt, this short sword could display one’s speed to the limit!

“Blood Moon, it seems that you are going to die here today. What a pity that your arrogance and pride have doomed you, it is truly regretful. In the past, Big Boss also greatly appreciated you.”

White Sky’s voice was cold and indifferent. His white and black mask was blank and without expression, but those two lines that ran down from the base of his eyes seemed even fiercer than they were before.

“Leave Blood Moon for me to deal with! You can all manage the rest of these underlings!”

White Sky’s focus had already locked onto Blood Moon. As for Empress Naye, she quietly sat back on her throne and gently waved her hand. Eunuch Sun understood this order, and led the remaining 15 old maids and eunuchs to surround Lin Ming, Xiao Moxian, and Eunuch Liang.

Even the young eunuchs and young maids that followed Blood Moon were surrounded.

The young maid that brought washing water to Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian was already pale with fear. She had guessed that there would be nothing good coming from the Empress’ summons, but she never thought that matters would develop to this stage. The two sides were actually going to fight in Arid Peace Palace, with life and death on the line!

These young maids were well aware that if Blood Moon was defeated, they would be buried along with her. To the Empress, killing them was no different from slaughtering chickens or dogs!

And in the current situation, it seemed impossible for Blood Moon to win. Even if she could escape by herself, the young maids and eunuchs she left behind would be brutally beaten to death!

“Haha! Eunuch Liang, I never thought there would be such a day between you and me… a smart bird knows which tree to nest in. If you regret your decision, there is still time for you. I can plead sympathy for you to the Empress and perhaps the Empress will allow you to keep your cheap life.”

Eunuch Sun flicked his yellow eunuch robes, the smile of a victor on his face. As he looked at Eunuch Liang, his eyes were the same as if he were looking at a pitiful worm.

Facing such an arrogant Eunuch Sun, Eunuch Liang’s face darkened. There was no hope that he would obtain any form of safety if he voluntarily surrendered.

Currently, he was figuring out just what his chances were that he could safely escape from Arid Peace Palace.

“As well as you…” Eunuch Sun turned towards Lin Ming. “Your talent isn’t too bad. If you are willing to testify against Imperial Concubine Moon and confess to all those shameful activities that occurred between you and her, then the Empress will pardon you of your capital crimes. Perhaps you will even receive her favor and be accepted into the palace as a eunuch. You will have the chance to practice the Sunflower Melody that so many people long for in their dreams.”

Eunuch Sun said, a thoughtful and playful look on his face. Indeed, if the Empress were to get rid of Imperial Concubine Moon today, she would still need a justified reason to do so as well as evidence in order to stop the criticism of others. And, Lin Ming would make the perfect evidence as a witness.

“You want me to testify against Imperial Concubine Moon and practice the Sunflower Melody?” Lin Ming laughed, his laugh filled with reckless mirth.

Eunuch Sun frowned. “What are you laughing about?”

“He’s laughing at how stupid you are.” Xiao Moxian suddenly said, her voice clear and loud, attracting the eyes of everyone present. “A dumb old turtle like you has slaved their life away as a minion and yet you can still feel superior to anyone? Look at the disgusting thing you’ve become. You don’t seem like a ghost or a person. Is it possible that you think everyone in this world wants to be like you?”

As Xiao Moxian spoke, she smiled with glee as if she didn’t care at all for the tense atmosphere around her.

And, her actions naturally enraged Eunuch Sun!

He had already been mocked by Xiao Moxian and had been called inferior to castrated horses and donkeys. Now he was being mocked yet again!

“You little whore, you seem to have forgotten what I’ve said. In the palace, we have the greatest forms of torture. Do you know what a wooden horse is? First we will cripple your cultivation and turn you back into a mortal. Then, we will strip you of all your clothing and make you ride the wooden horse down the streets. And, this wooden horse has all sorts of trap devices. Once you’ve understood their exquisite pain, you’ll know what it means to wish for death, hahaha…”

Eunuch Sun queerly cackled. A wooden horse was the most brutal form of punishment that a mortal palace could pass down to a woman. There was a wooden pillar on the wooden horse, and this pillar would expand up and down, ruthlessly destroying a woman’s body from the inside. Many times, the person riding the wooden horse would be tortured to death. It was an extremely cruel and barbaric form of punishment.

And in the world of martial artists, the wooden horse was formed by thorn hardwood that was tens of thousands of years old. This wood was as hard as divine iron, and with the female martial artist having their cultivation wasted away, they would equally die a miserable death from suffering.

As Eunuch Sun said such sinister and malicious words, Lin Ming’s complexion turned icy cold. His eyes burst out with blazing killing intent.

Eunuch Sun cackled once more. He simply didn’t place an early Divine Lord junior’s killing intent in his eyes. To him, this was the same as a praying mantis waving its scythes at a wild tiger.

Just as Eunuch Sun was about to spit out some more perverse words at Lin Ming to cause him to shake in fear, Lin Ming spat out two words – “Go die.”

In that moment, Eunuch Sun only saw Lin Ming’s right hand shoot out, followed by a chilling spear light!

At the same time, a primal and boundless aura covered everyone present. This aura was incomparably heavy, as if a giant mountain was pressing down on them from the sky, making them able to display less than 30% of their strength!

As Eunuch Sun was crushed by this mountain-like weight, he found that even breathing became difficult!

And at this time, Lin Ming moved!

Lin Ming’s velocity reached unimaginable heights. In just a thousandth of the blink of an eye, he arrived right in from of Eunuch Sun, the Phoenix Blood Spear in his hands piercing forwards!

What!?

Eunuch Sun was panic-stricken. He never thought that Lin Ming would possess such a terrifying force field that could completely bind his movements!

He desperately resisted this pressure, wanting to block Lin Ming’s strike. At the same time, he opened his mouth to spit out gray flames. He wanted to use these gray flames to force Lin Ming backwards and half his attack.

However, Lin Ming was far too strong. And under the suppression of the grandmist force field, killing Eunuch Sun was as simple as turning his hand!

With a loud cracking sound, the gray flames that Eunuch Sun spat out weren’t even able to stop Lin Ming for a split-second before they were scattered by the Phoenix Blood Spear!

The long spear continued forwards with overwhelming momentum. The cold spear point thrust straight towards Eunuch Sun’s throat!

And at this time, Eunuch Sun’s mouth was still open from spitting out flames. As he saw this spear point nearly stab into his mouth, he was almost frightened to death!

He quickly traced his spatial ring, wanting to take out the divine runic symbol that he saved as his life-saving card. However, Lin Ming’s spear was too fast. Underneath the savage attack of this spear, Eunuch Sun’s protective true essence was pierced through like paper.

The Phoenix Blood Spear stabbed into Eunuch Sun’s mouth, twisting apart his teeth and tongue, penetrating through his throat and exiting through the back of his head, carrying with it a rain of blood!

And at this time, Eunuch Sun no longer had the ability to use the ancient divine runic symbol that he had pulled out. With his throat pierced, the agonizing pain made him want to cry out but he couldn’t make a single sound at all!

This sort of pain was indescribable!

As for Lin Ming, he raised his right hand and strung up Eunuch Sun through his throat with his spear, lifting his entire body up!

Chapter 1585 – Fighting White Sky

Raging flames surged about and waves of heat howled through the air. A sun seemed to ignite within Xiao Moxian’s body.

In that moment, from behind Xiao Moxian, a massive black phoenix phantom soared into the air. This phoenix phantom was also wrapped in flames and the moment it appeared, the vault of Arid Peace Palace began to be scorched away. The carvings and paintings that decorated the palace began to melt into the walls.

White Sky never imagined that this sort of change would occur just as he was about to capture Xiao Moxian. This young girl with her low cultivation was actually able to burst out with such a terrifying strength!

“Counterforce – Heaven Absorbing Demon Art!”

Xiao Moxian drew her whip and slashed it outwards. This whip burned with flames. At the same time, the dark power within the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art erupted out, swallowing the void and locking White Sky in a thick and viscous darkness!

“Concept of Darkness sixth level! Concept of Fire seventh level!”

White Sky sucked in a cold breath. This common-looking young woman had actually achieved such horrifying attainments in the Fire and Darkness Laws!

White Sky’s short sword thrust out. In this moment White Sky didn’t hold back at all and attacked with everything he had. Facing Xiao Moxian, who was burning her phoenix blood essence, he had no choice but to be cautious of her.

Ca!

The sword light cut through the whip shadows. Flames filled the skies, howling and raging. Xiao Moxian took a step back as she lashed out with her whip once more!

But her whip wasn’t aimed at White Sky. Rather, the whip shadows spread all over White Sky, forming an enchantment barrier around him!

This enchantment didn’t have any striking power but it actually locked White Sky within it, making it difficult for him to use that strange and ghostly movement technique.

“Mm!?”

White Sky was shocked. Xiao Moxian had set up an enchantment around him!

An ominous feeling appeared in his heart. At this time, he could feel a profound killing intent growing behind him, savage and turbulent!

He turned around to see that Lin Ming had grasped his Phoenix Blood Spear. Lin Ming’s hair fluttered in the wind as he rushed forwards like a demon god!

Facing White Sky, Lin Ming was filled with killing intent. Originally, Lin Ming had the mentality that he wouldn’t fight with this person unless he had to. After all, this White Sky was a World King powerhouse and fighting with him at this time wasn’t the wisest course of action. But, he never thought that White Sky would actually attack Xiao Moxian. This action had irreversibly touched upon Lin Ming’s reverse scale, the source of rage!

Lin Ming hadn’t held back in this strike. The Heretical God Force completely exploded within him and inside his inner world, the Purple Temple Dao Palace began to open!

In that moment, the world seemed to fall away. Arid Peace Palace vanished as everyone seemed to suddenly appear in the boundless starry skies of the endless universe!

Everyone stood in this void, surrounded by infinite space. And above the heads of these people, nine stars began to appear!

Of these nine stars, seven were bright and two were dark. Their locations seemed to faintly hint at the highest truths of the Great Dao. Endless starlight fell down as trillions of silver threads fell onto Lin Ming.

A terrifying killing intent surged out in all directions. With Lin Ming’s inner world as the center, this starlight crazily gathered into him, forming a terrifying river of stars that swirled around him. The space around everyone seemed to be locked down, completely disconnected from the outside world.

In this instant, everyone in Arid Peace Palace was left stunned!

“This is…”

Blood Moon looked at the nine stars in the skies, her eyes filled with utter disbelief. She had also once tried to dual cultivate body and energy so she was well aware what these nine stars meant!

“Nine Stars of the Dao Palace… this is the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace!”

Blood Moon felt as if everything she knew had been turned upside-down!

The Nine Stars of the Dao Palace was a legendary realm that was forbidden by the Heavenly Dao rules. Lin Ming was less than 60 years old so when he had asked Blood Moon to borrow the Celestial Tyrant Manual, she had urged him to forget about the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace because it was simply far too unrealistic.

Lin Ming had lived in Full Moon Hall for over half a month but in the end, Blood Moon hadn’t lent the Celestial Tyrant Manual to him. One reason was because she didn’t think that Lin Ming would be able to help her, and another reason was that even if she were to lend it to him, there would simply be no meaning to it. He wouldn’t be able to cultivate it and would just be wasting his time.

But she never would have imagined that the truth was that Lin Ming had already stepped into the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace!

The reason he had asked her to borrow the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace section of the Celestial Tyrant Manual was because he had already cultivated it!

“How is this… possible…”

Blood Moon could no longer understand Lin Ming. This was not a question of talent anymore. She couldn’t think of just what lucky chance existed that could allow him to break into the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace.

Many of the martial artists present were talented but they hadn’t chosen to walk the path of dual body and energy cultivation. And, the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace had already disappeared for billions of years, so even though they saw these stars appear behind Lin Ming they still didn’t know just what they were.

They could only feel that this was a dreadful phenomenon. As those nine stars appeared in the skies, all of the human martial artists present felt their blood vitality gravitating towards those nine stars, as if all the blood running within their bodies wanted to howl out of them!

Then, Lin Ming attacked!

The Nine Stars of the Dao Palace was currently Lin Ming’s greatest strength. The boundary he had reached had already surpassed the early Divine Lord realm of the essence gathering system!

Explosive crackling sounds lit up from within Lin Ming’s body. The galactic storm within his inner world erupted and his bodily strength reached 15 billion jins. When combined with the techniques of the Celestial Tyrant Manual, Lin Ming’s striking power rose to the strength of five dragons!

Bang!

A horrifying air wave burst outwards. Even the dual imprisonment of Xiao Moxian’s enchantment and the grandmist space wasn’t able to cage this terrifying strength. The entirety of Arid Peace Palace was torn apart by the explosions of energy, completely collapsing!

“Asura Heavenly Dao – Demon Extermination!”

Lin Ming once again used a move from the Asura Sutra. He was only just able to use this technique when he gathered the power of the nine stars unto himself. He had once used this Demon Extermination technique to kill Tian Mingzi!

Out of all of Lin Ming’s attacks, it could be called his strongest one!

As Lin Ming thrust out his spear, space itself was crushed!

Facing this attack, White Sky’s complexion changed.

Although he didn’t recognize the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace he could still feel the wild and tyrannical power erupting from within Lin Ming. With this strength used by the present Lin Ming, he resembled an ancient great dragon!

How could one’s strength reach such a terrifying degree!?

In that moment, White Sky’s body ballooned outwards. All of the strength contained within his inner world burst out!

White Sky held his sword, his feet dancing on seven stars. His body emitted a creamy white light, a light that contained a primal flavor beyond description.

Of the nine tribulation Laws of metal, wood, water, fire, earth, wind, thunder, yin, and yang, this was the Yang Laws!

The Yang Laws stood above the five elements. When the universe formed, first came chaos, then came yin and yang!

Yin and yang came after chaos and grandmist; it was one of the most extreme source Laws! It was only an extremely rare breed of person who thoroughly mastered the Yang Laws.

In the past, White Sky had stumbled upon a great lucky chance and had obtained an ancient inheritance concerning the Yang Laws. By coincidence, his physique also happened to be suited to practicing the Yang Laws. This was the main reason he was able to struggle through the plot-filled assassination organization of Heaven’s Net and slowly crawl his way to becoming a World King and assassin leader!

At White Sky slashed out his short sword, all of the surrounding light was swallowed up by this luminescent white divine light, as if the heavens and earth were isolated outwards.

The eunuchs and maids of Arid Peace Palace were suppressed by this dreadful divine light and found it difficult to breathe. Their blood vitality restlessly surged within their bodies, on the verge of exploding out from them!

Peng!

With a loud crack, two eunuchs of Arid Peace Palace blew up into pieces. But as their bodies exploded there was no blood that splashed out. Rather, their bodies evaporated beneath this white divine light, dissipating into nothingness!

This caused all of the eunuchs and maids with lower cultivations to shiver. As long as this divine light shined upon them then their bodies would disintegrate; how could they not be terrified of such a scene!

“Retreat!”

Xiao Moxian suddenly called out. Xiao Moxian was the closest one to Lin Ming and White Sky’s battle but she didn’t fear the shock waves of their attacks. Rather, it was the young maids and eunuchs of Full Moon Hall that could not withstand this pressure.

The long whip in her hand slashed out, wrapping around four or five frightened eunuchs and maids. Then, she drew backwards, preventing them from being covered by the divine light.

White Sky’s Yang Laws were similar to a force field. This force field wildly clashed with Lin Ming’s grandmist space!

Chi chi chi!

As the white light entered the grandmist space, it rapidly dissipated like snow falling into molten iron. As the two force fields collided, the difference could be seen with a glance.

The Yin Yang Laws originally came after the Grandmist Laws. Moreover, Lin Ming’s grandmist space was established by Empyrean Primordius and there was true grandmist energy supporting it!

The power of this grandmist space had long reached unimaginable levels!

As White Sky watched his own force field be swallowed up by the grandmist space, his complexion changed. White Sky was also a ruthless and decisive individual. In this grave and imminent danger, he forced out a mouthful of blood essence. This blood essence brilliantly burned, its strength used by White Sky to fiercely raise the power of his Yang Laws.

For a time, White Sky’s sword light became increasingly ancient, as if it were a blade that shuttled through the endless years to slash forth from the nothingness of the most primitive times.

This was the atmosphere of the absolute beginning!

Beneath the superimposed power of two force fields, Lin Ming’s spear light collided with White Sky’s sword light.

Bang!

In that strike, the sun and moon lost their luster and the world lost all light!

A horrifying surge of energy exploded from the center of the grandmist space and yang force field! If it weren’t for the barrier of these dual force fields then this strike would have swept up the entire imperial palace in a storm. Within this storm, all other buildings besides those protected by the strongest array formations would have turned to ash!

Puff!

White Sky spat out a mouthful of fresh blood and was sent flying backwards. As for Lin Ming, his body shook and his blood tumbled within him.

In that exchange just now when Lin Ming had erupted with all his strength, White Sky had managed to use the Yang Laws to screen out most of Lin Ming’s strength and then block Lin Ming’s spear light with his own sword light.

“Genesis energy! In his Yang Laws, he had already evolved elementary genesis energy! Although it is only a tiny bit, it is still dreadful. Indeed, it seems there isn’t a single World King powerhouse that is simple at all!”

Lin Ming thought to himself, stunned. In this world, there were three great source powers – grandmist energy, genesis energy, and spirit source!

Genesis energy was able to stand on the same level as grandmist energy!

Chapter 1586 – Imperial Palace’s Great Chief Eunuch

Of the three major source powers, none of them were a trifling matter.

Grandmist energy – the source of matter.

Genesis energy – the source of energy.

Spirit source – the source of soul.

When these three source powers were unified, they formed essence, energy, and divine!

In the past, it was because Lin Ming lacked spirit source that Divine Dream didn’t allow Lin Ming to study the Divine Dream Law.

Each one of the three major source powers was incomparably precious. The reason that Lin Ming was able to possess so much grandmist energy was because he inherited it from Empyrean Primordius. By himself, it would have been impossible to obtain it. This was because grandmist energy had almost completely disappeared after the forming of the universe. It was said that grandmist energy still existed in black holes, but black holes were celestial bodies where the gravitational force reached such an extreme that it created a force field around itself, an absolutely separate space. Even an Empyrean couldn’t enter one!

Empyrean Divine Seal’s Divine Seal Art was founded with inspiration from black holes.

It was incredible that this White Sky was able to cultivate a tiny amount of elementary genesis energy in his attacks. It was clear that he had once obtained a powerful inheritance, and although this inheritance was inferior to the Primordius martial intent, it should still have been on the level of a transcendent divine might.

At this time, Arid Peace Palace, which was supported with all sorts of array formations and was comparable to a spirit artifact, was completely razed to the ground. Empress Naye had been injured in the chaos. Her entire body was drenched in blood and she looked miserable.

In the center of the battlefield, the only ones left were Lin Ming and White Sky, standing in harsh opposition with each other!

In that strike just now, White Sky had been forced to burn some of his blood essence and had even suffered a loss. As for Lin Ming, he had only been forced back with his blood tumbling within him; the difference could be easily seen.

Everyone who stood on the Empress’ side was currently looking at Lin Ming with fear and dread in their eyes. Even White Sky wasn’t Lin Ming’s match!

A World King powerhouse had been suppressed by Lin Ming!

At this time, the maids and eunuchs of Arid Peace Palace who luckily survived were all trembling with fear. The pressure that Lin Ming placed upon them was too great. With the aura of the grandmist force field also covering them, they couldn’t even stand steady.

And at this time, the one with the most tumultuous mood was Blood Moon.

It was already shocking when Lin Ming displayed the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, but afterwards when Lin Ming used that terrifying 15 billion jins of strength, he actually used an arcane technique to increase his strength to 50 billion jins: the strength of five dragons!

When Blood Moon saw this technique Lin Ming used, she felt it was strangely familiar.

“Celestial Tyrant Manual? This is the Celestial Tyrant Manual? This Lin Ming actually understands the Celestial Tyrant Manual?” All sorts of chaotic emotions swelled in Blood Moon’s heart. She thought that the Celestial Tyrant Manual was a unique cultivation method manual and yet Lin Ming also knew of it?

“No wonder… no wonder he would request the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace section of the Celestial Tyrant Manual from me… it is because he already practiced the Eight Inner Hidden Gates section to the peak and has even opened the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace!”

Blood Moon mumbled to herself. She felt that this youth in front of her was filled with riddles.

White Sky’s complexion was grim. In that collision of force fields just now when White Sky’s yang force field had smashed into Lin Ming’s grandmist space, the disparity had been evident.

This sort of disparity manifested in the grade of the force fields!

The yang force field was originally not as exquisite as the grandmist space. Moreover, there was a massive amount of grandmist energy that flooded the grandmist space; this was true grandmist energy, not elementary grandmist energy!

And within the yang force field, there was only elementary genesis energy.

This sort of difference couldn’t even be described with clouds and mud. The only reason that White Sky had suffered a small loss was because his cultivation was far deeper than Lin Ming’s. With the difference in their cultivation boundaries he had forcefully made up for their force fields to block Lin Ming’s Demon Extermination.

“Divine Lord realm… you really are at the Divine Lord realm?”

As White Sky looked at Lin Ming, there was a strange trembling in his voice!

In that exchange just now, he had been able to confirm what Lin Ming’s boundary was!

The true essence standard that Lin Ming displayed, although it far surpassed all other early Divine Lord martial artists, could still be explained with the reasoning that he was an unrivalled genius. Even so, it was explainable. In other words, Lin Ming didn’t truly surpass the Divine Lord realm!

At first he had thought that Lin Ming was a World King powerhouse that had concealed himself, but no matter how profound a World King powerhouse was at camouflaging their cultivation, it would be impossible for them to maintain a Divine Lord realm cultivation in the heat of battle. Otherwise, they would be brutally beaten by others.

“You… just who are you?”

White Sky said with raging emotions. He found it hard to keep his expression or tone calm. Ever since he joined Heaven’s Net as a child, he had grown one step at a time until he became a leader. He had experienced the sandy plains of slaughter numerous times and had walked upon the thread of life or death almost daily. Even so, this was an expression that he rarely showed. He had long since formed a mindset where he could face death without panicking, but now that he faced such a terrifying character like Lin Ming he was actually left flustered.

Nothing about Lin Ming could be explained with common sense!

Lin Ming didn’t bother replying to White Sky. He slowly stepped forwards, closing the distance between them, his focus locked onto his enemy the entire time. When his focus was combined with that star-heavy grandmist energy, it seemed menacing and forceful!

White Sky’s complexion changed. He couldn’t help but take a step backwards. “Do you really want to bet life or death with me?”

“Isn’t that what you just did?” Lin Ming coldly sneered.

“I was trying to capture your dual cultivation dao companion but I wasn’t planning to do anything to her. I only wanted to use her to threaten you to retreat and stay out of the internal struggles of my Heaven’s Net. I didn’t attack you nor did I have the thought of killing your dao companion!” White Sky explained his motives. But, in doing so, he had already admitted defeat.

However, Lin Ming disregarded this explanation. “And yet your actions have enraged me even more.”

“Even if you try as hard as you can, you still won’t be able to keep me here!” White Sky’s eyebrows shot up. He had absolute confidence in his own movement techniques.

“Yes, but perhaps I might try to leave some mark on you.”

“Why must you be so forceful?” White Sky said, frowning. He still hadn’t unraveled who Lin Ming was and he didn’t want to offend someone he knew absolutely nothing about.

He had already thought of escaping.

But at this time, the grandmist force field that shrouded Arid Peace Palace strengthened by several points, as if it wanted to completely lock down this space!

Although White Sky’s movement techniques were skillful he was still temporarily stuck in this grandmist space!

If White Sky were to attack he could definitely break open the grandmist space. But at this time, Lin Ming would definitely take the chance to attack him. White Sky would be hard pressed to split his attention and would likely be severely wounded by Lin Ming.

Then, it would really be as Lin Ming said; there would be a mark left behind on his body!

Thinking of this, White Sky’s voice became dreary. “Do you think that I’ve already shown my hand and I don’t have a final all-out attack?”

As an assassin leader of Heaven’s Net who had risked his life over tens of thousands of years in Heaven’s Net, survived and even come out on top, it wasn’t a surprise that he had some final trump card in his hand.

And as Lin Ming faced White Sky’s threat, he remained silent as before, still not removing the grandmist force field!

“Good! You’re ruthless enough!” White Sky’s voice carried with it an icy chill.

For two masters to fight to such a degree had already exceeded everyone’s expectations. Lin Ming had hidden himself in this crowd of masters and had crippled Eunuch Sun with a single strike, destroyed Empress Naye’s divine runic symbol jade slips, and then suppressed World King White Sky; his strength was unbelievable!

Not only was Lin Ming abnormal but his dual cultivation companion wasn’t easy to deal with either. Although she seemed like a charming and delicate young girl, she was actually able to erupt with a horrifying combat strength. Even White Sky had been forced to avoid her attack.

These two people gave off a feeling as if they didn’t belong to this world. They were strong to the point of disbelief.

And as White Sky was about to use his desperate trump card to engage in a bloody final battle with Lin Ming, an old voice echoed outwards –

“Why must you fight to this degree…”

As this voice sounded out, the killing intent that pervaded the air suddenly diminished.

Everyone turned around to see an old yellow-robed man calmly stepping towards them, walking on the wind!

This yellow-robed old man had a face covered with wrinkles and a head of white hair.

His voice was old with a strange sharpness to it, making him sound bizarre. He wore yellow robes in the style of a eunuch, with the difference that there was a golden dragon embroidered on his front and back.

In the imperial palace, a dragon was the symbol of royal authority. Only the emperor and crown prince had the qualifications to wear imperial robes, and the crown prince’s imperial robes had a dragon with one less claw, a four-clawed golden dragon.

This old eunuch wore yellow robes with the image of a four-clawed golden dragon. In other words, he had status equal to that of a crown prince! But, the truth was that the Marvel Blue Nation had no crown prince. In other words, within the Marvel Blue Nation, this eunuch had status second only to the Marvel Blue Emperor!

That meant his status was extraordinary!

He was one of the three World King masters that commanded the Marvel Blue Nation below the Marvel Blue Emperor; he was the great chief eunuch of the imperial palace, Eunuch Wei!

Chapter 1587 – To Admit Defeat

“Greetings, Empress.”

Eunuch Wei slightly bowed as he set down on the floor.

His words were peaceful with a hint of true essence poured into them. This true essence rushed into Empress Naye’s body like a cool wind, making the pain wracking her body feel much better.

Within the Marvel Blue Nation, besides the Marvel Blue Emperor, there were three other World Kings. The Grand Marshal was in charge of the military, the Imperial Scholar was in charge of political affairs, and Great Chief Eunuch Wei was in charge of internal affairs and national resources. This included managing blue snow gold, the various heavenly materials, assigning resources, expenses of the imperial palace, and even the daily matters of tens of thousands of maids and eunuchs in the imperial palace. All of this was within Eunuch Wei’s hands. He could be said to have tremendous power and influence.

Although this type of character had to greet the Empress based upon court etiquette, the truth was that within the Marvel Blue Nation, his status was faintly above that of the Empress.

This was the world of martial artists in which strength ruled supreme. In the world of martial artists, even if one founded an imperial power as their center, it would still be different from a mortal’s imperial palace. Those without strength, whether it was a prince or imperial concubine, none of them would be able to stand out.

Lin Ming was vigilant against this Eunuch Wei who just appeared. This person’s aura was deep and his true essence was restrained; it was hard to judge what the limit of his strength was.

Although he was an ordinary World King, there were still those that were strong and weak within the World King realm. Lin Ming could feel that this Eunuch Wei was even stronger than White Sky.

Thus, he had no choice but to be cautious of him.

After all, Eunuch Wei was likely not on their side.

After Naye restored a bit of her strength, she stood back up. With a wave of her hand, the bloodstains that covered her evaporated. Even Eunuch Sun’s shredded meat was burnt into ash.

Her robes of blue snow gold and sky work silk had originally been a treasure, and now that the blood had evaporated and the ash fell away, they immediately became bright and clean again. Unfortunately, the robe itself had been torn by Lin Ming, causing Naye’s grandeur to be reduced by a great deal.

“Eunuch Wei… you have come. I am happy to see you here.”

Naye smiled. She didn’t do as Lin Ming thought she would and accuse Lin Ming, Blood Moon, and the others of conspiring to rebel against her to Eunuch Wei. Rather, she only said that she was happy to see him, completely ignoring the fact that Arid Peace Palace had been razed to the ground and she herself had been severely beaten up.

With this, Lin Ming couldn’t help but measure the Empress a few points higher.

Eunuch Wei had already managed affairs within the imperial palace for hundreds of thousands of years and naturally understood what was happening. As for the disputes of the throne, he didn’t take a side nor did he divide between right or wrong. Whoever was stronger would be able to take the throne. To the victor went the spoils; this was the only truth.

When the old Emperor went into seclusion, he had told Eunuch Wei not to interfere in the affairs of the imperial struggle. But now that Arid Peace Palace was destroyed, and with the possibility that the entire imperial palace might be ruined if this fight continued any longer, Eunuch Wei had to interfere.

“Everyone, how about we end today’s matter as is? The Empress and Imperial Concubine Moon should also be tired? Perhaps it would be good if you were to return to your quarters to rest.”

With Eunuch Wei’s appearance, he spoke a few words in order to defuse the conflict.

Just as the two sides were about to engage in a life or death fight, a word to pause the battle and they had paused. In a situation where either side would suffer a loss if they continued, this was the only choice they could make.

Lin Ming looked deeply at White Sky. In truth, he also knew that with his strength, although he could defeat White Sky if he used everything at his disposal, killing him wasn’t likely.

And in the imperial palace, if he wanted to kill the Empress then Eunuch Wei wouldn’t stand idly by and allow that to happen. Not to mention that Eunuch Wei was stronger than White Sky. If Lin Ming were to fight with him then it was unknown who would win in the end. Truly fighting with Eunuch Wei would be an unwise idea that would only earn him another formidable enemy. Moreover, in the Marvel Blue Nation, there was more than one World King master.

Besides, Lin Ming didn’t know this Lord Snow to begin with so he had no obligation to risk his life for him. He also didn’t intend to interfere in the struggle for the throne.

Lin Ming only wanted the Celestial Tyrant Manual and now he had mostly achieved his goal.

Lin Ming glanced over at Blood Moon. Blood Moon bowed, intending to resolve the conflict like this.

The truth was that they had already taken the advantage. The maids and eunuchs that Naye had raised had mostly died and Eunuch Sun had been killed by Lin Ming. Even the carefully constructed Arid Peace Palace that symbolized the will of the Empress had been destroyed.

To Naye, the peak Holy Lord Eunuch Sun had been her absolute right hand. But now that he was cut down by Lin Ming, she could only swallow this insult.

This was the suppression brought by strength.

Blood Moon was filled with curiosity towards Lin Ming. She wanted to know just how Lin Ming had learned the Celestial Tyrant Manual, but now was not a good time to ask.

She gently smiled and said to Eunuch Wei, “Since Eunuch Wei has appeared then let us resolve matters like this. I only hope that in the future when I am in Full Moon Hall, there will not be another summons from the Empress where her only goal is to reprimand me!”

Blood Moon’s voice carried with it a slight warning. In truth, she relied on Lin Ming to gain the upper hand.

Even so, Blood Moon still had the capital to remain standing tall. This was because her wounds would heal in another month or two and when her strength was restored to its peak state, she wouldn’t be any weaker than White Sky.

If so, then she naturally had the ability to establish herself in the entire Marvel Blue Imperial Palace.

After being warned by an imperial concubine, Naye’s eyes flashed with a cold light. But, she eventually flung her sleeves backwards and calmly told the remaining eunuchs, “Begin a trip to Soul Nourishing Temple!”

Now that Arid Peace Palace was no more it was naturally impossible for her to rest here. As for Soul Nourishing Temple, it was the palace of the Emperor and only the Empress had the right to enter and pass the night there. The imperial concubines did not have the ability to do so.

Like this, the sudden storm had passed. Although there would be some criticisms due to the destruction of Arid Peace Palace, these opinions would slowly be suppressed.

Lin Ming wouldn’t care about any of this. His only regret today was that he wasn’t able to leave some mark behind on White Sky. Even so, forcing him to burn a bit of his blood essence could be considered sufficient interest.

Lin Ming planned to return to Full Moon Hall with Blood Moon. But at this time, he was stopped by someone.

“This little brother, please stay a moment.”

Lin Ming paused and turned to see Eunuch Wei smiling at him. A eunuch originally grew old strangely, especially when they had a senile-looking appearance. When they smiled, it normally appeared unappealing, and sometimes extremely repugnant.

However, when this Eunuch Wei smiled, it appeared somewhat gentle and kind.

“I never imagined that Lord Snow would have such hidden depths that he could actually request the help of such a peak character like this little brother.”

Eunuch Wei said, his eyes looking up and down Lin Ming. Although he hadn’t seen the entire fight, he could guess the approximate situation. He was extremely curious as to what Lin Ming’s status was. If this Lin Ming came from a large influence, then that influence was likely not something that a Great World King influence like the Marvel Blue Nation could compare with.

The difference was too great!

Lin Ming lightly smiled, “Eunuch Wei has misunderstood. I am not Lord Snow’s helper and I also do not help him. It is only that I have some old friendship with Imperial Concubine Moon so I have come to the palace to pay a visit to her.”

Lin Ming smoothly said. His words caused Eunuch Wei to look at Imperial Concubine Moon with a different light in his eyes. Eunuch Wei was an intelligent person who was also well-informed; he naturally knew the purpose of Imperial Concubine Moon coming to the palace.

He never would have thought that Imperial Concubine Moon knew such a person!

Like this, he had to completely reconsider the imperial struggle between Lord Shen and Lord Snow. He would even need to rely more on Eunuch Liang who was on good terms with Imperial Concubine Moon.

All of this was on the premise that Eunuch Wei thought Lin Ming might have come from a peak Empyrean influence.

A peak Empyrean influence could command the wind and rain within the entire inner Asura Road. To such an influence, Eunuch Wei was nothing more than an ant. If he could form relations with an Empyrean influence then that would mean many benefits in the future!

However, Eunuch Wei could see that Lin Ming had no intention of revealing his background so he could only put the plan of climbing relations with Lin Ming behind. He smiled and said “Little brother, if you are interested then you can come to the Marvel Blue Nation as a guest. My Marvel Blue Nation will certainly welcome you as an honored guest!”

Eunuch Wei spoke these words in front of everyone.

And at this time, Empress Naye had yet to leave. Whether it was Arid Peace Palace of Full Moon Hall, the many eunuchs and maids were able to clearly hear him.

In the eyes of these young eunuchs and maids, Eunuch Wei was, aside from the old Emperor who was nearing the end of his lifespan, one of the three World King powerhouses of the Marvel Blue Nation. Moreover, even amongst ordinary World Kings, Eunuch Wei’s strength was still considered in the upper echelons. He had already cultivated the Sunflower Melody to an unbelievable boundary.

Within the imperial palace, Eunuch Wei was the absolute chief eunuch in charge of all internal affairs. Not only did the Empress and numerous princes need to pay him due respect, but if he was to clearly state his support for Prince Shen or Grandprince Snow, then the matter of ascension would already be half-settled.

Unfortunately, no one was able to successfully curry favor with Eunuch Wei. Even though Lord Shen and Lord Snow and sent him gifts again and again, these gifts had been fully returned by him.

But now, this Eunuch Wei who held one of the top three positions of power and authority within the Marvel Blue Nation was actually taking the initiative to show goodwill towards Lin Ming. This caused the young eunuchs and maids to be startled. As they looked at Lin Ming once more, they felt that he was an increasingly unfathomable youth.

In fact, these young eunuchs and maids had a limited cultivation boundary so it was hard for them to understand just what Lin Ming’s strength and talented represented. It was Eunuch Wei’s flattering words towards him that left the greatest impact on them!

As for Empress Naye, as she sat in her palanquin she also froze as she heard Eunuch Wei’s words. Her complexion turned grim.

Finally, she settled herself in her seat and shouted to the eunuch beside her. “Begin the trip to Soul Nourishing Temple –”

Like this, the people of Arid Peace Palace vanished around a corner.

As for the eunuchs and maids of Full Moon Hall, all of them returned, overflowing with joy and thankfulness. The eunuchs that carried the palanquin were especially zealous in their actions, each step they took floating up as if they were going to fly.

They all felt as if they had overcome and won a great war.

Chapter 1589 – Blood Moon’s Identity

Lin Ming had long felt it was strange. A cultivation method manual on the level of the Celestial Tyrant Manual was unique; only a single copy existed. If one wanted to copy it then they would need to practice the Celestial Tyrant Manual to perfection like the creator themselves had.

In this sort of situation, the creator would need to spend many years and a great deal of energy to make a copy.

There were extremely few people able to achieve this point, especially since the Celestial Tyrant Manual was so difficult to cultivate.

If there really was someone capable of making a copy of the Celestial Tyrant Manual then that was likely from some time before 3.6 billion years ago.

For this cultivation method to be found within the Divine Realm as well as by Blood Moon in the Asura Road, and for the two versions to supplement each other, that was far too great a coincidence.

Although Lin Ming had his suspicions, he had only just met Blood Moon and didn’t know her at all. Anything that involved the Celestial Tyrant Manual likely involved some secret of hers, thus she wouldn’t reveal that to others. It was only now that Lin Ming was slightly closer to Blood Moon that he asked her.

However, Lin Ming didn’t think that after he asked this question, Blood Moon would actually seem embarrassed, not too willing to reply.

“Sir Lin… this Celestial Tyrant Manual is something I obtained in a mystic realm and as for the details, they actually concern some of my secrets. Once I speak of them they might become a threat to my personal safety so I cannot tell you… my apologies!”

Blood Moon carefully weighed her words. Even though Lin Ming had helped her she still had to conceal the origins of her cultivation method manual; she couldn’t help but feel sorry from her heart.

But Lin Ming was actually quite relaxed about this. He casually said, “If this matter involves your safety then there is no need for you to tell me anything. I am not offended at all.”

As Lin Ming said this, a glimmer of remorse shined within Blood Moon’s eyes. She said, “This is really difficult to say, but Sir Lin, the truth is that I would like to ask you about the origin of the Celestial Tyrant Manual in your hands. If I’m not wrong, at the time Sir Lin was facing White Sky, when you faced the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, you used a secret technique from the Celestial Tyrant Manual to increase your strength by several times?”

Lin Ming was a bit surprised that Blood Moon recognized the Celestial Tyrant Manual he used. Although it seemed that Blood Moon also practiced the Celestial Tyrant Manual, the Celestial Tyrant Manual in her hands only concerned the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace and she hadn’t even opened the complete Eight Inner Hidden Gates, so how had she done it?

Lin Ming had some faint ideas in his mind. Could it be that…?

He looked deeply at Blood Moon, a brilliant light shining in his eyes.

This brief hesitation caused Blood Moon to think that Lin Ming wasn’t willing to reply. She sighed and said, “I know that my question is somewhat excessive, but it’s just that the origin of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates section of the Celestial Tyrant Manual in your hands is extremely important to me and involves someone that I have been continuously searching for all this time. To me, that person is as important as my own life. I ask that Sir Lin please tell me. If Sir Lin wishes to know about the Celestial Tyrant Manual in my hands, then I can also explain, but I hope that Sir Lin can take an oath on your heart of martial arts to never reveal it…”

As Blood Moon spoke to here, Lin Ming looked at her, his eyes filled with disbelief.

Could the person Blood Moon was searching for be…

In this world, was there really such a wonderful coincidence?

Seeing Lin Ming in a daze, Blood Moon was a bit worried. The reason she was willing to concede this time was to ask Lin Ming about this matter. But if Lin Ming didn’t want to say anything to her then there was nothing she could do.

“Sir Lin, I will tell you about the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace section of the Celestial Tyrant Manual in my hands. I only hope that you do not leak it to others, otherwise it will create a threat to my life…”

Just as Blood Moon was about to reveal some of her secrets, Lin Ming took a deep breath. With a strange expression he said, “Could… the person you be looking for have the surname Mo…?”

As Lin Ming spoke, Blood Moon jumped up as if she had been shocked, her entire body suddenly freezing. She looked at Lin Ming with eyes filled with disbelief. Then, slowly, the shock in her eyes slowly turned to joy and euphoria!

Her fingers trembled. However, she was aware of what was about to happen, and fear surged in her heart. She was afraid that what she was about to learn was bad news.

Seeing Blood Moon’s response, Lin Ming was able to confirm his own speculations. He sighed. He never thought that he would find the person Miss Mo had requested him to find.

Lin Ming understood that the ‘moon’ word from the codename Blood Moon actually came from her real name – Mo Brightmoon.

And Mo Brightmoon was Mo Eversnow’s younger sister who had been lost for many years. In the past, because Tian Mingzi was hunting them down, Mo Eversnow had offered her soul to the Magic Cube in order to start a storm that killed 10,000 masters of the Divine Realm as well as send her little sister away from the Snowfall Realm. From that day on, Mo Brightmoon’s whereabouts had been unknown.

Lin Ming never imagined that Mo Brightmoon, in order to take revenge, would enter the Asura Road to temper herself and even join Heaven’s Net!

On the edge of life and death, she sharpened her strength so that she would one day have the power to take revenge.

At the same time, she was also searching for news of her older sister.

As for the word ‘blood’ from Blood Moon, it expressed her blood hatred that was as deep as the sea, as well as her domain, the Endlessly Long Night which Mo Brightmoon used. This domain had a phenomenon where a blood moon would hang high in the sky!

For Lin Ming and Blood Moon to meet here today was a tremendous coincidence as well as reasonable truth. This was because Blood Moon had to enter the Asura Road due to Tian Mingzi’s existence in the Divine Realm, just like Lin Ming had entered the Asura Road because of the Good Fortune Saint Son. And after entering the Asura Road, he went searching for clues related to the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, and this led him to the Celestial Tyrant Manual and Blood Moon.

These similar choices led to today’s coincidence. It was the existence of the Celestial Tyrant Manual that led the two of them to meet each other.

However, in Lin Ming’s opinion, it was far too difficult for Blood Moon to take revenge. If Tian Mingzi hadn’t lost his hand at the Sky Spill Planet then he might have already entered the half-step Empyrean realm.

As for Mo Brightmoon, after passing through many tribulations and working herself to the bone for all these years, she was only at the early World King realm.

The difference between these two boundaries could be overcome by a peerless genius that ranked in the top several talents of their race. But to geniuses whose level of talent was similar to an Empyrean descendant’s, this difference could take tens of thousands or even hundreds of thousands of years to bridge, and even that would be extremely difficult.

And for those with less talent, they would never be able to overcome this boundary.

Tian Mingzi’s talent was at the peak Empyrean descendant level. It would be far too difficult for Mo Brightmoon to surpass him!

Seeing Mo Brightmoon waver as if she were caught in a dream, Lin Ming said, “Miss Mo is safe. Because of some reasons, she was unable to come with me, but she is currently training with an Empyrean master. If you wish to see her then after my journey through the Asura Road I can lead you to her. Before this, I had also heard Miss Mo speak about you. Are you the young Saintess of the Verdant Feather Holy Lands, Mo Brightmoon?”

As Lin Ming said this, Mo Brightmoon’s entire body shivered. She had to grab onto the table to steady herself.

She had searched for 50,000 years, and now she had finally obtained news about her older sister!

“She’s safe… she’s safe…”

Mo Brightmoon mumbled, repeating Lin Ming’s words like a mantra. Tears fell down from her eyes, moistening her veil.

Lin Ming didn’t speak. He sat silently on the side. He knew that today’s news was extremely impactful to Mo Brightmoon and she would need some time to regain her composure.

After a quarter hour, Mo Brightmoon returned from the great sadness and happiness of hearing news about her family. As she looked towards Lin Ming, her eyes were filled with a deep sense of gratitude.

“Excuse me, but may I ask what Sir Lin and my older sister’s relationship is…” Mo Brightmoon said. As she looked at Lin Ming, her vision towards him was completely different from before. To Mo Brightmoon, finding out clues about her older sister was more important than any favor.

“To me, Miss Mo is both a master and a friend. She helped me walk through the road of martial arts when I first started, and that period of time was the most difficult for me. She taught me many things, and although Miss Mo and I could be called master and apprentice, we are also partners that have fought for life and death together. She has saved my life several times, and I have also saved her. Our relationship could be said to have reached a degree where there is nothing we cannot say to each other and nothing we cannot share with each other. We trust each other as much as we trust ourselves. Normally, I call Miss Mo my senior-apprentice sister, thus in terms of relations, I am her junior-apprentice brother.”

As Lin Ming said these words, Mo Brightmoon mostly believed him. Of course, this was only Lin Ming’s one-sided statement and that wasn’t enough to win over Mo Brightmoon’s complete trust.

Thus, Lin Ming continued to speak. He spoke about Mo Eversnow bringing him to Carefree Island and Immemorial Imperial City. He spoke about obtaining the Ten Severing Dao Fruit Tree and many other treasures. He spoke about meeting Mo Eversnow’s aunty, Mo Riverbliss. He spoke about the chess piece that the Verdant Feather Holy Lands had hidden in Carefree Island. He spoke about all of this in great detail.

After hearing this, Mo Brightmoon completely believed Lin Ming. If Lin Ming didn’t have a completely trustworthy relationship with Mo Eversnow then there was no way she would lead Lin Ming to Carefree Island and entrust him with everything. This was the same as placing all hopes of reviving the Verdant Feather Holy Lands onto Lin Ming.

And in Mo Brightmoon’s opinion, Lin Ming was far too amazing. He had the strength and ability to easily accomplish this!

“I never thought that my older sister would be able to find an unrivalled talent like you. This is my older sister’s luck as well as the luck of the Verdant Feather Holy Lands. You have yet to reach 60 years of age and yet your cultivation is at the early Divine Lord realm and you can even fight an ordinary World King. Your achievements in the divine runic arts are also unbelievable. Moreover, you even cultivated the complete Eight Inner Hidden Gates and broke into the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace! I’m really finding it hard to imagine just how you accomplished all of this in less than 60 years of training… no matter how talented you are and how many lucky chances you find, your diligence and hard work must be incomparable!”

In Mo Brightmoon’s ear, Lin Ming could be called a hero of the world! Even within a great calamity, an unrivalled talent like Lin Ming might not appear. He was a person that could carry a great calamity on his shoulders. For instance, Empyrean Divine Seal from 3.6 billion years ago might not be any better than Lin Ming.

Of course, all of this was on the premise that Lin Ming could maintain his current level of talent as well as maintain his forwards momentum.

“Big Sister is really fortunate to have your help. With you, rebuilding the Verdant Feather Holy Lands won’t be too difficult! Even taking revenge on Tian Mingzi will only be a matter of time!” Speaking of Tian Mingzi, Mo Brightmoon found it hard to remain calm. She really hated Tian Mingzi to the point of gnashing her teeth at the thought of him! Tian Mingzi also came from the Verdant Feather Holy Lands but had betrayed them, overthrowing them and even slaughtering the Mo Family!

This hatred was absolutely irreconcilable!

“That scumbag Tian Mingzi is probably at the peak Great World King realm now. The grudge that my Verdant Feather Holy Lands holds towards him must be considered further; we cannot be impatient about this.

As Mo Brightmoon spoke, a strange color came over Lin Ming’s face. He hesitated for a moment before saying. “Ah… about your enmity against Tian Mingzi, you might not need to worry about that anymore…”

Chapter 1590 – Hard to Believe

“Mm? What did you say?” Mo Brightmoon froze for a moment. She didn’t understand what Lin Ming meant. “‘You might not need to worry about that anymore?’”

As Mo Brightmoon spoke, she looked at Lin Ming, puzzled. According to Lin Ming, he and Mo Eversnow were partners that trusted each other with their lives. If Mo Eversnow had an enmity she had to avenge, Lin Ming wouldn’t sit by and do nothing.

Mo Brightmoon looked at Lin Ming, waiting for his explanation.

Lin Ming thought about his words for a moment. Although he felt this was ridiculous to say, Mo Brightmoon should still believe him. But it might take her some time to accept it…

He paused for a while to give Mo Brightmoon enough time to prepare her mind. Then, he slowly said, “Well… the truth is that Tian Mingzi has already died.”

“W-what!?”

Mo Brightmoon shot up, even nearly knocking over the pot of fog rain tea.

“You said… that Tian Mingzi has died!?”

Mo Brightmoon stared at Lin Ming, great waves roiling in her heart!

For all these years, Tian Mingzi was a great mountain that constantly pressed on her. Her joining an assassin organization was all in order to temper herself. Only by passing through endless slaughters and walking upon the thin edge of death would she be able to easily break through to the next boundary.

Mo Brightmoon was well aware that her talent was far inferior to Tian Mingzi’s. Not just that but Tian Mingzi was far older than she was. For her to surpass Tian Mingzi would be more difficult than ascending to heaven!

Thus, she had to put forth even greater effort!

And because of Tian Mingzi’s existence, Mo Brightmoon had to conceal her identity and never mention anything about her life. Even Eunuch Liang only knew that her nickname was Blood Moon; no one knew her true name.

Hiding her status in an assassin organization like Heaven’s Net was even easier.

However, this blood enemy that had pressured so much it left her gasping for breath, her greatest enemy that prevented her from rebuilding the Verdant Feather Holy Lands, her enemy, an existence she never knew when she would be able to contend with, she had been informed by Lin Ming that he had died!

This caused Mo Brightmoon’s mind to turn into chaos. She found it hard to respond.

What sort of person was Tian Mingzi? 50,000 years ago he broke through to the World King realm. Moreover, with his talent, he was likely a Great World King now, or even a peak Great World King, someone touching upon the half-step Empyrean realm.

Such people rarely perished within mystic realms. And with Tian Mingzi’s sinister and crafty tactics, wanting him to randomly perish would simply be a daydream. So, how did he die?

Was he killed by someone? Who could kill a peak Great World King?

Mo Brightmoon’s first reaction was disbelief. But, she felt that Lin Ming was someone who didn’t normally boast, but when he did it would surprise others. This sort of person would normally not lie and there was also no benefit for Lin Ming to do so.

“Is… it this thanks to the help of your master?” Mo Brightmoon suddenly realized. If Lin Ming had the help of a peak Empyrean powerhouse then he really could kill Tian Mingzi!

Even if Tian Mingzi was a Great World King who ruled over his own world and even established his own Great World King influence, a peak Empyrean could still kill him and suppress everything that followed with their strength.

If her big sister Mo Eversnow wasn’t able to wait and truly hated Tian Mingzi to the bone, then asking Lin Ming’s master for help was a high possibility.

“Master…” An awkward expression colored Lin Ming’s face. He drank some more fog rain tea and said, “I have had several masters before, but currently, most of them cannot fight me… as for that peak Empyrean master, the truth is that he doesn’t exist…”

Lin Ming had indeed apprenticed himself to several masters in the past. There was Divine Phoenix Island’s Mu Yuhuang, the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s Fairy Feng, Huo Violentstone, and many others. These people were no longer Lin Ming’s match.

However, as Lin Ming said this, Mo Brightmoon’s face twisted like the tiny runes in a divine runic symbol. She looked at Lin Ming like he was some sort of freak.

Mo Brightmoon didn’t respond for a long time. “You… you don’t have a master? Did you cultivate to your present level by yourself?”

“Mostly, yes.” Lin Ming spread his hands. “I created an Empyrean master in order to provide some protection for myself. My strength is a little limited right now so I feared that there would be some people with dark intentions towards the secrets on my body. With the deterrence of a peak Empyrean master, more people will hesitate before doing anything.

“If I really had to say that I had an Empyrean level master, the truth is that I do; that is Empyrean Primordius. But he has been missing for many years and he has likely perished. As for others, there is also Empyrean Divine Dream who gave me directions once, although she didn’t direct me too much.”

Lin Ming’s words had already left Mo Brightmoon speechless.

If Lin Ming didn’t have a true peak Empyrean master, then how had he managed to cultivate to such an abnormal degree!?

“Then… if you don’t have a master… Tian Mingzi… how did he die?”

Mo Brightmoon said with some difficulty as she slowly recovered from accepting the fact that there could be a monstrous existence like Lin Ming.

Lin Ming stiffened for a moment. He looked at Mo Brightmoon. Even though he knew she would find this hard to believe, that anyone would find this hard to believe, he still said, “The truth is that… Tian Mingzi was killed by me…”

With this, Mo Brightmoon nearly spat out a mouthful of blood.

“W-what did you say!?”

Was there anything more absurd than this? Lin Ming was a youth with less than 60 years of cultivation and yet he had killed a peak Great World King!!

Even though Mo Brightmoon believed that Lin Ming wasn’t someone who liked to boast, she still felt this was far too unbelievable!

Luckily, Lin Ming continued to explain, “I didn’t strike down Tian Mingzi all by myself. It was because Tian Mingzi was injured beforehand. To be more exact, I lured him into an absolute death zone and used the killing array within to severely wound him and then kill him at his weakest point.”

Although Lin Ming explained the situation, Mo Brightmoon was still shocked in a daze. Luring him into an absolute danger zone to kill him?

Lin Ming had said this all lightly, but how could it be so easy? This sort of danger zone was likely deadly to Lin Ming too, moreover, Mo Brightmoon understood what Tian Mingzi’s methods were like. He was a sinister and deceitful figure, so how could he be easy to trick? And how could he be so easily killed by others?

“What… what danger zone was it?” Mo Brightmoon felt as if she had used up her lifetime supply of astonishment. She didn’t know how to face this monster in front of her.

“God Burying Ridge.”

“God Burying Ridge…” Mo Brightmoon sucked in a breath of cold air. She had definitely heard of this danger zone before.

That was a place where it was said even Great World Kings could perish and only Empyreans could freely enter and leave. Lin Ming had actually used the terrain of the danger zones within God Burying Ridge to kill Tian Mingzi. If he did so then he must have chosen the most dangerous of places within God Burying Ridge, but how could Lin Ming himself leave those places alive?

“If there was a danger zone that could even severely wound Tian Mingzi, then how did you live?” Mo Brightmoon asked, unable to understand what happened.

“That… is a long story. The main reason is that I perfectly passing a trial in the past and obtained some certain information on God Burying Ridge, and when I was forced into Tragic Death Valley by Tian Mingzi, that allowed me to comprehend some things, giving me an understanding of God Burying Ridge’s killing arrays.”

“You… you entered… Tragic Death Valley?” Mo Brightmoon’s jaw nearly fell down. Disbelief colored her face. “You said that you entered Tragic Death Valley? The Tragic Death Valley that no one has managed to return from for 10 billion years?”

Mo Brightmoon knew how horrifying a place Tragic Death Valley was; it was the core of God Burying Ridge. Although Empyreans could freely enter and leave God Burying Ridge, if they were to enter Tragic Death Valley, they still wouldn’t be able to return no matter what they tried.

There were some rumors that Empyrean Divine Mist might have entered Tragic Death Valley and was unable to leave. Although these were only legends, it was still enough to demonstrate how terrifying Tragic Death Valley was.

“Uh… there should only be one Tragic Death Valley…” Lin Ming rubbed his nose. Even he felt this was a bit too outrageous. The average person would find this really too hard to accept.

“…”

Mo Brightmoon had long been at a loss for words. When Lin Ming said he had entered Tragic Death Valley and then returned, Mo Brightmoon wasn’t shocked at all. Rather, after learning so many surprising new things, she had been left numb.

“You said… you were forced into Tragic Death Valley by Tian Mingzi and then after you left you lured him into a danger zone and kill him instead…?”

Mo Brightmoon mumbled, summarizing what had happened.

“Yes.” Lin Ming nodded.

“Tian Mingzi is a cunning and sinister person, so how could he have been tricked by you?” Mo Brightmoon asked.

Lin Ming said, “He thought that he could kill me. Moreover, he had no choice but to kill me. So even though he knew that he was heading into a danger zone, he had no choice but to continue hunting me down. The situation at the time was extremely special…”

Concerning the matter about being chased down by Tian Mingzi, Lin Ming didn’t conceal anything from Mo Brightmoon. He explained to her the entire process, including what the circumstances were that Tian Mingzi chased after him as well as his escape route being blocked so he had no choice but to try and kill him.

Lin Ming even explained about Imperial Prince Naqi, half-step Empyrean Ash Murder, and World King powerhouse Mister Zhou, all of those people who had tried to kill him and then ended up dying instead.

As Mo Brightmoon listened to this, her lips twitched. She lifted her teacup and took a big sip as she regained her composure, slowly digesting everything Lin Ming said.

According to what Lin Ming said, when he was still at the Divine Transformation realm he had been chased down by a number of World Kings.

Then, Lin Ming was forced into Tragic Death Valley where he broke through to the Divine Lord realm. After he left, he killed several half-step World Kings, a World King, and a half-step Empyrean. During this time, Lin Ming had used a killing array to play around with all of these people, using all sorts of tricks and schemes to slowly kill them off. During this process, his strength, will, judgment, mentality, foresight, his ability to adapt, everything was indispensable!

After that, Lin Ming was nearly defeated by Tian Mingzi. Even though Tian Mingzi had fought with every trick up his sleeves, forcing Lin Ming into dead end after dead end, Lin Ming still broke through his boundaries and opened the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace.

Finally, he killed Tian Mingzi!

Like this, everything that tried to kill him had ended up being killed by him.

After thinking about all of the events that happened, Mo Brightmoon calmed down. Her gaze was steady as she looked at Lin Ming, and she thought to herself, “Big Sister, Big Sister… just what kind of monster have you found?”

As Mo Brightmoon spoke, she slowly lifted her veil…

Chapter 1594 – Quiet Training

News of Lin Ming establishing his own divine runic arts room and an alchemy room soon spread throughout the entire Blue Moon Sect.

This was extremely fresh and novel news. In the Asura Road, alchemists were not rare, but the occupation of divine runic master was considered a noble career throughout the entire Asura Road. Divine runic masters would only gather in peak great influences as well as large cities devoted to the divine runic arts like Divine Rune City.

But to the Blue Moon Sect, these peak great influences were simply legends amongst legends; it was impossible for them to ever come into contact with them. As for Divine Rune City, only the most amazing elites of the Blue Moon Sect were able to enter; ordinary disciples wouldn’t even be able to step past the city gates.

Thus, the occupation of divine runic master was something that the disciples of the Blue Moon Sect had only heard of but had never seen before. As they suddenly heard that a divine runic master had appeared in their sect, all of them ran over to Lin Ming’s residence to take a look and see just what a divine runic master looked like and what type of work they did.

However, this disciple called Lin Ming didn’t seem willing to communicate with others. When the average person entered his residence he would actually remain in his alchemy room or divine runic arts room, tinkering with something, without any intention of coming out to greet guests.

Even if he wasn’t refining pills or practicing divine runic arts, he would often be quietly meditating in his room. Or, he would sometimes be holding a blood red jade slip. This jade slip was extremely strange. It was far larger than an ordinary jade slip and had a very heavy and solemn appearance to it. It was unknown just what was recorded within it.

This youth called Lin Ming would look at this jade slip every day. His straight eyebrows often rose up and wrinkled like he was puzzled. But sometimes he would have an extremely happy appearance as if he was suddenly enlightened.

These actions left his visiting guests feeling awkward and embarrassed. Others asked Lin Ming how he had come into contact with the divine runic arts, what his divine runic arts level was, or whether he had a true divine runic arts master as his teacher. But, Lin Ming either remained silent or immersed in his blood red jade slip, without seeming as if he heard anything at all. This caused those disciples that were extremely interested in the divine runic arts to feel snubbed, as if they were making themselves unwelcome.

There were many female disciples within the Blue Moon Sect. Many of these young girls were well known for their beauty within several hundred thousand or even millions of miles. However, no matter how outstanding their appearance or how amazing their talent was, they were all denied by Lin Ming.

Slowly, no one came to visit Lin Ming anymore.

And Lin Ming also began his quiet days of training.

After practicing martial arts for so many years, Lin Ming had never been like he was today, truly settling down his mind and heart, not needing to think about matters or worrying every day. Instead, he calmly and peacefully trained.

With Xiao Moxian, they were like an ordinary mortal couple. Every day was filled with ease and enjoyment.

Here there were no battles, no dangers, no mystic realms that he had to risk his life in, and no people with dark intentions that coveted his treasures.

Life and death dangers and slaughter battles were undoubtedly helpful for making breakthroughs in cultivation.

But to practice the divine runic arts and accumulate cultivation, a peaceful environment was much more suitable. Many heroic young elites often spent several thousand years or even over 10,000 years to break into the Divine Lord realm.

Of these thousands upon thousands of years, only a minor period of time would be spent searching for lucky chances and adventuring through dangers. Most of the time would be spent tempering one’s state of mind and accumulating one’s cultivation and consolidating one’s foundation. This was the life Lin Ming was living now.

Although his cultivation progressed extremely slowly during this time, this was an essential process of walking down the road of martial arts. All martial artists had to experience it and Lin Ming was no exception.

Spring became autumn and then back again. In the blink of an eye, a year had passed.

If Lin Ming wasn’t practicing the divine runic arts or alchemy, he could be found with that blood red jade slip in his hands.

This jade slip was the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace section of the Celestial Tyrant Manual.

As Lin Ming was reading through this jade slip he didn’t conceal anything. This was because no one would be able to recognize anything about this jade slip to begin with.

After diligently meditating for a year, Lin Ming gradually found clues about refining the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill.

Of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, the second Dao Palace corresponded to the Ravenous Wolf Star.

The Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, seven bright and two dark. They were – Ravenous Wolf, Titan Gate, Cherished Kismet, Merciful Song, Ardent Virtue, Martial Song, Army Breaker, Left Aide, and Right Support.

The first Dao Palace that Lin Ming opened was the Purple Temple Dao Palace, corresponding to the Army Breaker Star.

The function of the Purple Temple Dao Palace was to gather the power of the nine stars and massively increase the strength of Lin Ming’s astral essence. This sort of increase could enhance Lin Ming’s bodily strength by three or four times to eight or nine times. All of this depended on a martial artist’s own foundation and the degree to which they had opened the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace.

As for the second Dao Palace, that was named Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace, and corresponded to the Ravenous Wolf Star.

Lin Ming revolved his astral essence every day according to the Celestial Tyrant Manual. In addition to dual cultivating with Xiao Moxian, Lin Ming estimated that in another 20-30 years, he would finally reach the level where he could attempt to break into the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace.

And in these 20-30 years, Lin Ming had to bring his divine runic arts and alchemy up to the level where he could refine the Ravenous Wolf Heavenly Pill.

Otherwise, if he spent an unimaginable amount of wealth and time to collect the materials for the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill but failed in refining it, that would truly be a hopelessness beyond crying.

Although there seemed to be plenty of time with the opening of the final trial being 50 years from now, the truth was that time was of the essence. There were far too many matters for Lin Ming to process.

Like this, a few more years passed. Lin Ming continuously practiced alchemy and the divine runic arts. The massive amount of materials he had purchased from Divine Rune City was slowly used up.

His skill in the divine runic arts and alchemy also steadily increased.

During this time, Lin Ming refined a mind-boggling amount of low level pills and divine runic symbols.

Lin Ming’s soul force far surpassed that of others at his level. In addition to his understanding of the Asura Heavenly Dao, whether it was refining pills or drawing up divine runic symbols, he was much faster than the average person would be.

However, even though Lin Ming had inherited the memories of three alchemists and divine runic masters, this didn’t mean his alchemy technique and divine runic arts technique was flawless.

On this day, as Lin Ming was halfway through refining a furnace full of pills, there was a massive bang as the entire pill furnace exploded.

Even though Lin Ming reacted extremely fast, half the room still collapsed. The carefully arranged alchemy room was also left in an utter mess.

As a Divine Transformation outer court Elder of the Blue Moon Sect heard this news, he quickly went to personally check it out.

He inspected Lin Ming’s body. Then, after making sure that Lin Ming was uninjured he gave him several words of advice. In short, he hinted that Lin Ming need not worry about such useless things and only needed to practice martial arts; that was the true, orthodox path.

In the eyes of these numerous Elders, experimenting with alchemy and divine runic arts was simply a wasteful occupation where one idled their time away. This was because with Lin Ming’s current conditions it would be impossible for him to make any progress.

Moreover, the divine runic arts had too high a requirement on a martial artist’s talent. Almost only spiritas martial artists were able to be divine runic masters. For a human martial artist to become a divine runic master, that was far, far, far too difficult.

To put it rudely, it was the dreams of a fool.

But Lin Ming didn’t heed the advice of the Elder and the Elder couldn’t force him. After all, if Lin Ming joined the Blue Moon Sect, he could also leave.

If they wanted to retain the mind and hearts of people, they needed to give them more freedom.

The Blue Moon Sect Elder sent a low level disciple to clean up the room. Soon, three outer court disciples came to Lin Ming’s residence to clean his room.

These outer court disciples were in their teens and their cultivation was at the Pulse Condensation realm. They had just joined the Blue Moon Sect and had been chosen from the mortal world.

In the Blue Moon Sect, their status was low. Although they were called outer court disciples, the truth was that they weren’t much different from maids.

Lin Ming glanced at these three female disciples. All of them looked naïve and adorable, like lovely young girls.

Lin Ming also knew that although these young girl disciples seemed to be living through many hardships, the truth was that their families were proud to have daughters who managed to pass the standards to join a large martial arts sect. The family and friends of these young girls were filled with pride and joy, and even the royalty of the mortal world had to show courtesy to their parents.

This was the deterrence brought about by a martial arts sect!

However, the road of martial arts was well known as being extremely rough and filled with bumps. Although the families of these young girls were living bright and glorious lives, who knew what would happen to their daughters in the end? Perhaps they might be abducted by others to become living furnaces, or perhaps after a little bit of success they would perish in a mystic realm, or perhaps they might even be murdered for their possessions…

Thinking of this, Lin Ming lightly sighed. In the past when he first stepped onto the road of martial arts, he also suffered many difficulties.

Seeing the three young girls giving their best to clean up the room, Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. He waved his hand, beckoning them over.

These young girls froze. Lin Ming was a core disciple and his cultivation had reached the late Divine Sea realm. To them, he was an impossibly lofty character. Their difference in status couldn’t even be described as clouds and mud.

Moreover, Lin Ming’s manner was indifferent, and even when inner court disciples came to visit he still didn’t respond to them. Even those amazingly talented and beautiful senior-apprentice sisters had to eat closed doors when they tried to approach Lin Ming.

But Lin Ming was actually calling them over. This made them all feel extremely flustered and flattered.

They stepped over, a bit shy, a bit nervous. Lin Ming took out some bottles. The contents of these bottles were some of the pills that Lin Ming had refined over the past few years.

As Lin Ming was practicing the divine runic arts and alchemy he had produced far too many pills and divine runic symbols. To Lin Ming, these things didn’t have any value at all. They weren’t even worth his time or effort selling them.

However, throwing them away was also a pity. Thus, Lin Ming suddenly had the idea to give these things to others.

This was also for the benefit of the Blue Moon Sect.

After all, for these past years the Blue Moon Sect had treated him considerably well. After determining that Lin Ming’s background had no problems, the Elders of the Blue Moon Sect would send someone over to deliver pills, origin energy runes, and other such resources. To the Blue Moon Sect that could be called poor, these things were worth a good amount of wealth.

These things were for the benefit of the inner court disciples. And because Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian had extremely high levels of talent, the benefits they received were higher than others’. But, Lin Ming also knew that he would have to eventually leave the Blue Moon Sect. If the Blue Moon Sect was depending on him to break through to the Divine Lord realm and become a pillar of the sect, they would be disappointed.

Thus, Lin Ming decided to give away all of these pills and divine runic symbols that didn’t have much value to him to the disciples of the Blue Moon Sect.

The Blue Moon Sect was a small sect to begin with and he didn’t fear arousing suspicions or causing waves by bringing out these items.

It wouldn’t be an exaggeration to say that Lin Ming could raze a sect of this level to the ground with a single hand.

“These are for you.” Lin Ming placed the bottles of pills in a jade box and passed it to the three Pulse Condensation realm outer court disciples. These disciples were lost in a daze, not sure what was in the jade box.

And at this time, Lin Ming said, “Go and call your sisters here as well as the male disciples you know. Call all of them here together.”

Chapter 1595 – Middle Divine Lord Realm

The young female disciples received the jade box. From the slits of the jade box, a rich medicinal fragrance wafted out.

Just by smelling this medicinal fragrance they felt their bodies relax as comfort swept over them. The true essence circulating within their bodies quickened and their cultivation sharpened by several degrees.

If just smelling this medicinal fragrance had such an effect, then eating a pill directly would have an unimaginable benefit.

The oldest of the three young girls gulped. Her hands trembled as she opened the medicine bottle and several green pills rolled out.

These pills were crystalline and sparkled with a clear light. On the surface of the pills were strange lines, faintly hinting at the aura of mysterious Laws.

These lines that were carved onto the pills were pill symbols. The young girls had never seen these pill symbols before; they couldn’t even recognize the names of most of these pills.

However, Lin Ming had given them several types of pills, and the young girls were able to recognize one of them.

This pill was called a Nine Yang Pill and was used by martial artists at the Xiantian realm or below. It was used to consolidate one’s foundation and nourish one’s blood vitality. Each Nine Yang Pill was several dozen times more precious than a single Heaven Opening Pill!

The young girls had once seen the sect provide these pills for talented disciples and had nearly been blinded by awe and greed. Of course, they didn’t have the qualifications to use them.

These Nine Yang Pills that Lin Ming refined were different from the Nine Yang Pills they had seen before. These Nine Yang Pills had strange patterns on the surface, and seemingly because of these patterns, the effects of these pills were far better!

These young girls didn’t know that these ‘pill patterns’ were in fact traces of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws left behind after Lin Ming reinforced them with the divine runic arts.

To Lin Ming these were useless items, but if placed within the Blue Moon Sect, these were treasures even to inner court disciples. These young girls were only outer court disciples, moreover, the effects of these pills were enhanced several times by the divine runic symbols drawn onto them.

In these years, the direction of divine runic arts that Lin Ming practiced had mainly focused on medicinal runic symbols.

Only these types of divine runic symbols had an effect on pills and thus were the most useful to Lin Ming.

“These medicines… are too precious… we cannot accept them…”

The oldest girl, one that looked around 18-19 years old, grit her teeth as she spoke. The truth was that one could see from her expression that she really wanted these pills.

Lin Ming faintly smiled. He had a much more favorable impression of this girl. It wasn’t easy to gather the courage to reject such things.

During these years, Lin Ming had watched the low level disciples of the Blue Moon Sect go into seclusion, journey out to adventure, rush about for resources, and do all sorts of other things. This made him recall his experiences when he was also in his teens.

He lightly smiled, saying, “If I give them to you then take them. Or, are you afraid that the higher level disciples will steal them from you?”

Lin Ming was well aware that even though the Blue Moon Sect seemed like a calm and comfortable place, there were still inevitably inner struggles. These three young girls had ordinary levels of talent and there would naturally be people jealous of these pills.

“For the things I give, I will naturally ensure justice is served. You can feel at ease in taking these pills.”

The two younger girls swallowed a gulp of saliva. Their hands shook as they held the pill bottles.

“Call those you know here.”

Lin Ming sent out the young girls. Several quarter hours later, there were really several outer court disciples that arrived.

These disciples were in their late teens or early twenties. None of them had a cultivation that surpassed the Xiantian realm. They had just started walking on their own roads of martial arts.

For these last four or five years, every other day Lin Ming would refine a furnace full of pills. When he refined less there would be seven or eight, and when he refined many there would be over a dozen. After accumulating pills for all these years, he had already gathered over 10,000 of them.

And, these 10,000 plus pills were all supported with divine runic symbols.

Placed within the Blue Moon Sect, this was an unimaginable level of wealth.

News of Lin Ming wantonly giving out pills soon spread to the entire Blue Moon Sect.

Many outer court disciple and inner court disciples only thought these were rumors, but after seeing the pills that Lin Ming passed out they had no choice but to believe this. Thus, disciples began to visit Lin Ming like droves of ducks. This was because his pills were far too tempting to them.

However, to the inner court disciples, Lin Ming didn’t give pills freely. Instead he had them gather some violet sun crystals.

The price in violet sun crystals was only half or a third of the true value of the pills. This sort of price was already extremely favorable. Many inner court disciples didn’t have a place to purchase pills and these pills were far too difficult to buy to begin with.

Originally, Lin Ming wasn’t too popular. This was because he was far too eccentric and withdrawn, ignoring all visitors that came to see him.

But now, because Lin Ming was passing out pills, this caused his reputation to rise to unprecedented degrees within the Blue Moon Sect.

“Where did these pills come from? Did you refine them?”

The Elders of the Blue Moon Sect were startled. Several of them came over to Lin Ming’s residence to ask him.

“I obtained them through a variety of channels and some are refined by me.” Lin Ming shrugged.

This vague answer clearly indicated that he didn’t wish to speak more about the matter.

The Blue Moon Sect Elders were at a loss of what to do. In truth, it was completely reasonable for Lin Ming to refine these low level pills. According to common logic, these pills could be refined by a late Divine Sea alchemist.

But the low level pills that Lin Ming refined were far too great! Not even the nearby famous alchemists were able to refine pills of similar quality.

Had Lin Ming done all this by studying alone? Was he actually a rare prodigy of alchemy and the divine runic arts?

The Elders looked at each other. They didn’t have any plans of pressing Lin Ming to reveal the origin of the pills. However, on the second day, the Elders invited a family famous for constructing cave dwellings to the Blue Moon Sect, where they constructed an expensive divine runic arts room and alchemy room for Lin Ming.

The Blue Moon Sect even helped Lin Ming by buying a great deal of alchemy materials for him.

This was all welcomed by Lin Ming. Although these were all low level materials, they were more than enough for Lin Ming to practice his technique.

Time slowly passed. The seasons came and went, from spring to fall and back again.

Lin Ming’s skill in the divine runic arts and alchemy reached an increasingly high degree of proficiency.

Now, what he pursued was not just quality in alchemy and divine runic arts, but speed.

At the start, Lin Ming would refine a furnace of pills every two days. Now he would refine two furnaces of pills every single day.

A massive amount of low level pills was constantly produced by Lin Ming.

Although Lin Ming was only giving away some of the inferior medicines he had refined, the quality of these medicines became increasingly high.

Gradually, Lin Ming’s reputation soared to the heavens!

More and more disciples came to purchase pills from Lin Ming. There were even some nearby sects that would come to the Blue Moon sect to purchase pills. Of course, the price this time would rise to the market standard.

Although the price of the pills was increasing, more and more people flocked to buy them.

At this time, no one suspected Lin Ming of obtaining pills from ‘various channels’ any longer. If so many pills were being sold and given out, then the only possibility was that Lin Ming refined them himself.

The Blue Moon Sect realized they had picked up a treasure!

The income from selling pills went into Lin Ming’s hands. Then, he handed this money over to the Blue Moon Sect to have them seek out different materials.

The materials Lin Ming wanted were of an increasingly high grade. The pills he refined also became increasingly refined.

Of course, Lin Ming would not bring out pills that true Divine Lord or Holy Lord realm martial artists could use, in order to prevent some martial artists having dark thoughts. Lin Ming wasn’t scared of them, but if they were to bother him it would be impossible for him to peacefully and calmly meditate here.

Slowly, 12 years passed.

The cultivation that Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian revealed was risen to the Divine Transformation realm.

In the Blue Moon Sect, Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian experienced the toil of daily life. Every now and then they would join the disciples of the Blue Moon Sect to go out adventuring.

For instance, exploring mystic realms, finishing missions, and so forth.

By watching the slaughter and struggles of low level martial artists, he actually found a strange feeling that he had almost forgotten. This odd feeling strangely touched Lin Ming’s heart.

And in the 13th year, as Lin Ming was calmly meditating one day he finally felt something stir within his inner world. He knew that his cultivation was about to make a breakthrough!

From the early Divine Lord realm to the middle Divine Lord realm!

This breakthrough didn’t come suddenly at all. It could be called a simple matter of course. This was like filling a cup with wine, filling it so much that it naturally overflowed.

And the scene of this breakthrough was extremely peaceful.

In the past when Lin Ming made breakthroughs, they tended to shake the heavens and earth or be extremely thrilling, sometimes almost breaking apart his inner world.

But, this breakthrough was tranquil, like a quiet spring day.

Lin Ming only sat in meditation for the night and on the next day as he opened his eyes, his inner world had developed once more and his cultivation rose to the middle Divine Lord realm.

Besides the sensitive Xiao Moxian feeling the change of atmosphere in the room, not even tiny animals in the surrounding area were alarmed.

After five months Xiao Moxian also broke into the middle Divine Lord realm. She only cultivated the essence gathering system and her cultivation speed had been faster than Lin Ming’s. If it wasn’t for Lin Ming obtaining greater advantages during all the lucky chances they experienced, then perhaps Lin Ming’s essence gathering system cultivation might have fallen behind Xiao Moxian’s.

After making a breakthrough, Lin Ming’s strength rose once more. As for the level of Lin Ming’s divine runic arts, it arrived at the standard of a peak fifth grade divine runic master. Moreover, even amongst ordinary fifth grade divine runic masters, Lin Ming had a special advantage; that was that no one could compare to his understandings of the Asura Heavenly Dao.

And at this time, Lin Ming finally began his preparations to refine the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill. In refining the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill, just collecting the required materials would take a tremendous amount of time. He had no choice but to prepare as early as possible. Just by breaking into the middle Divine Lord realm, Lin Ming’s strength hadn’t risen by too much. If he were able to open another Dao Palace then he would be much more confident in entering the final trial.

Chapter 1597 – Astronomically Expensive Materials

When Lin Ming returned to Divine Rune City, he discovered that the atmosphere was different from before. There were over ten times the guards stationed at the city gates.

Originally, there were several guards at the gates of Divine Rune City, and their cultivation was at the Divine Lord realm.

But now, there was a small army of soldiers, and the leader of this group was a Holy Lord.

Every person that entered the city was subjected to a strict interrogation. That Holy Lord captain always held a crystal ball in his hands with strange Law lines that shimmered within it.

These Law lines were clearly due to the divine runic arts. Lin Ming could see from a glance that this crystal ball was used to determine whether or not a martial artist that was trying to enter the city had disguised their cultivation.

“Strange…”

Lin Ming rubbed his chin. Why was Divine Rune City on such high alert all of a sudden?

“Is there some influence that wants to attack Divine Rune City?” Xiao Moxian asked.

Lin Ming shook his head. “It shouldn’t be. Divine Rune City is a neutral place to begin with and it is a massive influence with a tremendous number of divine runic masters. There shouldn’t be anyone that would move against Divine Rune City, especially since so many other organizations depend on them.”

Lin Ming pressed down the suspicions in his mind. He walked over to the city gates with Xiao Moxian whereupon the both of them were immediately stopped.

“City entrance token!” A martial artist icily said as he blocked Lin Ming’s path. Lin Ming looked at the war armor that these guards were wearing. Some of them wore the standard service armor of Divine Rune City and others didn’t.

As if they were formed from two different groups.

Lin Ming said, “I am a divine runic master from the Divine Runic Masters Guild. This is my badge.”

Lin Ming took out his third grade divine runic master badge. After the guard inspected it, he returned it to Lin Ming and allowed him and Xiao Moxian to pass.

After entering Divine Rune City, it became apparent that the inside clearly hadn’t changed much. The streets were still busy and bustling as usual.

Lin Ming walked all the way to the Divine Runic Masters Guild, flashing his divine runic master badge and entering.

As he passed through the trading area he saw many divine runic masters and alchemists trading within. He also immediately saw Old Xue.

At this time Old Xue was comfortably reclining back in a rocking chair. A pile of random items was placed in front of him and he seemed to have fallen asleep.

After 25 years, Old Xue hadn’t changed at all.

As Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian walked past, Old Xue’s eyes suddenly shot open. “Hey boy, so it was you!”

Old Xue’s eyes shined as he saw Lin Ming as if he had seen a treasure. He looked at Lin Ming for a long time, looking him up and down until even Lin Ming began feeling uncomfortable.

Lin Ming coughed, “Elder Xue, it’s been a while.”

Xiao Moxian also sweetly called out, “Elder Xue, it’s nice to see you.”

Old Xue lit up with a smile as he heard Xiao Moxian greet him. He had an extremely good impression of this likable young girl. But as he turned back to Lin Ming, his face darkened.

“It’s been over 20 years. Do you even remember that you are a divine runic master of the Divine Runic Masters Guild? Brat, I think you must have forgotten everything as you went adventuring outside! Even so, it seems you managed to make a breakthrough in your cultivation. I remember that when you left you were only at the early Divine Lord realm.”

Lin Ming rolled his eyes. It seemed this Old Xue really spoke without caring for what he said.

“It’s a lucky breakthrough. I must say Old Xue, now that I’ve returned to Divine Rune City I saw a great number of guards standing outside. Just what is going on?”

“Heh, it’s a war.” Old Xue grinned, looking as if he didn’t care much. It seemed he was already accustomed to these types of situations.

“Although I said it's a war, the truth is that it’s not related to us. It’s a spiritas Empyrean influence of the inner Asura Road, the Extreme Star Holy Lands, fighting with another saint Empyrean influence, the Heaven Strife Holy Lands. As for the reason they decided to suddenly go to war, it's probably because they are competing for something. Our Divine Runic Masters Guild is one of the groups supporting the Extreme Star Holy Lands. Because they’re at war they buy up a massive amount of pills and divine runic symbols that are constantly transported to the war front. As for the guards at the city entrance, they were sent here by the Extreme Star Holy Lands. They’re afraid that there will be some saint spy infiltrating into our city to stir up chaos. During this period of war, all saint martial artists, regardless of whether or not they’re connected to the Heaven Strife Holy Lands, are forbidden from entering the city.”

In these last 100 million years, the Divine Runic Masters Guild would occasionally cooperate with some great influences and provide them with a massive number of pills and divine runic symbols. Of course, these great influences would pay them back with rich rewards, including origin energy runes, rare and precious materials, inheritance jade slips, and so forth.

This was a significant source of wealth for the Divine Runic Masters Guild. Compared to the income of the shops in Divine Rune City, the income from participating in these wars was often far more valuable.

“So it’s like that.” Lin Ming thoughtfully said. When human martial artists studied the divine runic arts they were only inferior to the spiritas. As for the saints, they could be called simple-minded with extremely brawny bodies; their soul force was pitifully weak and they weren’t suited for auxiliary skills like the divine runic arts or alchemy.

Moreover, the saints didn’t have a good relationship with the spiritas to begin with. Indeed, in all these years, there weren’t many saint martial artists that came to Divine Rune City.

The crystal balls placed at the gates of the city were to prevent any saint martial artists from sneaking their way in.

Lin Ming was secretly startled. In these 100 million years it was unknown how many times the Divine Runic Masters Guild had cooperated with other influences like this. The wealth they had accumulated after all this time could be imagined.

“I must say boy, why did you return so suddenly? Is there something going on?” Old Xue eyed Lin Ming suspiciously. He felt that this fishy boy probably needed something.

After being seen through by Old Xue, Lin Ming awkwardly rubbed his chin. He said, “There really is something I need. The reason I returned to Divine Rune City is because I need to buy some materials to refine a pill.”

Lin Ming directly stated a goal.

“Hoh! So you’ve even practiced alchemy!” Old Xue looked at Lin Ming in surprise. With his current understanding of Lin Ming, if Lin Ming dared to say he wanted to refine a pill then his skill in alchemy was likely considerably high.

“You brat, you know to return when you want to make use of us, but are you aware you have zero contribution points!?”

In the Divine Runic Masters Guild, the contributions that a divine runic master made to the guild would be converted into points. Since Lin Ming had been gone for 25 years, he naturally didn’t have any contribution points.

Lin Ming awkwardly coughed. He smiled and said, “There were some matters I had to attend to so I’ve been a bit delayed. I should be staying at the Divine Runic Masters Guild for a period of time, and there really are some rare and precious materials I need to buy, I just don’t know where they are sold.”

As Lin Ming spoke, Old Xue rolled his eyes and sent Lin Ming a look of disdain. He said, “What are you smiling so sadly about? My Divine Runic Masters Guild has the best and most complete material storehouse in the entire world! There are no materials you cannot buy, I’m only afraid that you can’t afford them.”

Old Xue said with full confidence, a great deal of pride glowing on his face.

“Then I’d like to request for you to look over this list and see if I can obtain these materials here.”

Lin Ming smiled and took out a list from his spatial ring. This list had all the materials needed to refine the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill. There were a total of 32 different kinds of materials.

Old Xue took the list with a great show of graciousness. Then, he looked over the list.

He was immediately left dumbfounded.

The first several materials on the list were precious, but as long as one had enough money they could be bought. However, the latter materials were horrifying!

There were several materials that even Old Xue had never seen before; he had only heard of them!

“Dragon saliva grass, heaven devouring snake gallbladder, jade dragon’s horn, primal jade quintessence…” Old Xue was left stunned. Not even the Divine Runic Masters Guild had all of these materials!

Although the Divine Runic Masters Guild’s storehouse was rich and abundant, since there were materials that came in, there were materials that went out. If these materials couldn’t be converted into pills and divine runic symbols then they were useless. Thus, after many rare and precious materials entered the storehouse they would soon be traded away to others.

As for the extremely rare and precious materials that were in high demand and couldn’t be bought normally, they didn’t stay in the storehouse for too long.

These materials that Lin Ming had listed, if placed within the Divine Runic Masters Guild storehouse, would require the highest level of authority to use. That was, the authority of a seventh grade divine runic master!

Moreover, the price was bound to be astronomically high, to the point where one would strain their neck!

“Are you messing around with me!?” Old Xue slapped the list on the table, his beard and eyebrows flying up in a rage. He felt that Lin Ming was teasing him; just how could a young junior use these materials!?

In his opinion, even if Lin Ming obtained these materials it would be impossible for him to use them in alchemy. It would be a complete waste.

“Why would we be messing with you? If we buy them we’re definitely using them.” Xiao Moxian backed up Lin Ming.

Old Xue looked at Xiao Moxian, half believing, half disbelieving. He turned back to Lin Ming. “Are these materials things your master wishes to use?”

Old Xue immediately thought. Lin Ming pushed this train of thought along. He laughed, saying, “That’s about right. Do you think the Divine Runic Masters Guild has these materials?”

Old Xue gave Lin Ming a side-eye and leisurely said, “The more general rare and precious materials are indeed here, but I’m afraid that the Divine Runic Masters Guild only has two or three of the most precious materials on this list. Moreover, they are exorbitantly expensive. Not only do you need a massive amount of origin energy runes, but more importantly you need a certain degree of authority as well as contribution points. I estimate that just one of those materials will require 700-800 million points. If you stay in the Divine Runic Masters Guild in the future you will receive a monthly salary of contribution points. As a third grade divine runic master, I think every 18 million years or so you’ll be able to barely afford a few leaves of dragon saliva grass.”

Old Xue mockingly said. As a third grade divine runic master, Lin Ming’s yearly salary would be around 20 points. In 10 million years he would receive 200 million points, just barely enough to buy a single material.

Of course, if Lin Ming rose to a higher level of divine runic master in the future then his salary would also increase. Even then, it wouldn’t be by too much.

Lin Ming wryly smiled, “Old Xue, I’m glad you’re happy teasing me.”

Old Xue spread his hands in goodwill. “I’m just speaking the truth. Even I can’t afford the things you want. But… if your master is willing to join the Divine Runic Masters Guild then he might be able to obtain what is needed in a short period of time.”

Seeing Old Xue make circles to ask about his master, Lin Ming said, “My master will not come to the Divine Runic Masters Guild. Only I can buy these materials…”

“Ha! Then do as you want.” Old Xue lazily said, his expression saying he didn’t care about Lin Ming’s business. He leaned back in his chair and closed his eyes.

Chapter 1598 – Mission Division

“Lin Ming… what do you plan on doing? 700-800 million points to buy a single one of the materials you need, how could we afford that?”

Although Xiao Moxian’s lips twitched as she saw Old Xue’s disdainful attitude, she couldn’t help but acknowledge that what he said was the truth.

There was simply an astronomical number of contribution points needed to buy these materials. Not to mention that even if they had the contribution points they also needed nine sun jades.

And their nine sun jades weren’t enough.

“Let’s go take a look. Maybe there’s some way we can earn some…”

Lin Ming thought for a moment. He knew that there were several ways in the Divine Runic Masters Guild to earn points.

The first way was a monthly salary. However, as a third grade divine runic master his monthly salary was negligible; it was simply far too little.

The second way was to trade, but Lin Ming couldn’t think of anything he could take out to sell for a large number of contribution points. He had some of the pills and divine runic symbols he drew up at the Blue Moon Sect, and some of them were even decent in quality, but none of these things would be able to sell at a good enough price. The people of the Divine Runic Masters Guild simply had too high a standard.

The third way was missions. The Divine Runic Masters Guild often issued out missions. After completing them, one would receive contribution points as a reward.

The fourth way was to contribute one’s research results and specialized techniques to the Divine Runic Masters Guild. One would earn a great deal of rewards from this.

Lin Ming had several special techniques that others didn’t know of that he had obtained from the memories of the three divine runic masters he killed. But, these techniques weren’t particularly heaven-defying. Even if he contributed them, it was nothing but a drop in the ocean compared to the hundreds of millions of points he needed.

If Lin Ming had a true heaven-defying technique, that would be the understandings of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws described in the Asura Sutra First Volume. But, Lin Ming hadn’t even fully cultivated the Asura Sutra so it was impossible for him to copy down the intricate secrets within, and even if he could he wouldn’t reveal the tiniest secret related to the Asura Sutra. This type of inheritance was just far too tempting to others.

Removing the first, second, and fourth way of earning points, Lin Ming could only choose the third way. That was to undergo missions and earn contribution points.

“Elder Xue, I plan to take on missions to earn points…”

“Take on missions?” Elder Xue looked up at Lin Ming in surprise, a strange light glowing in his eyes. “Don’t tell me you plan on completing missions to earn enough points to buy those materials…”

Lin Ming nodded. “I’ll give it a try. There isn’t another way I can think of.”

“Good heavens boy!” Elder Xue looked at Lin Ming like a lunatic. “Have you not woken up yet? Do you know how many points you will receive per mission at your level? I don’t know what you’ve been messing around with during these last 20 some years, but I could approximately guess it. A monstrous abnormality like you can surprise me, but no matter just how amazing your achievements have been in these 20 some years, you shouldn’t think of relying on that alone to earn enough points through missions. If you want to buy all the materials you want, I estimate you will need at least 3 billion points! Even if I wanted to earn 3 billion points I would have to work myself to the bone and I’d still have no idea how long it would be until I would have earned them all.”

Lin Ming had already thought of everything that Elder Xue spoke of. Although he had a shortcut to studying the divine runic arts and alchemy, in terms of grade, Lin Ming was still a fifth grade divine runic master. After all, the three divine runic masters Lin Ming killed had been at most at the sixth grade, and wanting to surpass them would take more time.

To practice to the point of being a fifth grade divine runic master in a mere 25 years was far too exaggerated; there wouldn’t be anyone who believed this. What fifth grade divine runic master hadn’t spent thousands of years or tens of thousands of years to get where they were?

And even a fifth grade divine runic master wouldn’t be able to refine the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill!

Just the materials alone gave one a headache. Basically speaking, those that could afford the several rare materials he needed were Empyrean level characters. Even a Great World King would feel destitute if they tried to purchase these materials.

However, everything depended on the individual and everything was possible with enough effort. Lin Ming had spent an unimaginable price to first establish the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace and then spent a considerable effort to obtain the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace section of the Celestial Tyrant Manual, finally finding a light on the road. It was impossible for him to give up now.

“Elder Xue, where is the special Mission Division?” Lin Ming asked. He wasn’t too familiar with the Divine Runic Masters Guild.

After Old Xue listened to this he rolled his eyes yet again. “You brat, you don’t even know where the Mission Division is. It’s clear you haven’t come to the Divine Runic Masters Guild even a handful of times!”

Lin Ming hollowly laughed at Elder Xue’s grumbling, not speaking back.

“Whatever, whatever, I just think you’re crazy so just forget about it. I’ll lead you over there so you can see just what the level of rewards is for the missions and finally decide to give up.”

Old Xue had sat at his stall all day and hadn’t sold much at all so he decided to close shop instead. At his age, it was no longer possible to increase his cultivation and he liked to idle his time away. Setting up a stall was just a casual lifestyle that Old Xue liked to live. He loved the sense of achievement of selling high and buying low, and also finding good treasures. The truth was that he didn’t need the stall for any income. This was what people meant by fishing for the fishing and not for the fish.

Old Xue brought Lin Ming through some ancient-looking corridors. Finally, he arrived in another hall of the Divine Runic Masters Guild.

This hall resembled a small city square. The area was considerably broad, covering a wide area. There were a few people here, some young and some old and everyone wore the robes of a divine runic master or alchemist. It seemed they were all people with status.

At the center of the hall was a giant array disc. Above this array disc were floating screens of scrolling text.

This was an illusory magic array. Its role was to project text information and all of these scrolling texts represented missions.

In addition, on the side of the hall there were stacks of scrolls. These scrolls were also missions, but the difficulty was a bit lower than the missions projected on the illusory magic array.

“This is where you can pick up missions! Most of the missions they hand out can be found here. The minor missions give as little as several hundred points and the highest ones are worth a dozen or two million points. But, those missions that give 10-20 million points require you to be at least a peak sixth grade divine runic master. They are extremely difficult and not even I can complete them.”

Old Xue slowly said as he played with a walnut in his hands. This walnut was a magic tool crafted from wood. “Look, I’m not trying to bring you down here, but if you really want to rely on completing missions to buy those precious materials you want then you’ll need several hundred thousand years unless you can rise to an even higher level of divine runic master.”

Lin Ming looked through the mission contents. Indeed as Old Xue said, those that rewarded several million points required one to be a Great World King divine runic master or alchemist to be completed. With Lin Ming’s current strength it was impossible.

Although Old Xue had underestimated Lin Ming’s skill level in the divine runic arts, his conclusion wasn’t wrong in the end. Lin Ming silently calculated. As a fifth grade divine runic master, the highest reward missions he could complete only offered several hundred thousand points.

Moreover, anything that gave several hundred thousand points wasn’t an easy mission at all. These missions took more than four or five days and some even took as long as a month.

If he was obtaining 20,000-30,000 points in one month, he would need to work for over a thousand years to gather 3 billion points.

And this was in a situation where one took missions non-stop. In reality, no one would do this. A divine runic master had to practice, study, go into seclusion, and so forth. It was also impossible for this war to continue for 1000 years.

Lin Ming gained an even deeper understanding of how precious the materials were that he needed to buy. It was simply impossible for a fifth grade divine runic master to obtain them. The only possibility would be a peak sixth grade divine runic master expending a massive amount of time and effort!

Xiao Moxian also knew what level Lin Ming’s skills were at. She worriedly said, “Lin Ming, what can we do? We’ll have to participate in the final trial in another 25 years. There isn’t enough time for you to earn the points.”

“I don’t know. Let’s continue looking first.”

Lin Ming didn’t have any plan currently.

Old Xue spread his hands. “Well, now you’ve seen it. If you want to complete missions to earn enough points for those materials then you’re simply living a dream. But if you don’t want to give up, you can go to the mission posting office to see if there’s some mission that’s good for you.”

Old Xue pointed at the end of the hall.

Over there was an antique long counter, and standing behind this counter were four or five people. Out of them, a young woman with an explosive figure was the most eye-catching.

This woman wore a flame-colored dress, and this dress drew tight to her skin, accentuating her enthralling curves and buxom, perfectly enchanting figure. The front of the dress had deep, plunging neckline, thrusting down and exposing a snow white valley even as it gave a sneak peak of her proud and full breasts. The tight dress had slits that ran up to the base of her thighs and every movement she took drew the eyes to her waist, inviting one to daydream over the hidden wonders.

Chapter 1599 – Fourth Grade Mission

Seeing the woman in the red dress, Lin Ming was stunned. In the world of martial artists, every place had their own clothing customs. In the human race within the Divine Realm, most clothing types tended towards being conservative. But in the inner Asura Road, many places had women that wore bold and provocative clothing.

And with this woman in front of him dressed the way she was, Lin Ming couldn’t help but acknowledge that she had a special flavor to her. She easily aroused a man’s desire to conquer and ravish.

“This woman is quite extraordinary…”

Lin Ming said, his eyes remaining glued to the woman’s body.

Old Xue cheekily grinned. He said to Lin Ming, “Isn’t she a top grade woman? She is from the Extreme Star Holy Lands and her name is Suya. Don’t look down on her, she’s not simple at all!”

Old Xue traced his beard, meaning thick in his voice. He knew that someone with an explosive figure like Suya who dressed in such enchanting clothing exerted a considerably strong attraction towards young men. Her body was like a ripe peach, making everyone want to take a bit of her.

Seeing Old Xue’s expression, Xiao Moxian coughed in displeasure. She twisted Lin Ming’s arm with her hand.

Women could be strange sometimes. Towards naïve and young competitors, they wouldn’t develop any jealousy. For instance, when Lin Ming was in the Blue Moon Sect, Xiao Moxian could see that the Sect Master’s granddaughter Qian Qiao had developed a crush on Lin Ming and she was only a third of his age. As long as Lin Ming wanted to he could have easily taken her in as a concubine. Even so, Xiao Moxian had still been very kind to Qian Qiao, even treating her like she would her own little sister.

But towards this alluring and sexual Suya, Xiao Moxian couldn’t help but think that she was displeasing to the eyes.

Old Xue coughed upon seeing Xiao Moxian’s disgruntlement. He straightened himself out and seriously said, “This Suya is our Divine Runic Masters Guild’s contact with the Extreme Star Holy Lands. If you want to take on a mission it’s best if you go through her, because since the Extreme Star Holy Lands are at war, there are many missions with a high point reward.

“I see.”

Hearing Old Xue’s response, Lin Ming found it all amusing. He walked over to Suya. As he approached he could see that there were six divine runic masters there to take on missions.

Without exception, all of these divine runic masters were men. There were young men as well as middle-aged men. These six divine runic masters were speaking with the red-dressed woman, and from their eyes Lin Ming could see a faint hint of vivid heat.

Normally, young elite divine runic masters had extremely high standards and were never for want of women. There were innumerable women that were willing to throw themselves in the chests of these divine runic masters.

But in front of Suya, they seemed to have lost all the lofty manners of a divine runic master and fell down in worship at the base of her deep red dress.

This also implied to Lin Ming that this Suya was not just a beautiful vase, but also someone with considerable strength and methods.

Lin Ming discovered that these six divine runic masters were treated differently by Suya. Towards the four younger divine runic masters, Suya was polite and curt in her answers, not really paying much attention to them.

It was only to those two middle-aged divine runic masters that Suya spoke at length and smiled warmly. And, those two middle-aged divine runic masters were both peak fifth grade divine runic masters, not too far away from becoming sixth grade divine runic masters.

“This woman is quite arrogant. Those young divine runic masters don’t even enter her eyes, but the range of missions that a young divine runic master can complete is indeed limited.” Lin Ming mused to himself.

Xiao Moxian scoffed. “Did this Extreme Star Holy Land specifically send such a sexually charged young woman here to attract all those deviants at the Divine Runic Masters Guild to complete missions for her?”

Lin Ming was startled for a moment before he laughed out loud. Indeed, this was a possibility. Because of Suya, this Mission Division area might be busier than usual.

Lin Ming pushed into the group of six divine runic masters, causing the four young ones to look at him with annoyance in their eyes.

Lin Ming glanced over their divine runic badges. The four youths were second or third grade divine runic masters. Lin Ming’s badge also indicated he was a third grade divine runic master so their statuses were similar.

“Stop being so pushy!” Someone unhappily said, not recognizing Lin Ming.

Lin Ming had only briefly appeared when he joined in on the divine runic masters examination 25 years ago. Afterwards he left the Divine Runic Masters Guild. Besides Old Xue, Old Su, and the several examination officials present, no one would recognize him.

As that young divine runic master was halfway done speaking, he caught a glance at Old Xue behind Lin Ming. He quickly hid away all anger and instead put on a bright smile, saying, “Greetings, Elder Xue.”

The two middle-aged men also politely greeted Old Xue. “Elder Xue, it seems you also came for missions.”

Although the two middle-aged men were peak fifth grade divine runic masters, there was a great difference between them and the sixth grade divine runic master Old Xue. This was essentially the difference between a peak Holy Lord and a World King!

It was at this step that countless martial artists were stranded forever, never able to make a breakthrough. It had to be known that even an ordinary World King had the talent of an Empyrean descendant!

“I’m just taking a look.” Old Xue laughed, accepting the greetings of these juniors.

Behind the counter, Suya brightened as she saw Old Xue, like a peony opening in the shining spring sun. She sweetly said, “Elder Xue, I’ve been here for so many days and there are many missions that I can’t seem to get completed… perhaps you could help me out a little.”

Suya’s voice was crisp and tender to the bone. If a girl heard it, it might seem a bit fake. But to a man, this was a lethal tone.

Even Old Xue’s beard shook as he heard this; it seemed he enjoyed the attention.

“You old pervert.” Xiao Moxian harshly denounced. Lin Ming chuckled at her response.

“I’m flattered, flattered. I’ll take a few missions since I’m here, but the main reason I came to the Mission Division is to introduce this boy to you…”

As Old Xue spoke he pointed towards Lin Ming. “He entered the Divine Runic Masters Guild 20 some years ago. He’s in a bit of a need for contribution points, so he’ll probably need to do a number of missions for you.”

As Old Xue introduced Lin Ming, Suya took a glance at his divine runic master badge. As a mere third grade divine runic master, she didn’t place him in her eyes.

She didn’t really want to bother speaking to such a young divine runic master, but since Old Xue introduced him she couldn’t ignore him.

“Raindrop, arrange a mission for him.”

Suya casually said. Beside her a well-behaved little girl took out a pile of mission scrolls and gave them to Lin Ming to look at.

Lin Ming looked over these missions scrolls. They were third grade missions and below. The rewards were several hundred points or even several dozen points; it was really small to the point of being pitiful.

“Do you have higher grade missions?”

Lin Ming asked. Suya was a bit taken aback. Lin Ming was a third grade divine runic master but he wanted to take on even higher grades of missions?

Old Xue wasn’t surprised at all. A monstrous freak like Lin Ming simply couldn’t be judged by common sense. He laughed, saying, “Since this boy wants to see them, take out some higher grade missions for him. Perhaps he has the ability to complete them.”

Although Suya thought otherwise, since it was Old Xue requesting this she had no choice but to act accordingly. “Raindrop, bring out some fourth and fifth grade missions.”

Raindrop picked out a number of mission scrolls, all of them at the fourth and fifth grade.

Lin Ming earnestly looked through every mission. He carefully analyzed them all, calculating which one had the potential for the most points.

“What an idiot…”

Behind Lin Ming, those several young divine runic masters mocked him without holding back. Of course, because Old Xue was present they could only speak to each other with sound transmission.

“This fellow’s courting tactics are… well, he’s got more guts than we do. We’re only at the level of trying to get closer to Miss Suya, but this idiot is trying to stir up a big fuss in front of her. We should study his techniques a little later…”

“I bet you he will take out several mission scrolls to bring back. It’s not like he will lose anything if he can’t complete them!”

As the several young divine runic masters spoke, Lin Ming indeed took out several mission scrolls.

These missions scrolls were all fourth grade, but they were also at the highest level of fourth grade missions. Compared to the rewards from fifth grade missions, the difference wasn’t that great.

Lin Ming meticulously looked through these mission scrolls. The more difficult a mission was, the more time it took, the higher the rewards would be.

As a fifth grade divine runic master, Lin Ming had the ability to complete fifth grade missions. But, he also had to calculate the time and energy he would need to invest into these fifth grade missions and after doing so he discovered that the reward to effort ratio wasn’t much higher.

As for these peak fourth grade missions, Lin Ming could rely on his skill and understanding of the Asura Heavenly Dao to rapidly complete them.

Lin Ming took out a total of five fourth grade missions scrolls and lined them up on the countertop.

Looking at the difficulty of these five mission scrolls, the several young divine runic masters present were left speechless.

“This boy, his skin is too thick!”

Putting on an act all depended on how thick one’s skin was. If one’s skin wasn’t thick enough there was no way they could fake things to such a degree. If they were in Lin Ming’s position there was no way they could pretend to peruse through such difficult missions.

These missions, all of them could only be completed by someone that was at least a peak fourth grade divine runic master!

“He’s forcing this too much. Only an idiot would think he could complete them, and Miss Suya isn’t stupid so how could she believe him?”

“That’s right, his acting is going to have the opposite effect now.”

As the several young divine runic masters spoke, they indeed saw Suya frown. If it weren’t for the fact that Lin Ming was brought here by Elder Xue, she would have already sent him tumbling out of the Mission Division.

She felt nothing but disgust for young men that liked to play such tricks.

“These missions, do you plan on completing them by yourself?”

Suya heatedly asked Lin Ming. Because the reward points given by the Divine Runic Masters Guild were directly placed into the divine runic masters badge, normally divine runic masters would come here in person to receive missions; they wouldn’t send representatives.

Lin Ming didn’t directly answer. Instead, he said, “If I’m taking a mission I naturally have some confidence I can complete it.”

“Haha…”

Suya faintly sneered. She felt that she had to put some restrictions on people who would appear at her counter in the future, lest some brain-addled idiots like this Lin Ming appear in front of her again.

“Raindrop, register these missions to him.” Suya coldly said. She would do things properly for Old Xue’s sake, but the truth was that she had already considered Lin Ming an idiot who was up to no good and had placed him on her personal blacklist.

Chapter 1601 - Havoc Flame Symbol

A Havoc Flame Symbol was formed from more than 800 tiny runes, and each tiny rune had its own profound structure.

In order to draw one up, one had to have excellent attainments in the divine runic arts and the divine runic master had to have a thorough understanding of the Fire Laws.

When the Havoc Flame Symbol was activated, it would erupt with an annihilating flame that could melt away mountains and evaporate rivers. This required that the divine runic master have an understanding of the Fire Laws that reached the sixth level Concept.

This was also another reason that Lin Ming chose the Havoc Flame Symbol. If he drew this symbol up then he would have a natural advantage over others because his Fire Laws already touched upon the seventh level Concept. Although he was inferior to Xiao Moxian, his understanding was still superior to that of most ordinary fire-attribute ordinary World Kings!

Lin Ming had originally inherited Torchriver’s memories, and with his extraordinary soul force, understanding of the Asura Heavenly Dao, and deep understanding of the Fire Laws, he was able to easily draw up the first Havoc Flame Symbol. After undergoing a few problems, Lin Ming quickly produced a successful result.

The palm-sized divine runic symbol in his hand had a warm atmosphere to it.

This Havoc Flame Symbol was already successfully drawn up and matched every standard. As long as Lin Ming could draw up 19 more than he could complete the mission.

But Lin Ming didn’t plan to do so.

Even if he completed the mission and obtained 50,000-60,000 contribution points then that was still meaningless. It was simply far too small a number.

He held onto the Havoc Flame Symbol and walked out of the divine runic symbol drawing room.

“Sir, may I help you?”

The young receptionist who had helped Lin Ming before bowed as she saw him, sweetly smiling. Towards this wealthy young divine runic master who also had outstanding looks, it was inevitable that a young girl like her would develop a good impression.

“I need an array formation to test the power of a divine runic symbol.”

“Of course.” The young receptionist smiled. “All divine runic masters that have rented our rooms may use our test array formation at no cost.”

The young receptionist led Lin Ming to another room. This room was completely sealed off and the walls and floor were all especially supported with array formations. In addition to the power of space locked in here, even a tremendously powerful divine runic symbol would find it hard to destroy this place.

The young girl pointed to a platform in the center. This was where the test array formation was.

Lin Ming took the Havoc Flame Symbol and stepped onto the platform. The young receptionist politely drew back. All divine runic masters were sensitive about their inheritances and kept them strictly confidential; it wasn’t good manners to look at their experiments.

As the young girl left, Lin Ming started the array formation.

This array formation was in itself an illusory magic array. When Lin Ming activated the array formation his surroundings changed and several ancient great desolate beasts appeared.

These great desolate beasts were simulations created by the array formation. As they appeared, they turned to Lin Ming and savagely roared as if they wanted to eat him whole.

Facing these vicious beasts, Lin Ming slowly lifted the Havoc Flame Symbol.

Flooding the Havoc Flame Symbol with his true essence, hundreds of tiny runes shimmered together. A destructive power erupted from the Havoc Flame Symbol and with an explosive sound the several ancient desolate beasts were swept up in the waves of flames, many of the beasts turning to ash.

Some were severely wounded, but some only suffered minor injuries. There was even one that wasn’t affected at all.

Hu - !

The illusory magic array vanished and all the ancient desolate beasts disappeared.

Lin Ming stepped down from the platform.

The light from the array disc flashed, producing an evaluation of Lin Ming’s divine runic symbol.

“Power: Holy Lord injury level, one star.”

Lin Ming had inherited the memories of three divine runic masters thus he naturally knew what this evaluation meant. A Holy Lord injury level evaluation meant that this Havoc Flame Symbol could heavily wound or even kill a Holy Lord level martial artist.

And Holy Lord level injuries were divided into five magnitudes. A Holy Lord one star was the worst magnitude possible.

“Only a Holy Lord one star… it’s a bit weak.”

Lin Ming shook his head, not too satisfied with this injury level. With his understanding of the seventh level Fire Laws, his strength as a fifth grade divine runic master, and also his comprehensions of the Asura Heavenly Dao, the divine runic symbol he drew up was only able to severely wound the weakest of Holy Lords. He wasn’t content with this result at all.

But, if any other divine runic masters were to hear Lin Ming’s thoughts now, all of them might die from vomiting blood.

In the domain of divine runic arts, a sixth grade divine runic master was equivalent to a World King, a fifth grade divine runic master was equivalent to a Holy Lord, and a fourth grade divine runic master was equivalent to a Divine Lord.

Lin Ming had drawn up a peak fourth grade divine runic symbol. Ordinarily this level should be able to heavily injure a late Divine Lord or wound a half-step Holy Lord.

But now it was already exaggerated that Lin Ming’s Havoc Flame Symbol had reached a Holy Lord one star injury level. Most importantly, this was the first time that Lin Ming had drawn it up!

How could anyone still live upon hearing this!

Lin Ming recalled that brilliant detonation of flames. In that explosion of flames, Lin Ming had carefully observed the entire process of how the energy within the Havoc Flame Symbol interacted with the Asura Heavenly Dao.

He discovered many places where the flow of energies didn’t harmonize.

The divine runic master who invented the Havoc Flame Symbol in the past simply didn’t understand the Asura Heavenly Dao. Rather, he had used his accumulated experiences to create the Havoc Flame Symbol. Now, to Lin Ming’s eyes, there were many holes in the process where the Havoc Flame Symbol had fused with the Asura Heavenly Dao.

If these holes were fixed then the Havoc Flame Symbol would undergo a massive transformation. As for what this transformation would end up like, Lin Ming wasn’t able to estimate it at all.

Lin Ming would have to finish patching all of these holes before he could further rend judgment.

With these thoughts in mind, Lin Ming stepped out of the test room. He didn’t even hear when the young receptionist greeted him; he had completely immersed himself in his own world.

After returning to his divine runic arts room, Lin Ming began the process of deduction.

He closed his eyes, meditating with the Asura Sutra in mind.

The Asura Sutra was the most current cultivation method of all the ones that Lin Ming possessed. Its grade was at least at the peak True Divinity realm, or possibly even surpassed the boundary of a True Divinity. Even though this cultivation method was still incomplete, the power behind it was incomprehensible!

To be more exact, describing the Asura Sutra as a cultivation method wasn’t wholly accurate.

The Asura Sutra should be called a set of Laws. These were Laws that the Asura Road Master created and stood outside the Laws of the 33 Heavens. It was the 34th Heavenly Dao Law that stood on equal footing with the Laws of the 33 Heavens.

The Asura Heavenly Dao was complex and difficult to understand. The innumerable patterns were ever-changing and impossibly complex! To repair the problems within the Havoc Flame Symbol would be easier said than done!

Lin Ming took out several dozen jade slips, recording all of his calculations within them.

It was impossible to write down the structural patterns of the Heavenly Dao Laws in a journal like mortals did. These different structural patterns had energy transformations that were complex to the extreme. All of these transformations needed to be felt with one’s sense, and then engraved onto a jade slip.

Like this, Lin Ming lost himself in deducing the Asura Heavenly Dao. He compared the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws with the tiny runes in the Havoc Flame Symbol, modifying all the areas that were in disharmony.

From time to time, Lin Ming needed to use materials to draw up tiny runes and test the effects of the modifications.

But in most situations, there would be new problems with the modifications Lin Ming made. Sometimes the entire structure of tiny runes would collapse due to the instability of the energy!

To make these sorts of deductions was far too much work!

Lin Ming’s current understanding of the Asura Heavenly Dao, when compared to other divine runic masters’, could be called the difference between clouds and mud.

But compared to the entire Asura Heavenly Dao, what Lin Ming understood was only the tip of the iceberg; he was far from being sufficient!

This also caused many new problems to occur as Lin Ming was modifying the Havoc Flame Symbol. His understanding of the Laws was too lacking.

Peng!

Another brilliant burst of flames appeared in front of Lin Ming. The several dozen tiny runes he drew up exploded, indicating that new problems occurred in the revisions Lin Ming had just made.

This situation had already occurred countless times. The results that he had carefully calculated again and again were proven wrong during experimentation and had to be redone once more. This sort of frustration couldn’t be tolerated by most people.

However, Lin Ming’s patience and stubbornness far surpassed that of others.

With every wrong calculation he would begin anew, making deduction after deduction until he made it right.

Like this, Lin Ming made deductions through the day and night. He had already achieved a wholly absorbed state, not eating food or drinking any water. It was only when Lin Ming completely exhausted his soul force that he stopped. Then, he revolved the Divine Mist Heart Mantra, restoring his soul force and beginning once again. Soon, ten days passed in an instant…

Chapter 1606 – Power of the Flame Symbols

A divine runic symbol was originally a one-time use consumable item. Once it was used up it was gone. No one had ever heard of a divine runic symbol that would not disappear after being used and would instead be restored to its original state!

The two divine runic symbols floated back into Crimson Cloud’s hand as if they had a mind of their own. After entering his hand, besides a warm and comfortable feeling that surrounded them, everything was the exact same as before he had used them.

If he didn’t watch the inner sea being swept up in a terrifying explosion of flames and didn’t see the two saint martial artists being scorched black, Crimson Cloud would really wonder whether or not he had used these Havoc Flame Symbols just now.

“Can these Havoc Flame Symbols actually be used multiple times?”

As soon as this thought flashed through Crimson Cloud’s mind he nearly couldn’t believe it himself.

Divine runic symbols were one-time use objects just like pills. He had never heard about a pill being eaten, reforming, and then being able to be eaten again. That completely defied all common sense logic!

“This fellow!”

Those two saint martial artists that were burnt by the destructive flames also saw the divine runic symbols used by Crimson Cloud restore themselves to their original appearance after being used.

The saint martial artists were panic-stricken. Just what was going on here? If a divine runic symbol could be used multiple times, was that even allowed!?

Seeing Crimson Cloud hold those two divine runic symbols in hand, the saint martial artists were already deeply afraid. They didn’t dare to attack.

But at this time, another martial artist sneered. “He’s just bluffing. If that spiritas dog was able to use divine runic symbols multiple times then our Heaven Strife Holy Lands would have been long destroyed by their Extreme Star Holy Lands!”

“That’s right! I can’t believe I was almost fooled.” The two saint martial artists grimaced as they mocked themselves for their stupidity. If this Crimson Cloud fellow really had such fierce divine runic symbols then why would he only use them after one of his arms was cut off? He would have used them at the start!

If so, then the two of them together wouldn’t have been able to defeat him.

“Attack together, kill him!”

“This spiritas dog, he dares to trick me? I will tear off that dog head of his!”

The two saint martial artists launched their attacks once more. Last time they had defended with everything they had, but now they were attacking with everything they had!

Seeing those two masters hurtle towards him, Crimson Cloud grit his teeth and activated the Havoc Flame Symbols once more!

In a hopeless situation he still had to try everything he could. At this time, his only hope of survival was that these two Havoc Flame Symbols could actually be used multiple times. Otherwise, he was as good as dead!

Pouring his spirit essence into the Havoc Flame Symbols, Crimson Cloud felt as if they had been insatiably hungry, crazily sucking up his spirit essence!

Although Crimson Cloud had lost an arm, the truth was that he hadn’t used up too much of his spirit essence. Even after these two Havoc Flame Symbols wildly drew out his spirit essence, he still had over half remaining.

“What is this…”

Crimson Cloud was startled by the Havoc Flame Symbols drawing out so much of his spirit essence. When he had used peak fourth grade divine runic symbols in the past, although he had to pour in his spirit essence, he had never poured in this much!

This sort of feeling was like the two Havoc Flame Symbols in his hand were a bottomless abyss, recklessly sucking out his strength.

Crimson Cloud had no time to respond. At this moment, the two Havoc Flame Symbols flew out, releasing a blazing light in the skies.

The surrounding heaven and earth origin energy began moving like a tsunami, gathering together and condensing into a raging sea of flames in the skies. And in the midst of this sea of flames, the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws wove together with the mysterious dao patterns. Beneath the influence of these dao patterns, the sea of flames gained a horrifying destructive aura, as if they would burn through space!

The two saint martial artists that were rushing forwards were instantly surrounded by this turbulent sea of fire!

“What!?”

No matter what, the two saint martial artists would never have imagined that those two divine runic symbols could be used multiple times. If this Crimson Cloud really had such divine runic symbols then why didn’t he use them earlier? Why wait until now!?

They had no time to think. That ghastly sea of black flames contained a terrifying destructive aura. As they were sucked into the center of it, their astral essence quickly consumed itself.

The power when these Havoc Flame Symbols were used again even far surpassed the first time!

Peng!

One saint martial artist’s protective astral essence was burnt to nothing! He cried out in alarm as he faced the roiling black flames alone, nearly scared out of his mind.

He had already been severely wounded by the first use of the Havoc Flame Symbol; how could his body endure it a second time?

“How could this happen!”

All across the battlefield, the other martial artists also noticed the situation happening here. Two seas of flames had appeared and their reckless surges of energy were wildly rushing out, colliding with everyone else.

“This is… Havoc Flame Symbols!?”

Dunepeak’s squad was stunned. According to traditional concepts, divine runic symbols should only be used at the last moments of a desperate struggle in order to display the best effects. Thus, besides the almost-dead Crimson Cloud, no one had used them.

With a pitiful scream, that saint martial artist whose protective astral essence shattered first was swept up by the black flames! The destructive power within those black flames broke into his body, ravaging through his meridians and recklessly destroying everything!

Those black flames could burn astral essence and were impossibly difficult to suppress!

The saint martial artist frantically struggled but his life vitality was rapidly fading!

“Captain!” Crimson Cloud suddenly shouted out, “Let’s use our Havoc Flame Symbols together!”

He didn’t know whether or not all the Havoc Flame Symbols could be used multiple times, but this was the only gamble he could make!

If he was right then they could make all their opponents suffer severe wounds without paying too great a price!

Hearing Crimson Cloud’s shouts, the other martial artists in Dunepeak’s squad were all stunned. At this time, they witnessed something incredible.

The Asura Heavenly Dao Laws that formed the terrifying sea of fire suddenly converged in the air, turning into two new flame symbols that flew into Crimson Cloud’s hand.

“What in the world!?” Dunepeak’s squad felt this was all too unbelievable. After these Havoc Flame Symbols were used they actually restored themselves to their previous state!

Without further speaking, Dunepeak took out his own two Havoc Flame Symbols. He didn’t know whether these two flame symbols could be used more than once but this was his only hope!

All the other martial artists in Dunepeak’s squad followed suit, bringing out their Havoc Flame Symbols.

In an instant, the entire sky was lit up with an endless panorama of black flames.

Because of these flames, the vast inner sea seemed to boil with excitement…

……

After Lin Ming handed over the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols he bought a massive amount of materials and returned to his divine runic arts room to practice.

Lin Ming was only practicing one thing: revising the structure of the divine runic symbols so that they drew even closer to the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws. This would allow their strength to greatly increase or they could even be like the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols and obtain an unbelievable special effect.

Only this type of divine runic symbol would sell for a sky-high price.

The Havoc Flame Symbol that Lin Ming revised was only a peak fourth grade divine runic symbol. Although its effects were heaven-defying, Lin Ming still remained unsatisfied.

Because the grade of the divine runic symbol wasn’t too high, only an Empyrean level influence like the Extreme Star Holy Lands that was also at war with another party would purchase them in bulk. Otherwise, selling them off one at a time would be far too slow a method to gather wealth.

Lin Ming’s goal was to revise a fifth grade divine runic symbol!

This was a gargantuan project. The revision of a fifth grade divine runic symbol was several times more difficult than that of a fourth grade divine runic symbol!

Even though Lin Ming had some previous experiences, he would still struggle with it.

Lin Ming secluded himself in his divine runic arts room and restarted the days of neglecting to eat and sleep.

A massive amount of materials was placed atop the divine runic table. Jade slips were haphazardly scattered everywhere as he made new calculations and deductions every night.

Making countless calculations all day long was an extremely arduous and tedious process. Luckily, Xiao Moxian would frequently make soul recovery soups and bring them to him, relieving his boredom and making him feel a hint of pleasure and concern.

But, Lin Ming was well aware that the revision of a fifth grade divine runic symbol could not be accomplished in one go like with a fourth grade divine runic symbol. Rather, the process was divided into multiple stages and each stage only represented a part.

What Lin Ming studied now was only the theoretical basis behind it.

If Lin Ming didn’t have any inspirations, he would find something else to do.

And of these other things, the most important was to refine a soul recovery pill for Empyrean Divine Mist.

A soul recovery pill that could help an Empyrean would have a grade close to a transcendent divine pill. It would be extremely difficult to refine.

At least, this was with Lin Ming’s current level.

Time passed a day at a time. In the blink of an eye, 20 days had passed since Lin Ming handed in his mission.

At the front lines of the Extreme Star Holy Lands, ten Holy Lord level squads were gathered together. The 100 plus people were called here to hold a war assembly.

This sort of war assembly would occur every month. Everyone would freely exchange information. This included information they obtained on enemies, fighting tactics, and new adaptations to make on the battlefield.

At this time, in a corner of the assembly, a tall and majestic man was standing there. This big fellow had a long beard and a pair of large axes hanging on his back. He was currently beaming with joy!

“I’m not exaggerating! You have no idea what the scene was like at the time! There were over 21 opponents and also two late Holy Lords leading them! As for us, we only had 10 people; this was a completely one-sided match! And, those saint demons even laid traps for us. With an order from the captain we engaged them in a brutal struggle for survival. That battle was truly world-shaking, enough to shock gods and alarm ghosts!

The big fellow was speaking so fast and excitedly that his beard was flying up. Then, a strong hand slapped his back and an icy voice sounded out. “Sit down and stop making things up!”

After being yelled at the big bearded fellow wasn’t feeling too good. But as he turned around, he saw the one standing behind him was his captain – Dunepeak.

The bearded fellow immediately shut up. He said, “Captain, I’m just telling the truth… where am I making things up…”

“Good. Then shut up.”

Even though Dunepeak had earned a massive merit he still couldn’t be happy about this war assembly. He knew that he couldn’t conceal his combat report, otherwise that would be a grave and oftentimes fatal offense. But, he still had a single worry. That was… once he gave his report, would the strange Havoc Flame Symbols in their hands be confiscated by the higher powers?

Before this, he had learned through other channels that it was only his squad’s Havoc Flame Symbols that had special effects; the divine runic symbols of the other squads were the same as before and could only be used once.

Chapter 1607 – “Lin”

At this time, a large middle-aged man stepped into the center of the assembly site. This person had thick eyebrows, eyes like a tiger, and an intimidating aura. He was an Empyrean disciple from Extreme Star Heavenly Palace, a Great World King powerhouse – Deep Blue.

These 10 Holy Lord squads were under Deep Blue’s direct jurisdiction and he was also the one presiding over this assembly.

As he stepped into the assembly site, Deep Blue spoke a few opening remarks before looking at Dunepeak. He went straight to the point, “Dunepeak, in your combat report you said that your team achieved a great success. You fell into an ambush of 21 enemies that even had two captain-level characters but instead of being killed you slayed 13 people and forced the remaining eight to flee into the wild. As for your squad, the only price you paid was some wounds?”

Although Deep Blue seemed to have a happy expression, his eyes were like a hawk as he looked over Dunepeak’s squad of 10.

After being praised by Deep Blue in the war assembly, Dunepeak and his squad felt proud of their accomplishments. Indeed, they had truly won a great victory in that battle and had fought with vigor!

However, Dunepeak’s mind was still filled with doubts. 20 Havoc Flame Symbols were given to their squad of 10; would the other 10 be taken back? He clenched his teeth, “Yes!”

“Mm, good, you earned merits, great merits. All of you may receive rewards in accordance with army regulations!” Deep Blue said. The martial artists in Dunepeak’s squad were increasingly excited.

But at this time, Deep Blue changed the conversation. “Then… I want to know, how did you win?”

Dunepeak’s mind shook. The subject had finally been brought up!

As he expected, when headquarters provided those Havoc Flame symbols they didn’t know about their special effects.

Dunepeak took a deep breath and took out the combat report he had prepared long in advance.

He stepped forwards and bowed, saying, “Lord Deep Blue, I have already prepared the combat report. This combat report may have a considerable influence on the war. But, before Lord Deep Blue takes a look, I have a request to make.”

“Oh? Request?”

“Yes!” Dunepeak had a serious expression. “I request that in any event, Lord Deep Blue does not take back military equipment!”

“Why would I take back your military equipment?” Deep Blue’s eyebrows shot up. He could faintly feel that Dunepeak’s combat report was related to this equipment.

He hesitated for a moment before saying, “As long as it is equipment issued by the military I naturally won’t take it back.”

“Thank you Lord Deep Blue.” Dunepeak said, ecstatic. If Deep Blue guaranteed this under the eyes of so many people present then he wouldn’t renege on his words.

Dunepeak immediately passed over the combat report and began speaking. He could give up the rewards from this merit but he definitely had to keep those 20 Havoc Flame Symbols no matter what. This was a matter that concerned his life and the lives of his brothers!

As Deep Blue listened to the combat report, his expression was calm, then startled, then filled with disbelief. At the end, he rose to his feet, unable to contain his surprise!

His eyes were filled with excitement. He looked at Dunepeak with disbelief. “Havoc Flame Symbols that can be used multiple times? Are you speaking the truth?”

Deep Blue’s voice was filled with potent energy. It spread through the entire war assembly. For a time, the entire assembly site fell into complete silence.

Everyone could clearly hear Deep Blue’s words.

Havoc Flame Symbols that could be used more than once? This kind of divine runic symbol existed in the world?

Divine runic symbols were powerful but their creation costs were astronomical. They could only be used once. A martial artist normally had two or three divine runic symbols to protect themselves and they would only be willing to take them out in critical situations. They were treated like hidden treasures.

If there was a Havoc Flame Symbol that could be used unlimited times, just what sort of scene was that? If there was a squad where each person had a Havoc Flame Symbol, wouldn’t that be a violent and random barrage of explosions? There was no opponent who could withstand that!

This sounded unrealistic, but Dunepeak’s squad had defeated an enemy force twice their size and hadn’t lost a single person. This was the best proof!

As the members of the other squads realized this, their eyes began to burn with heat.

Such a divine tool of the battlefield, they also wanted one!

………..

Late at night, Divine Runic Masters Guild –

At night, the Mission Division of the Divine Runic Masters Guild would be extremely lonely and desolate. But no matter how lonely it was, Suya would not leave her position.

For 24 hours a day, whether it was eating, meditating, or occasionally cultivating, Suya would spend her time here.

In this alone, Suya was extremely devoted to her work. At any time, anyone could find her if they wished.

Of course, the reason for this was also due to the tremendous pressure on her.

At this time, Suya was dressed in a loose pink nightdress. She sat behind the counter, taking inventory of the divine runic symbols she had.

In truth, she had taken inventory too many times so it was impossible for her to have made a mistake. But she still did so because it was a habit of hers.

The reason this habit developed was because Suya was feeling extremely restless in her heart.

Of the time that Extreme Star Heavenly Palace had given her to complete her mission, a quarter had passed.

However, she had only received 9000 fourth grade divine runic symbols and 1500 fifth grade divine runic symbols.

But the mission that headquarters had given her was to gather 80,000 fourth grade divine runic symbols and 10,000 fifth grade divine runic symbols!

The disparity was far too great.

The divine runic masters weren’t too enthusiastic about taking on missions.

These people were extremely arrogant to begin with. Besides missions, they also had to cultivate, study, and research.

The soaring cost of materials had unknowingly increased the difficulty for divine runic masters to complete their missions. After all, if a divine runic master failed to draw up a symbol they would have to pay for the materials lost.

If things continued at this speed, Suya wouldn’t even have half the amount of divine runic symbols needed when the deadline for her mission came!

What should she do?

Suya’s advantage lay in her feminine charms.

But, those that prostrated themselves beneath her pink dress were mostly young divine runic masters without much skill. In Suya’s eyes, they were even worse than Lin Ming.

A true higher level divine runic master wasn’t necessarily attracted by Suya’s feminine charms and wiles.

In recent days, Suya had smiled towards these high level divine runic masters every day, trying to arouse their interest; she was beginning to feel a bit exhausted by this work.

Playing with the cup of red wine in her hands, Suya’s heart was not as calm as she revealed on the outside.

“Young Lady, the Heavenly Palace has passed down orders.”

At this time, Raindrop approached and took out a golden token with both hands.

“Another Extreme Star Command!” Suya’s heart skipped a beat. Every time she saw an Extreme Star Command, she would have an unlucky foreboding feeling.

With a deep breath, Suya swept through the contents of the Extreme Star Command with her sense. For a time, she was shocked.

“A divine runic symbol that could be used countless times? There was such a strange divine runic symbol in the ones I delivered?”

Suya also had some attainments in the divine runic arts, otherwise she wouldn’t have been sent here to the Divine Runic Masters Guild. She was well aware that it was an impossible matter for divine runic symbols to be used multiple times.

But, headquarters wouldn’t lie about something so important. Perhaps there really was someone who invented a divine runic symbol that could be used many times!

“Who is it?”

The first people Suya thought of were the peak divine runic grandmasters of the Divine Runic Masters Guild, and even the Guild President, a seventh level divine runic master!

But, none of these people seemed to have taken a mission from the Extreme Star Holy Lands. With their status they wouldn’t bother with such things…

“Could it be a peak sixth grade divine runic master?” Suya immediately thought. There were some sixth grade divine runic masters that had taken on missions.

But as she thought about it more she soon shot down this idea. Within the Extreme Star Command, there was a phantom image of the divine runic symbol which could be used multiple times. Suya could immediately see that it was a fourth grade divine runic symbol – a Havoc Flame Symbol.

A sixth grade divine runic master wouldn’t take on a mission to create Havoc Flame Symbols.

“Havoc Flame Symbol…”

Suya had a good memory and she could recall that there were people who took on missions to draw up Havoc Flame Symbols these days.

But as she recalled this, she knew there were only five or six people who had taken on missions to draw up Havoc Flame Symbols. Of these people, there wasn’t anyone who was capable of accomplishing such an unbelievable matter!

“It shouldn’t be him…”

Suya inexplicably thought of Lin Ming but she immediately shook her head. She was being too ridiculous here. Just how old was Lin Ming? He was less than a hundred years old and his divine runic master rank was only the third grade if she remembered correctly.

But as Suya was thinking this, the expression on her face froze.

She subconsciously covered her mouth.

On the phantom image of that Havoc Flame Symbol, there was a clear character carved onto the bottom right corner of the divine runic symbol – ‘Lin’!

“Lin? Could it… really be him!?”

Realizing this possibility, Suya was completely stunned.

Chapter 1608 – Late Night Suya

“You would like to look for Lin Ming? Miss Suya, please wait a moment, I will check for you…”

In the divine runic room rental area, a young receptionist in a long skirt smiled sweetly as she looked up Lin Ming’s room number for Suya.

“Fifth grade divine runic room, Room #28.”

The young receptionist continued, “It is late at night so Sir Lin is probably resting at this moment. Miss Suya, do you plan on visiting Sir Lin?”

“Yes.” Suya nodded.

The young receptionist tittered. Suya was the most eye-catching beauty in the Divine Runic Masters Guild this year. In the middle of the night she wore such a sensual pink nightdress to enter Lin Ming’s room alone, just what could she be planning?

This sort of meeting would always cause young girls to form interesting associations.

Of course, she naturally couldn’t reveal these ideas.

Seeing the strange glint in the young receptionist’s eyes, Suya certainly knew what she was thinking. But, she was disinclined to care about such things.

At this time her mind was a mess. She didn’t know whether or not that Havoc Flame Symbol really came from Lin Ming and how she should face him.

In Suya’s memories, there weren’t many people within the entire Divine Runic Masters Guild who had the surname of Lin. This was because while this name was relatively common within the human race, there were very, very few people of the soul race who had such a name.

If a spiritas divine runic master were to create their own divine runic symbol, there would be no reason for randomly putting the ‘Lin’ character on a corner of the divine runic symbol.

However, this third grade divine runic master was far too young. How could he possibly produce such a ridiculous divine runic symbol?

All of these thoughts raced through Suya’s mind. Soon, she reached Room #28.

Lin Ming’s contribution points were non-existent. This also meant that he couldn’t rent a room that required contribution points.

Looking at the tightly sealed stone door, Suya’s mood was extremely complex. She hesitantly reached out a hand and pressed down on the sound transmission array formation……..

……

At this time, within the divine runic room, materials were scattered chaotically everywhere. There were also many incomplete divine runic symbols.

But above a stone bed in a corner of the room, a beautiful spring scene was taking place.

After delivering the Havoc Flame Symbols and completing his mission, Lin Ming painstakingly researched in this room for a month and finally came up with a way to transform a fifth grade divine runic symbol.

Today, Lin Ming had completed the preliminary theoretical basis and this part of his work had come to an end. Then, he and Xiao Moxian began to dual cultivate Heavenly Extreme Bliss together.

But at this time, Lin Ming heard a sound transmitted from the array formation at the front door; someone was knocking on his door.

“Mm? Who would come looking for me at this time?”

Lin Ming frowned. Normally speaking, when a divine runic master entered their divine runic room they would spend most of their time in deep concentration. It wasn’t polite to suddenly bother them.

Moreover, it was late at night so this was even more impolite.

“Who’s here?”

Xiao Moxian’s face was blushed her. She grabbed her night clothes from a nearby counter and covered her perfectly shaped body. She had come to Lin Ming’s room many times and there had never been a visitor before.

“I have no idea.”

Lin Ming stood up, dressed himself, and walked over to open the front door.

With a creaking sound the stone door opened and the alluring figure of a sexy beauty stood on the other side. Lin Ming was stunned for a moment.

“Sir Lin.” Although Suya felt that this situation was extremely awkward and embarrassing, she still revealed a charming smile. At this time, Suya wore a light pink nightdress that exposed a blinding amount of snow-white skin. Her plunging neckline was so deep that it exposed the top of her gauzy negligee and one could make out her exquisite thighs and curves. To appear at night with such seductive clothing, most men would feel their blood boiling by now.

“So it’s Miss Suya.”

Lin Ming could approximately guess what Suya came here for but he didn’t reveal any of his thoughts. He simply stood at the entrance and asked with a smile, “What is Miss Suya here for?”

Sensing Lin Ming’s not quite welcoming smile, Suya thought little of it. Instead, she cast him a charming look and said in a soft and breathy voice, “Sir Lin, will you not ask me to enter?”

To ask such a question at such a time and place with these clothes and with such an alluring tone, there was no man that would refuse her.

However, Suya never thought that at this time, a young woman’s voice would echo out in response, “It’s not too convenient for you to come in now.”

Following this voice, a black-clothed young woman walked out from behind Lin Ming, a playful smile hanging on her voice. She said in a whimsical tone, “Oh, isn’t it Miss Suya? What, why are you here so late? Are you looking for my Lin Ming for some reason?”

Xiao Moxian emphasized the words ‘my Lin Ming’, clearly demonstrating a taste of her power here.

Seeing Xiao Moxian, Suya’s smile froze. She didn’t think that Xiao Moxian would also be here. Moreover, with the faint blush that was covering Xiao Moxian’s face as well as the light scent coming from the room, Suya could already guess what was happening inside.

This left Suya speechless. What sort of coincidence was this?

In ordinary times, with Suya’s pride, she would have already turned and left upon seeing such a scene. But, today was her unlucky day. With the Extreme Star Command pushing down on her she had to obtain an answer as soon as possible. The fires of war that blazed on the frontlines would not wait for her.

She barely managed to maintain her smiling face as she said, “Oh, isn’t it Miss Xian’er? The last time I saw you I felt that Xian’er’s looks and beauty were astonishing. You truly left a deep impression on me!”

Suya was overjoyed that she remembered Xiao Moxian’s name from somewhere, otherwise things would have been even more awkward.

However, Xiao Moxian remained indignant, clearly not falling for Suya’s words. She carelessly said, “I truly admire Miss Suya’s loquacious ability to communicate. For Miss Suya to say such fake words, it’s as if our last meeting had a happy ending. On another note, would it trouble you to not call me Xian’er? I’m not too familiar with you and hearing you call me that is quite disgusting for me, and embarrassing for you.”

As Xiao Moxian spoke, she looked down to stare at the proud twin peaks that were exposed through Suya’s flimsy garments. She chuckled and said, “I’ve already heard rumors that many young divine runic masters in the Divine Runic Masters Guild were enthralled by Miss Suya to the point of being crazed idiots, but now that I see it for myself it seems that these rumors weren’t an exaggeration. For you to come to a man’s room alone in the middle of the night and with such an appearance, do you think this is appropriate?”

Hearing Xiao Moxian’s cynical mocking, Suya was nearly angered to death. Just what sort of character was Suya? She had been revered for so many years and yet today she was being taunted by some young girl and her only choice was to respond with a smile.

“It seems that Miss Xian’er had some misunderstandings about me. If there was any place where I offended you before, then I, Suya, respectfully apologize to Miss Xian’er for any mistakes I made in the past.”

Suya had already made a full gesture of defeat and Xiao Moxian had no intention of beating up someone that had already fallen to the ground. She smirked and said, “What matters do you have with my Lin Ming tonight?”

The truth was that Xiao Moxian also approximately guessed what was happening. She certainly didn’t believe that Suya came in the middle of the night to have some sexual rendezvous with Lin Ming, but knew it was because of those Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols. It would be impossible for this Suya woman to seduce Lin Ming tonight, especially with her here.

“It’s a good thing I was here tonight, otherwise only the heavens would know what this succubus would have done.” Xiao Moxian thought, her lips curving up in a pleased smile.

Seeing the two women quarrelling, Lin Ming awkwardly coughed and said, “Miss Suya, please come in and take a seat.”

Although Lin Ming didn’t have any good impression towards this overly proud and arrogant woman, he still needed to go through her to earn contribution points.

Lin Ming’s words finally resolved Suya’s problem.

Suya looked at Lin Ming with gratefulness and then entered the room.

Lin Ming’s room was extremely messy. There were materials piled up and scattered all over with symbol papers thrown about. There was also a large pile of jade slips used for calculations and deductions.

The clean and orderly Xiao Moxian originally couldn’t stand this chaotic mess. However, she tried not to move these scattered things unless absolutely necessary so she didn’t affect Lin Ming’s research.

To invite a guest into such a messy room was extremely disgraceful to begin with. If a beautiful woman were to come in, she would likely frown and possibly leave.

However, as Suya saw this cluttered room and the messy divine runic table, her eyes brightened with a dazzling light!

She was also a divine runic master so she knew what the mess on the divine runic table meant. All of those failed symbol papers and haphazardly placed jade slips meant that Lin Ming was researching something!

When a divine runic master did research they would often consume a massive amount of materials. As for the deductions, they would be written on jade slips. Looking at the divine runic table, there were at least 50-60 jade slips piled atop it.

These specialized jade slips had an enormous storing capacity. If a massive mortal encyclopedia was stored into a single jade slip it wouldn’t even account for the tip of an iceberg.

Suya found it hard to imagine just how many calculations and deductions Lin Ming had made in these past days. Could the improvements of the Havoc Flame Symbol have been done by Lin Ming alone?

“Sir Lin is truly hardworking… no wonder you would have such proud results at such a young age.” Suya smiled as she looked at the divine runic symbols and jade slips on the divine runic table. The more she looked, the more startled she was. The failed divine runic symbols were all fifth grade divine runic symbols! Just what was Lin Ming doing? Could he actually be thinking of improving a fifth grade divine runic symbol? Had he gone mad?

These thoughts instantly flashed through Suya’s mind, making her even more startled. She felt she had to completely reassess the value of this young man before her.

“Miss Suya, please speak openly if you have any matters to discuss.” Lin Ming said, going straight to the point.

“Alright, then I won’t beat around the bush. Sir Lin, I want to ask you, did the 20 Havoc Flame Symbols you turned in for your mission have Sir Lin’s surname inscribed onto the bottom right corner?”

As Suya asked, although her expression was tranquil her breathing was heavy.

Suya’s question was well within Lin Ming’s anticipation. He indifferently nodded and said, “That’s right. Did the Extreme Star Holy Lands use those divine runic symbols well?”

Although Suya already had some guesses in her heart, she still held her breath upon hearing Lin Ming’s answer. She felt her heartbeat quicken. Yes, it was really him!

To revise the Havoc Flame Symbol that had been inherited for so many years to such a degree, how had he done it!?

“Yes, they did...”

As Suya spoke, stormy waves were set off in her heart. It wasn’t just her, but even the entire army was in uproar. There were countless squads that were clamoring to obtain a single one of these divine runic symbols!

Chapter 1609 – Cooperation

Lin Ming wasn’t surprised by Suya’s sudden change in expression.

He flicked his hand and took out the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol that he had placed in his spatial ring.

At the time, Lin Ming had created 21 flame symbols and delivered 20 of them.

“Are you speaking of this?”

Lin Ming placed the flame symbol on the divine runic table. Just saying that he was the creator of those divine runic symbols wouldn’t be enough to win trust; taking out evidence would be more persuasive.

Seeing this divine runic symbol, Suya’s eyes lit up. This was it!

This Havoc Flame Symbol seemed like it was no different from ordinary Havoc Flame Symbols, but it had the terrifying property of being able to be used multiple times. With that property, it became a divine tool for the battlefield!

If a small squad of 10 people was provided with a Havoc Flame Symbol, just what sort of battles would be possible?

With a massive fiery bombardment at the start, the opponent would definitely be left miserable by the opening salvo. Then, they would be encircled and barraged with martial skills and flame symbols; just who could live through that?

Suya took the Havoc Flame Symbol and touched a slender finger to the bottom right corner where the ‘Lin’ character was located.

The sharp strokes of the character were like swords, startling Suya.

These strokes were exactly the same!

She looked up, staring at Lin Ming. A strange feeling percolated in her heart.

Just what kind of man was this?

When Lin Ming had first accepted the mission to draw up the Havoc Flame Symbols, Suya thought that he was only pretending to be able to do so in order to attract her attention. She never would have dreamed that not only would Lin Ming complete the mission but he would also improve the Havoc Flame Symbol!

She wasn’t sure if Lin Ming had made these improvements himself, but she didn’t have to be a genius to know that after improving the Havoc Flame Symbol, the difficulty would be far higher. Even so, he had still managed to complete them!

“He’s likely less than 100 years old…” Suya felt all of this to be too incomprehensible. Lin Ming was too abnormal. Let alone a junior that was less than 100 years old, even the higher level divine runic masters would be unable to accomplish something so heaven-defying.

In the quiet divine runic room, Lin Ming sat behind the divine runic table, holding absolute initiative.

And facing this Lin Ming that could be called a little brother from a younger generation, Suya had no idea what to say.

“He already expected I would come here to look for him!” Suya immediately thought. As she saw Lin Ming having no intention to speak at all, she finally began to become aware of what he was thinking. Did he want her to speak first? In these types of negotiations, the first to speak would be the one to lose the initiative.

However, against Lin Ming who had such skills, what advantage did Suya have?

Strength was momentum!

Suya had no way to maintain her previous pride and confidence. To Lin Ming, she could only reveal a flattering smile. She said, “Sir Lin, was that batch of divine runic symbols created by you?”

“Yes.” Lin Ming had nothing to hide and this matter couldn’t be concealed anyways.

So it was true…

Suya wasn’t surprised. She immediately began to consider how to offer conditions to have Lin Ming cooperate with her. But as she thought about her haughty manner the last time she saw Lin Ming as well as the dispute she had with Xiao Moxian, Suya really wanted to kick a wall.

She had simply cursed herself to death, otherwise why would she need to be so humble and submissive today?

“These changes were also completed by Sir Lin alone?” Suya asked.

“The changes were made by me. The reason I was able to do so is because the inheritance I study is special.”

Inheritance?

Suya’s heart skipped a beat. According to Elder Xue, it seemed that Lin Ming had an extremely powerful master.

What was this inheritance that it could cause such abnormal transformation?

Even a seventh grade divine runic master was absolutely unable to accomplish this.

Suya felt her mood become increasingly unsteady. This Lin Ming was an extraordinary treasure! Whether it was for the Extreme Star Holy Lands or the Divine Runic Masters Guild, it was the same!

She couldn’t help but ask, “I do not know who Sir Lin’s honorable master is…”

Lin Ming frowned upon hearing this. His voice became much colder as he said, “Miss Suya should also know that every divine runic master has their own inheritance, and the core techniques are something that the master might not even pass down to their apprentice. Is Miss Suya asking this question because you intend to make a secret attack on my inheritances?”

Lin Ming immediately buckled down, causing Suya to stumble. She said, “I apologize Sir Lin, I was rude. The reason I am here today is to represent headquarters, which wishes to discuss cooperation with Sir Lin…”

Suya paid careful attention to Lin Ming’s expressions. Speaking with Lin Ming, Suya was being extremely careful. After all, because of her arrogance the last time she spoke with Lin Ming, it would be hard to get along well with him quickly.

Seeing Lin Ming not intending to respond, Suya continued to ask. “Sir Lin, may I ask you how many times the Havoc Flame Symbols you created can be used?”

The truth was that when Suya received the Extreme Star Command, Extreme Star Heavenly Palace had already done some experiments on their own. Suya only needed to obtain Lin Ming’s confirmation as to whether or not every divine runic symbol could reach the same standard.

“They can probably be used several hundred times. After being used too many times the divine rune structure will slowly collapse and be destroyed.

“And in a single battle, this type of divine runic symbol can be activated four times at most. Moreover, the last three times need the martial artist to pour in a certain amount of energy. After using the divine runic symbol four times the energy within will be exhausted and unable to activate. The divine runic symbol has to charge itself for a period of time before it can be used again.”

When Lin Ming created the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol, because he had used nirvanic fire and heavenly tribulation fire, this caused the flame energy to be too high. When combined with the many modifications of the Asura Heavenly Dao that Lin Ming had added on, this made the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol extremely powerful, to the point that it could kill a peak Holy Lord.

But at the same time, the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol placed high requirements on the user. According to Lin Ming’s estimates, one needed to be a peak Holy Lord to draw out its full strength.

Thus, Lin Ming also made another modification. Using his understanding of the Asura Heavenly Dao, he made it so that the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol released its energy in bursts, greatly extending the lifetime use of the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol as well as reducing the requirements for the user.

Lin Ming’s data was all similar to the data that Extreme Star Heavenly Palace themselves had gained through testing.

This sort of Havoc Flame Symbol had been given the price of 400,000 points for a single one. This was also the ideal price that Extreme Star Heavenly Palace wished for.

And in fact, when Extreme Star Heavenly Palace issued a mission they would request 20 symbols. In other words, Extreme Star Heavenly Palace would have to pay Lin Ming 8 million points every time.

Suya hesitated and said, “Sir Lin, the Extreme Star Holy Lands would like one batch of these improved Havoc Flame Symbols. No matter how many we will take that many and we will also pay you sufficient rewards.”

“Oh?” Lin Ming traced his chin. He had already expected this type of mission commission. Currently, the Extreme Star Holy Lands lacked offensive and defensive divine runic symbols. As for pills, they were less pressured for those.

“Before we speak about this commission, what about the previous account?”

Lin Ming had a smile on his face. But, his words left Suya stunned.

The previous account…

That’s right, Lin Ming was still owed for the 20 Havoc Flame Symbols he handed over last time!

Suya had wanted to pay 60,000 contribution points but Lin Ming didn’t want that at all. He said that he didn’t ‘lack contribution points’.

It was only now that Suya realized why Lin Ming didn’t need contribution points. He thought that 60,000 points was too little and was waiting for this development to occur so he could demand a higher reward!

Suya also remembered that Lin Ming had said that perhaps after a month, his total amount of points would reach a considerable number.

Lin Ming had already expected that today’s events would occur.

This left Suya slightly frustrated. She felt that she had been completely crushed by this little brother.

“I must say Miss Suya…” Xiao Moxian looked at Suya, faintly smiling. “I remember that someone said last time that they would never have any intention to look for Lin Ming to create divine runic symbols… right?”

A month ago, Lin Ming had predicted that there would be people scrambling to ask him to draw up divine runic symbols.

But Suya had rudely and needlessly added in, “I have no idea who will be scrambling for you to make divine runic symbols for you in the future, but I don’t have any intention of doing so...”

Now that Xiao Moxian mentioned this, Suya was left helpless.

“Miss Xian’er, about last time, I really must apologize…”

Under the roof of others, one had no choice but to lower their hands. Suya lowered her posture once more. “But today I believe I have put forth sufficient sincerity. Sir Lin, what do you think of… 250,000 contribution points?”

Suya used pleading eyes to look at Lin Ming. Her eyes were like autumn pools of water, able to stir one’s emotions.

She put the initial price at 150,000 contribution points below what headquarters’ limit had been. This was to keep a bargaining space.

Before Lin Ming could speak, Xiao Moxian said, “250,000 points? Your plan is quite well thought out. The divine runic symbols that Lin Ming draws up can be used 200-300 times. According to the initial price of 60,000 for 20, every one should be worth 3000. Then, if you multiply that by 250 times it should be 750,000 for a single one!

“Then again, the improved Havoc Flame Symbols that Lin Ming creates are even stronger than ordinary flame symbols. Perhaps we don’t even want this pitiful amount of money!”

Xiao Moxian forcefully said.

Suya froze. “750,000…”

According to such a price, if Lin Ming handed over 1000 divine runic symbols then they would have to pay 750,000,000 contribution points. If this continued then Extreme Star Heavenly Palace definitely wouldn’t be able to withstand it. After all, they had already consumed a massive amount of resources in this war.

Although Lin Ming’s Havoc Flame Symbols could be used 200-300 times and were even stronger than ordinary versions, Extreme Star Heavenly Palace still hoped they could obtain a lower price if they bought in bulk. After all, although this improved Havoc Flame Symbol had higher techniques behind it, the cost of creating one wasn’t necessarily much higher.

“Sir Lin…” Suya knew that quarrelling with Xiao Moxian was meaningless. She used begging eyes to look at Lin Ming. “The cost of materials will all be taken on by our Extreme Star Holy Lands…”

Lin Ming’s expression was indifferent. Suya’s starting price didn’t affect him at all.

250,000 for one divine runic symbol, that meant he would need to draw up 12,000 of them to obtain 3 billion points. How long would it take to draw up 12,000 divine runic symbols? It would likely be two or three years.

Lin Ming faintly said, “Miss Suya, the truth is that you seem to have made a mistake. My divine runic symbols don’t need to be sold to you alone. Do you think that besides your Extreme Star Holy Lands, no one else is willing to pay a higher price?”

Chapter 1610 – Grandmaster Overflow

Suya was shocked by Lin Ming’s words. Indeed, as Lin Ming said, if the Extreme Star Holy Lands wanted to buy those improved Havoc Flame Symbols they could only do so from Lin Ming, but Lin Ming didn’t necessarily need to sell to them.

This sort of improved Havoc Flame Symbol could be used 200-300 times and in a battle could be activated four times. This was a heaven-defying special effect. There were many Holy Lord powerhouses that would be willing to buy such a Havoc Flame Symbol in order to serve as their final trump card.

If an early Holy Lord martial artist had this sort of flame symbol, although they might not be able to defeat a middle Holy Lord realm martial artist, it still wouldn’t be a problem to protect themselves.

If they had to go to a life or death mystic realm to adventure and even desperately bet their lives against those other people there, they would absolutely want to buy one or two of these Havoc Flame Symbols no matter what the cost was.

In addition, these revised Havoc Flame Symbols had the special attribute of being able to be used multiple times; this was an almost completely unique attribute. There were many divine runic masters that loved to collect all sorts of divine runic symbols who would love to get their hands on one. Moreover, there were many wealthy juniors of powerful influences that would similarly love to possess such a rare divine runic symbol as a point of pride.

This was a symbol of status.

Thus, even if Lin Ming publicly sold these divine runic symbols, their price would still rapidly reach a horrifying level. Their price might even surpass the accumulated total of 200-300 Havoc Flame Symbols!

Thinking of this, Suya knew that perhaps there might not be any transactions.

The price that the Extreme Star Holy Lands offered simply wouldn’t be enough.

She stood up and despairingly said, “Sir Lin, Miss Xian’er, I apologize for disturbing you today. I will go back first. Sir Lin, I will come to visit you again in the future.”

Suya could be called miserable. Her overly large eyes seemed to contain tens of thousands of words, all of them touching.

Even Lin Ming, who was used to seeing beautiful women, couldn’t help but acknowledge that Suya was an extraordinary woman.

Suya and Xiao Moxian possessed two different types of figures. Suya had explosive curves, perfectly round and soft. Although she was a shocking beauty like Xiao Moxian, she possessed a flavor that ordinary women did not have. She constantly attracted the gaze and heat of men, even with the slightest movement.

Like this, Suya walked away. From beginning to end, she possessed a feminine beauty, one that was gentle and meek. She seemed completely different from the proud figure that was resting on the couch just a month ago.

“Big Brother Lin, it seems like you turned her down.” Xiao Moxian said after Suya left.

“No need to worry, I have too many concerns right now. I have to research how to transform a fifth grade divine runic symbol and I also have to refine a soul recovery pill for Senior Divine Mist. I don’t have much free time. If I have to draw up Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols I’ll have to create dozens of them. When something is rare, it becomes far more precious. If I were to sell them at a cheap price then these Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols won’t be valuable at all.”

Lin Ming said. He had already considered this. When a new product came out, no one would know its true price. The true price was artificially created by others.

If he sold a small number of Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols, then those who bought them would scurry to hype up the price as much as possible so they would have more value.

Once the price was higher, they might resell them.

As for the next person, they would also have a similar idea. As this process continued, the price would become increasingly high until it even exceeded the original value.

Lin Ming would be happy to see such a scene occur.

……….

Still night, Suya returned to her own room and opened a long distance sound transmission array, attempting to send a message to the Internal Affairs Envoy of Extreme Star Heavenly Palace – Sage Brightyang.

Suya relayed all of her experiences from today. As Sage Brightyang heard this, he frowned.

“This junior called Lin Ming wants 750,000 contribution points for one? He is insatiably greedy!”

Sage Brightyang’s face darkened. After a period of thought he sneered and responded, “There is no need for you to concern yourself with this matter. That brat probably thinks that we can’t live without him. What a naïve child! Since he’s so greedy then I won’t let him obtain even one point.”

As Sage Brightyang replied, Suya’s heart skipped a beat. It couldn’t be that Extreme Star Heavenly Palace wanted to do something to Lin Ming, right!?

Lin Ming was living within the Divine Runic Masters Guild and had an extremely sensitive status to begin with. If Extreme Star Heavenly Palace attacked a member of the Divine Runic Masters Guild without provocation then they would inevitably suffer backlash from Divine Rune City!

This might even cause their alliance to fall apart and both sides to become enemies.

After all, kidnapping a divine runic master and forcing them to refine divine runic symbols was the absolute most taboo action for all divine runic masters. It was something that all of them loathed, no matter who they were.

Moreover, there was said to be a peak Empyrean master behind Lin Ming!

If they were to offend a peak Empyrean level character for a mere improved Havoc Flame Symbol, then that would absolutely be saving a little to lose a lot. The foolishness of that decision would be unbelievable. There wouldn’t even be a need for the Extreme Star Holy Lands to continue their war. With a peak Empyrean joining the enemy side, their loss would be ensured.

Suya didn’t feel that Extreme Star Heavenly Palace would do something so reckless. But, she was still worried that Extreme Star Heavenly Palace didn’t know about Lin Ming’s background.

She soon obtained an answer. Sage Brightyang’s tone was extremely gloomy. “We naturally won’t do anything to cause enmity with the Divine Runic Masters Guild. But, this doesn’t mean that we don’t have any means to deal with this boy. We’ve already invited Grandmaster Overflow…”

Grandmaster Overflow?

Suya was stunned. She had heard this name before.

In the world of divine runic masters, most divine runic masters were extremely proud and famous, respectable characters that were honored by others.

But, there were divine runic masters that lived in the dark. These divine runic masters did not research the divine runic arts but instead plagiarized the results and accomplishments of others.

If someone were to develop an astonishingly valuable divine runic symbol, there would naturally be evil individuals that attempted to appropriate these techniques for themselves. After all, these divine runic symbols involved a massive amount of benefits!

Generally speaking, when a divine runic master drew up a divine runic master they would have measures to prevent them from being cracked. Moreover, divine runic symbols involved numerous tiny complex runes and structures as well as a fusion between the divine runic symbol itself and the Heavenly Dao Laws and different fluctuations of weak and strong energy flows. Wanting to recreate a forgery was nearly impossible.

But, there was one type of divine runic master that specialized in this field.

Just like in the mortal world where there were thieves who specialized in picking locks; they were able to open any of them.

These types of divine runic masters were loathed by all others. There was no divine runic master that wanted the things they carefully researched to be stolen by others.

However, when driven by tremendous benefits, there were a number of divine runic masters that would rather become one of the people that lived in the dark.

These people had their own inheritances.

Of course, these inheritances were especially focused on how to unravel the divine runic symbols of others.

And this Grandmaster Overflow was a grandmaster level character amongst all dark divine runic masters!

According to what Suya knew, Grandmaster Overflow was a peak sixth grade divine runic master! If he had chosen to focus his efforts on the orthodox path then he would have obtained great results.

But as someone of the dark path, Grandmaster Overflow was known as a person who could open any lock. The only problems to him were time and cost.

Although many divine runic masters had their own ultimate final technique, Grandmaster Overflow didn’t have a liking for these. After all, in order to crack open the secrets of a divine runic symbol one needed to consume a massive amount of rare and precious materials as well as a variety of costly array formations. The total cost could leave one dumbfounded.

“Unravel… if we can really unravel the secrets to this improved Havoc Flame Symbol, then the advantages to our Extreme Star Holy Lands will be tremendous!” Suya thought. She didn’t know why, but she felt something strange in her heart. In her short moment of contact with Lin Ming just now, she didn’t know why but that youth had become unfathomably deep and unpredictable.

Would Grandmaster Overflow be able to unravel Lin Ming’s divine runic symbol?

Suya knew that with things having reached this point there was nothing she could do. She could only calmly wait in her area of the Mission Division and do her own job…

……

Two days later, Extreme Star Holy Lands…

The Extreme Star Holy Lands was located above the Asura Road’s Miluo Star Ocean. This Star Ocean had countless massive 100,000 mile wide islands that floated above it, and although they were called islands, the truth was that they weren’t much smaller than continents of some planets.

Above these islands was an endlessly dark night. In the skies, there was always an endless ocean of stars that floated across the world.

Underneath this endless starlight, there was a deep blue palace floating high in the sky. This was Extreme Star Heavenly Palace!

This was the supreme command center of the Extreme Star Holy Lands as well as the residence of the Extreme Star Holy Lands’ two Empyreans!

And on this day, the gates of Extreme Star Heavenly Palace opened. As the Internal Affairs Envoy of Extreme Star Heavenly Palace, Sage Brightyang personally waited at the entrance of the Heavenly Palace to greet Grandmaster Overflow!

Grandmaster Overflow was a Great World King to begin with, and through these years, the wealth he accumulated was unimaginable. Although he was a cruel and infamous individual known for his spite, he still provoked fear and awe in many people!

This was the suppressive fear brought by strength!

Chapter 1611 – Test

“You actually managed to have Grandmaster Overflow come and help?” A World King said from beside Sage Brightyang. This World King was Waking Cloud, a direct disciple of one of Extreme Star Heavenly Palace’s two Empyreans.

“Requesting Overflow to help will definitely come with a great price…” Someone added in after Waking Cloud.

Sage Brightyang said, “To this type of divine runic symbol, Grandmaster Overflow will definitely have a great interest. And after he unravels the secrets to creating one, we will definitely have to pay a great price. However, for the techniques behind this sort of divine runic symbol, it is absolutely worth it…”

As Sage Brightyang was speaking, a melodious immortal song echoed through the air. A magnificent divine carriage decked in gold and jade shot through the horizon, dragging a brilliant rainbow behind it.

This divine carriage was hundreds of feet wide and was several times larger than an ordinary pavilion. It was pulled by 18 dignified ancient great beasts, slowly flying forwards. In front of the divine carriage was a squad of golden-armored warriors leading the way, each one carrying spirit artifacts. And behind the divine carriage were enchanting maids with high martial talents and cultivations, all of them holding various musical instruments. As they flew forwards, music filled the air. At the vanguard of the procession was a spirit boat filled with pretty maids that sprinkled down flower petals, like a cascading river of color fading into the deep!

And these flower petals were not ordinary flower petals. Rather, they were considerably expensive spirit flower petals. Just scattering these flower petals was an extremely great wealth!

From this alone, one could see how wealthy and opulent the master of the divine carriage was!

The divine carriage came to a steady stop before Extreme Star Heavenly Palace. Four beautiful maids moved forwards and parted the curtains of the divine carriage. Then, an old man in an opulent yellow robe stepped out.

This old man had unsightly features but his eyes were razor sharp. His held two young concubines to his chest. Without a doubt, this was Grandmaster Overflow!

“This kind of parade…” Waking Cloud was left flabbergasted. Just the flower petals alone cost innumerable origin energy runes. Even an Empyrean travelling outside wasn’t too different.

“Grandmaster Overflow!” Sage Brightyang hurriedly moved forwards to greet him.

But Overflow only slightly nodded back and released the two concubines from his arms. He lightly said, “My time is valuable. There is no need for any pleasantries.”

“Good!” Sage Brightyang said, leading Overflow to the best divine runic room in the entire Extreme Star Heavenly Palace.

As for Overflow’s guards, maids and concubines, all of them were treated well and asked to wait outside the palace.

Extreme Star Heavenly Palace’s divine runic room was several miles wide. This giant square was so large because there were all sorts of expensive arrays set up as well as a top grade divine runic table that seemed like an altar.

Above this divine runic table, the runes of multiple array formations shined.

After glancing through this facility, Overflow was fairly satisfied.

“Who created that divine runic symbol?” Overflow asked, getting straight to the point.

Sage Brightyang hesitated for a moment. “A third grade divine runic master.”

Seeing Overflow frown as if he were about to be angry, Sage Brightyang quickly explained, “His divine runic arts level is likely above the third grade, and the current rune structure of the symbol might not have been invented by him either.”

Overflow coldly coughed. If this was really the work of a mere third grade divine runic master, then asking him to unravel it was simply an insult.

He coldly said, “I hope it is a valuable divine runic symbol. I travelled several hundred million miles to come here and I’d better not be disappointed. Where is the divine runic symbol?”

Sage Brightyang immediately took out the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol that Lin Ming had created. From appearances, this divine runic symbol didn’t seem any different from an ordinary Havoc Flame Symbol.

Seeing this fourth grade divine runic symbol, Overflow didn’t seem to have any interest. But as he swept his sense through the structure of the divine runic symbol, a brilliant light shined in his eyes.

“Eh, this is quite interesting!”

Overflow was clearly excited. Sage Brightyang was ecstatic. If this could arouse Grandmaster Overflow’s interest then he would likely treat this not as a mission but as a personal endeavor. He would assuredly put forth 120% of his effort.

“Are there the array formations I want?”

“Yes!” Sage Brightyang immediately ordered people to start the array formations in this room. These array formations had long been arranged in advance, and all of them were to support one in the divine runic arts. The cost of construction for each one was astronomical. If the cost was exchanged for contribution points of the Divine Runic Masters Guild then every array formation would be worth at least 10 million points.

Although Extreme Star Heavenly Palace was considerably wealthy, they only arranged these array formations in a single divine runic room.

Sage Brightyang embarrassedly said, “We only have conventional array formations; we don’t have specialized unraveling array formations. I must ask Grandmaster Overflow for help in setting them up.”

Overflow laughed and proudly said, “This is natural. These unraveling array formations are all a specialty of my career; you naturally wouldn’t know of them.”

These dark divine runic masters made their living by plagiarizing and stealing the work of others. But, when it came to their own techniques and inheritances, they would keep them hidden watertight, never revealing their secrets to others.

If anyone wanted to steal their techniques, they would go all-out against them.

Grandmaster Overflow took out a dozen plus array discs from his spatial ring and placed them on the massive divine runic table.

Overflow was extremely careful in his actions. Each array disc was crafted from materials worth tens of millions of points. Moreover, the array discs also involved a variety of secret techniques. These array discs could be called Overflow’s specialty treasures.

After Overflow spread out all the array discs, Sage Brightyang and the others drew back and used crystal balls to observe what was happening. They didn’t want to disturb Grandmaster Overflow.

“He’s so professional.” Someone praised from behind Sage Brightyang.

“That’s right, the professionalism is completely different. Just those array discs that the Grandmaster took out are more expensive than the entire seventh grade divine runic room we prepared!”

“Lord Internal Affair Envoy’s move is quite wonderful. As long as we succeed then we’ll have saved a tremendous expense for Extreme Star Heavenly Palace and we’ll also have gained a top divine runic symbol technology. With this amazing battlefield weapon in our hands, no one will dare to move against our Extreme Star Heavenly Palace!”

Listening to this person, Sage Brightyang faintly smiled. He said, “Just who is this and just what is he doing? Grandmaster Overflow is a peak dark divine runic master. With him helping us, our plan of copying that technology is almost assured success. We only need to wait for the good news. I estimate that he should finish in around 10 days.”

………..

As Extreme Star Heavenly Palace launched their offensive to copy Lin Ming’s divine runic symbol, it was finally becoming known by others that these improved Havoc Flame Symbols made by Lin Ming were able to be used multiple times. Moreover, it was also learned that the true name of these divine runic symbols was actually Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol.

However, these were merely rumors spread from the frontlines and there was no way to measure the veracity of these claims. As for one of the few insiders, Suya definitely wouldn’t spread such news for Lin Ming.

The members of the Divine Runic Masters Guild were all highly accomplished in the divine runic arts. They all knew how difficult it was to create a divine runic symbol that could be used multiple times.

Their knowledge and experience made them doubt such an unbelievable matter.

All of this led to the scene today. A group of divine runic masters waited in a test room of the Divine Runic Masters Guild. They surrounded an illusory magic array, waiting to see the destructive might of this Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol.

Seeing was believing! Through this array formation test, they could confirm the truth.

Lin Ming was also in this test room. He held a Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol in his hand, the one that he had created a month ago.

“Lin Ming, you brat, you’re always up to some tricks.”

Old Xue had arrived with his good friend Old Su. The two of them had also heard the rumors, and although they felt it was a bit incredible, since it concerned Lin Ming they already half believed it subconsciously.

Old Su traced his chin. He couldn’t help but ask, “I heard that your Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol could be used multiple times? How many times is that?”

Old Su cared most about the number of times that the divine runic symbol could be used.

Lin Ming faintly smiled, “You’ll find out after the test…”

Lin Ming didn’t waste his time with idle chatting. After several dozen people finally gathered in the room, he walked into the center of the array formation and activated it.

At this time, Lin Ming saw Suya.

Today’s Suya was dressed much more conservatively. She wore a windproof coat with a high collar. Even so, her explosive figure still struggled to escape the confines of her clothing.

Suya faintly smiled as she saw Lin Ming glance at her. She knew that Lin Ming planned to establish the reputation of the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol and then sell it for a high price.

Today’s array formation test would pave the way for that high price.

Chapter 1612 – Copy

After the testing array formation activated, dozens of ancient vicious beast simulations conjured up by the illusory magic array appeared. These vicious beasts surrounded Lin Ming, their strengths ranging from the Divine Transformation realm to the World King realm!

These were merely living targets. Although they had defensive capabilities similar to real vicious beasts, they were not aggressive at all.

Facing these ancient vicious beasts, Lin Ming calmly activated the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol.

For a time, dao patterns of the Asura Heavenly Dao wove in the air. With a terrifying explosion, flames swept out like a tide.

Dozens of ancient vicious beasts were swallowed up by the flames. Over 90% of the vicious beasts were instantly reduced to ash with only several of them surviving the carnage.

Of the surviving vicious beasts, some were severely burnt. But, there were also several vicious beasts equal to the human late Holy Lord realm or peak Holy Lord realm, and even a World King level vicious beast that wasn’t injured at all.

In particular, that World King level armored forest dragon still stood tall and proud in the skies, its scales not damaged even the slightest bit.

Seeing this destructive power, Old Xue didn’t even need to look at the data; he immediately judged the strength of the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol in Lin Ming’s hands. “This is… a Holy Lord level two star destructive power. It’s slightly better than an excellently crafted Havoc Flame Symbol, about a star higher.”

“It’s quite good.” Old Su nodded.

Before anyone else could make their judgments, with Lin Ming’s right hand as the center, the numerous dao patterns of the Asura Heavenly Dao rapidly condensed, manifesting back into a new Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol in the blink of an eye!

Lin Ming didn’t pause; brilliant flames erupted once more.

Another explosive sound occurred!

Beside Lin Ming, a terrifying detonation blew up once more!

Lin Ming had activated the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol a second time!

All of the several remaining ancient vicious beasts were sucked up into the flames. Sorrowful howls filled the air.

The late Holy Lord and peak Holy Lord level vicious beasts were charred black by the flames.

“The second time came so fast!”

Although the people present had heard that the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol could be used continuously, they never imagined that the gap between uses would be so short.

But this was only the start. Following this, the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol within Lin Ming’s hand exploded for a third time!

As the creator of the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol, Lin Ming was the person most familiar with the runic structure within it. Combined with his understanding of the Asura Heavenly Dao as well as his achievements in the seventh level Concept of the Fire Laws, using the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol came as easily as breathing!

Normally, a martial artist could use the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol four times before the energy within it exhausted itself. Then, the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol would need time to recover energy for its next use.

But Lin Ming simply didn’t need to do this.

As Lin Ming used the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol, he continued to fill it with new energy!

The flames used to create the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol were Lin Ming’s tribulation fire and Xiao Moxian’s nirvanic fire.

Currently, Lin Ming had these two types of flames.

Thus, within Lin Ming’s hand, the power displayed by this Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol had an essential difference compared to when it was placed in someone else’s hands.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

Within the array formation, a terrifying explosion lit up the world every two breaths of time!

That dreadful sea of flames swept through the entire array formation. If it weren’t for the protection of that array formation, the entire testing room would have been ruined by the terrifying explosions!

Lin Ming activated the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol again and again.

Although this flame symbol was constantly absorbing Lin Ming’s energy, Lin Ming’s strength wasn’t comparable to a two star Holy Lord level attack. To him, keeping up a barrage of this level wasn’t anything at all.

This was just a well-trained martial artist doing hundreds of pushups without being exhausted.

Beneath the wild canopy of explosions, besides the World King level ancient beast, every single other vicious beast had been swallowed up by the flames and destroyed.

This scene left all of the other divine runic masters present speechless. In particular Suya; her eyes were as wide as full moons and she couldn’t find the words to describe this.

She had read the test reports that Extreme Star Heavenly Palace had sent her about the Nirvanic Flame Tribulation Flame Symbol. It was true that this flame symbol could be used multiple times, but every four times it was used it needed to recharge. It was impossible for it to perform like it did with Lin Ming today, continuously striking out without missing a beat!

Perhaps this wasn’t just because Lin Ming was the creator of the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol but also because of Lin Ming’s terrifying strength!

She finally became faintly aware that this youth in front of her, in terms of divine runic arts or strength, had far surpassed her imagination. Right now it was impossible for her to estimate him. His depths were completely concealed, absolutely airtight!

“Elder Xue… Lin Ming, he… is he really less than 100 years old?”

Suya glanced at Old Xue. Everything related to Lin Ming had been told to her by Old Xue.

“His skeletal age indicated so. I think he wouldn’t be so bored as to fake this.”

Old Xue licked his lips. Over the years he had seen many incidents of a monstrous genius occur around Lin Ming. It was hard for anything Lin Ming did to surprise him now.

Suya sucked in a deep breath, at a loss for words.

She suddenly felt that it was a laughable matter when she looked at Lin Ming like he was a little brother.

The explosions within the array formation were like a violent storm, continuing without a hint of dying down.

Everyone was keeping quiet count of this intense bombardment in their hearts. Now, after an incense stick of time, more than a hundred explosions had occurred!

Even that final World King level beast was struck into bloody shape by the barrage of attacks!

It howled again and again. Its scales were swallowed up by those destructive flames and a great deal of its flesh was burnt black!

“Could it be… that Lin Ming can burn the World King level ancient vicious beast to death?”

This thought flashed through the minds of many people present. A human could not compare to the defensive abilities of an ancient vicious beast. Even the bodies of the saints, in terms of defense, were slightly worse than vicious beasts.

And now, in this situation, it seemed that Lin Ming would really be able to annihilate this vicious beast!

By this time, the number of explosions had risen to over 200!

This World King level armored forest dragon was already burnt into a miserable appearance. A large number of red bones had been exposed and also scorched black by the flames.

Finally, with a miserable wail it fell to the ground, surrounded by flames!

With a slight cracking sound, the armored forest dragon turned into endless motes of light and vanished.

Like this, all of the vicious beasts within the array formation had been completely destroyed by Lin Ming’s Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol!

“How terrifying, even that World King level vicious beast was killed! This is only a fourth grade divine runic symbol!”

Although Lin Ming had relied on multiple attacks to achieve this, to use a fourth grade divine runic symbol to kill a World King vicious beast was far too amazing. Ordinarily speaking, only a sixth grade divine runic symbol could accomplish his.

Within the array formation, even though all of the vicious beasts had disappeared, the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol within Lin Ming’s hands continued to explode another 150 some times. Only then did the sea of flames finally die down before vanishing.

Thus, the test had ended.

“412 times!”

After the flames within the array formation dissipated, some people spouted out this number. How was this testing divine runic symbols? This was more like setting off firecrackers!

Many divine runic masters looked at each other and gulped. They heard that Lin Ming had created a Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol that could be used multiple times but they never imagined this would be over 400 times.

The price of a Havoc Flame Symbol was at the top of fourth grade divine runic symbols. If the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol was equal to 400 some Havoc Flame Symbols, then he was rich!

Many people soon realized this and Suya was no exception. She sighed. When Extreme Star Heavenly Palace had done their own tests, the upper limits of use was only 200-300 times. The reason that Lin Ming could use it over 400 times was clearly because he understood the runic structure of the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol.

“I wonder how headquarters’ copying plan is coming along.” Suya thought as she watched Lin Ming walk down from the testing array formation, his face not even slightly reddened. An inexplicable feeling of dread appeared in her heart. She feared that this Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol wasn’t as simple as it seemed. If Lin Ming dared to put it forth in such a grandiose manner, would it truly be so easy to copy?

“This Lin Ming… I really have no idea what depths he is hiding!”

Suya was increasingly awed by Lin Ming. And at this time, Lin Ming revealed a toothy smile as he asked, “Everyone, is there anyone that would like to buy this Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol? I only accept contribution points. You can purchase one alone or in batches; the highest bid wins!”

With these words, the entire audience of divine runic masters was left stunned…

…..

At this time, a hundred million miles away, in Extreme Star Heavenly Palace’s seventh grade divine runic room –

Grandmaster Overflow had been locked in battle with this Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol for the last two days and one night.

During this time, Grandmaster Overflow didn’t rest at all. He sat motionless in front of the divine runic table, using all sorts of methods to analyze this fourth grade divine runic symbol!

From the start where he didn’t expect much at all, to the time when his interest was aroused by the unique structure of this divine runic symbol, and now through two days of battling, Grandmaster Overflow’s complexion became increasingly dignified.

He could clearly feel that this Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol was unusually troublesome.

However, the more difficult things were the more it stirred his fighting spirit. He believed that he was amongst the best rune breakers within the profession of dark divine runic masters. In this world, besides seventh grade divine runic symbols which were only a problem because of the limit of his cultivation, there was nothing he couldn’t unravel. Whether it was a fourth grade, fifth grade, or sixth grade divine runic symbol, he could open any lock.

These were the thoughts in Overflow’s mind.

He was a considerably prideful person.

And now, Overflow had already been defeated by this fourth grade divine runic symbol many times. At this time, two jade slips were placed in front of him.

All sorts of calculations and deductions were recorded within these two jade slips. Overflow used his special inheritance to analyze the rune structure of the divine runic symbol. Every time he did so he had to make a massive number of calculations.

However, the results obtained from these deductions left Overflow feeling strange. He didn’t know whether or not these results were right, and just what he could draw up if he followed these results.

Chapter 1617 – Extreme Dual Polarity Symbol

Time flew by, an unending river.

Lin Ming worked like a construct that didn’t know of exhaustion. The amount of work he completed every day was staggering.

When Lin Ming’s soul force ran dry he would meditate and revolve the Divine Mist Heart Mantra.

As a peak transcendent divine might, the Divine Mist Heart Mantra was the most suitable method for restoring his dried up soul force. In the past when Lin Ming cultivated the Divine Mist Heart Mantra underneath Empyrean Divine Mist, he had his own spiritual sea completely ruptured and then restored. The pain from that time was countless times more exaggerated and agonizing then his current soul force exhaustion.

Day after day, Lin Ming discovered that the intensity of his soul force was rapidly growing!

At the start he was able to draw up 12 divine runic symbols a day before he collapsed.

But after two months, Lin Ming was able to draw up 13 divine runic symbols a day. After another two months, Lin Ming was able to draw up 14 divine runic symbols.

This also meant that every time Lin Ming turned in part of the mission, each time there would be more than the last.

Seeing Lin Ming work like a monster, bringing in almost 200 Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols every half month and even seeing this number increase over time, Suya was shocked at first, apprehensive next, and then as she became accustomed to this she simply became numb.

This was the beginning of the sixth month.

Lin Ming handed over 220 Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols.

In these past 15 days he had drawn up 220 peak fourth grade divine runic symbols. Even Suya didn’t know what expression to have for this.

With this, Lin Ming’s mission was complete. Moreover, he had even produced an extra hundred!

And before these divine runic symbols were shipped to the warfront they had already undergone a routine inspection.

The 2100 plus Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols were completely without a single defect. All of them maintained an absolute standard in quality. Compared to the 20 Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols that Lin Ming had sent at the start, none of them were worse.

At the end, the number of times that the flame symbols could be used had climbed to over 300. This was a result of Lin Ming’s technique becoming increasingly skilled and intricate, leading to each Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol he created becoming increasingly perfect.

To produce a single divine runic symbol at a high quality wasn’t strange at all. But, to produce over 2000 divine runic symbols perfectly, that was horrifying.

Not just that, but Lin Ming had maintained a constant speed of three times that of the average person!

And what left Suya breathless the most was that Lin Ming had continued this ultra-high intensity work pace for almost six months without end!

The exhaustion, loneliness, aridness of the situation, it was simply hard to imagine. Every time Suya saw Lin Ming she could also feel the serious overdrawn nature of his soul force. Perhaps anyone else would have collapsed by now.

But Lin Ming was able to persist through all of it.

Regarding this, it wasn’t just Suya, but even the people of Extreme Star Heavenly Palace had long been at a loss for words. They originally thought that Lin Ming would need at least two years to complete 2000 divine runic symbols, but he had managed to accomplish this in half a year with a production speed that could frighten one to death. They also finally realized that their early plan to copy his work had been doomed to failure from the start.

Lin Ming was able to produce these Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols not because of luck or coincidence but because he was an abnormal monster.

“Sir Lin, this is your reward.” Suya handed over a jade slip with around 13 million contribution points. With this, their transaction had ended.

Although Extreme Star Heavenly Palace had paid a gigantic sum of money for these Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols, correspondingly the frontlines of the war had obtained remarkable victories!

These Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols had a specific activation method and only the disciples of Extreme Star Heavenly Palace knew how to use them. If 20-30 Holy Lords activated their Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols together, even a World King would have to retreat.

“Thank you.”

Lin Ming took the jade slip and swept his sense through it. After seeing that there were no errors, he planned to return to his own room. But at this time, Suya called out to him, “Sir Lin, please wait.”

“Mm? Is there something else?” Lin Ming turned to look at Suya.

Suya covered her mouth and laughed. “Sir Lin, do you find me annoying? It seems that every time you come you are in a hurry, as if you’re afraid to see me!

“Sir Lin, it is like this. The mission to complete 2000 Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols has already been finished, but I wonder if Sir Lin has any interest in continuing to cooperate with us. The Extreme Star Holy Lands is willing to put forth a price of 600,000 points for every divine runic symbol and continue purchasing Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols from Sir Lin…”

Even 2000 Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols wasn’t enough for the Extreme Star Holy Lands to use.

Before this, they had only requested for Lin Ming to draw up 2000 because they had thought that Lin Ming would take a long time to complete this mission. But at that time, perhaps the war between the Extreme Star Holy Lands and Heaven Strife Holy Lands would have come to an end.

Now that they saw Lin Ming’s rapid production speed, they would be willing to eat the costs of another 1000.

“I’m sorry… there are other matters I must attend to.” Lin Ming refused this request but he didn’t absolutely reject all cooperation. He thought for a moment and said, “After around five more months I should have finished things. At that time I will consider working with your Extreme Star Holy Lands again…”

“Great!”

Suya was already satisfied with such an answer. In her opinion, Lin Ming wasn’t someone that lied or exaggerated. If he said something then that was proof he had confidence or interest.

Like this, Lin Ming took the 10 million plus points and went to the special materials section of the Divine Runic Masters Guild.

He bought up 12 million points of materials in a single go, including all sorts of rare and precious ones. For instance, osmosis rainbow flower fruit. This sort of fruit was the size of a pigeon egg and cost 3 million contribution points, but Lin Ming purchased three of them together.

After taking up all of these materials, Lin Ming returned to his own divine runic room.

By this point Lin Ming had long switched into the highest quality seventh grade divine runic room. This divine runic room was no smaller than a city square and was filled with all sorts of array formations and nearly processed all the materials for him.

He had temporarily refused Suya’s request because he had arrived at a critical moment in transforming the fifth grade divine runic symbol.

Before the treasure fair started, Lin Ming planned to select two types of fifth grade divine runic symbols and complete revisions of them.

Of these two types of divine runic symbols, the first one he chose was called the Heavenly Fire Symbol.

The Heavenly Fire Symbol could be called an improved version of the Havoc Flame Symbol.

Because Lin Ming already had experience transforming the Havoc Flame Symbol, it wasn’t too much work to transform the Heavenly Fire Symbol.

As for the second divine runic symbol, that was a true test of Lin Ming’s ability.

This was a peak fifth grade divine runic symbol!

With Lin Ming’s current level of skill, wanting to transform a peak fifth grade divine runic symbol wasn’t realistic at all. But, this fifth grade divine runic symbol seemed as if it were especially created for Lin Ming alone.

Its name was the Extreme Dual Polarity Symbol.

The word Extreme meant to bring things to the absolute extreme. The words Dual Polarity meant that this divine runic symbol was able to display the powers of two different elements to their extreme limits. And, these two elements were the thunder and flame elements that Lin Ming specialized in!

The Extreme Dual Polarity Symbol was a dreadfully dangerous offensive divine runic symbol. Out of all the known fifth grade divine runic symbols, the Extreme Dual Polarity Symbol’s power and performance could be ranked in the top three. It even surpassed many sixth grade divine runic symbols!

Thus, if one could successfully draw up a single Extreme Dual Polarity Symbol, its value would be enormous.

However, the Extreme Dual Polarity Symbol actually had many limitations.

The difficulty of drawing one up was extremely high. The powers of thunder and fire were violent and tyrannical to the extreme. Wanting to fuse these two types of powers together into a symbol paper wasn’t easy at all. If there was a single error, it was possible that the entire mess could explode.

Even a peak fifth grade divine runic master had to be utterly cautious in drawing up an Extreme Dual Polarity Symbol. Failure meant losing all of the invested materials and having blown up array formations. It was even possible to be injured in the process.

The original structure of this divine runic symbol wasn’t perfect to begin with. To make revisions and improve the Extreme Dual Polarity Symbol… the difficulty of this could be imagined!

At this time, all sorts of array formations began to activate in the divine runic room.

Lin Ming stood within these array formations, all of his concentration focused on a beautiful red and purple symbol that floated three feet in front of him.

The tiny runes each contained a horrifying strength. If there was even a single mistake in the structure of the tiny runes, the consequences would be incredibly severe!

It had to be known that if one broke any array formations in this room, all damages had to be paid by the divine runic master who rented it.

Because of this, many peak divine runic masters didn’t dare to draw up an Extreme Dual Polarity Symbol in the center of expensive array formations. This caused the difficulty to be even higher. It was rare to see a perfectly drawn Extreme Dual Polarity Symbol.

Lin Ming closed his eyes in meditation. At this time, behind Lin Ming, the phantom of a divine tree began to slowly appear.

This was the Heretical God Tree within Lin Ming’s inner world!

Chapter 1619 – Treasure Fair

Divine Rune City’s treasure fair was held by a business directly subordinate to the Divine Runic Masters Guild, the Runic Pill Trade Association.

Although the Runic Pill Trade Association’s reputation wasn’t too obvious, the truth was that the material warehouses of the Divine Runic Masters guild, the cashing in of contribution points, and many other shops and industries affiliated with the Divine Runic Masters Guild were all managed by the Runic Pill Trading Organization.

The term Runic Pill came from the divine runic arts and the pill refining alchemy arts. In Divine Rune City, the divine runic arts and alchemy came hand in hand.

The Divine Runic Masters Guild established the Runic Pill Trading Organization in order to govern their vast fortune and innumerable assets. After all, when it came to business affairs, they needed people who were proficient in that aspect. Divine runic masters generally didn’t have the time nor ability to manage such massive amounts of wealth.

As the treasure fair was readying to go into full swing, in a seventh grade divine runic room at the Divine Runic Masters Guild, an exhausted Lin Ming was slumped down in front of a table. His face was pallid and streaming sweat and he seemed completely drained.

But at this time, a burning excitement was shining in his eyes.

A moment ago he had just completed the improved Extreme Dual Polarity Symbol! This also signaled the first time he completed an Extreme Dual Polarity Symbol.

This improved version had a new name, a highly fitting one that was also very tyrannical – the Heretical God Symbol!

The reason it was called this name was because Lin Ming had successfully improved the Extreme Dual Polarity Symbol and he had relied entirely upon the Heretical God Tree’s ability to control fire and thunder energies to do so.

The successes of the Heretical God Symbol left Lin Ming feeling a deep sense of accomplishment and satisfaction.

This was something he had used over half a year of painstaking efforts to complete. Only then did he succeed in creating this masterpiece of his. This improved divine runic symbol was the manifestation of Lin Ming’s highest level of divine runic arts!

Even for a long time in the future, even if Lin Ming truly stepped into the realm of a sixth grade divine runic master he would it hard to surpass today’s accomplishments.

Thinking about the entire creation process of the Heretical God Symbol, Lin Ming felt a stirring feeling in his heart. The reason he was able to succeed was entirely because of some coincidental lucky chances in addition to the evolution of the Heretical God Tree. If he had to turn back time and repeat this process over again, he might not necessarily succeed.

Picking up the completed Heretical God Symbol, Lin Ming took a pen and wrote the ‘Lin’ character on the bottom right corner.

This was Lin Ming’s brand.

Besides the Heretical God Symbol, Lin Ming also drew up the improved version of the Heavenly Fire Symbol.

The various properties of the Heavenly Fire Symbol couldn’t be considered as outstanding amongst fifth grade divine runic symbols. Moreover, as with the improved version of the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol, Lin Ming found it much easier to revise because he knew the supporting theoretical basis behind it.

At the bottom right corner of the Heavenly Fire Symbol, Lin Ming also wrote his surname.

At this time, there was a knock on the door. The one who arrived was Xiao Moxian.

Today, Lin Ming decided to take a brief vacation. He made a plan with Xiao Moxian beforehand to go to the treasure fair and take a stroll through it.

Of course, this was also to pave the way for the treasure fair half a month from now.

…………….

In these past days, using the words lively or bustling wasn’t enough to describe the atmosphere of Divine Rune City.

On the streets there were Divine Lords and Holy Lords everywhere. Many of these people hid their cultivation so it was unwise to offend anyone. There were even Great World Kings and half-step Empyreans mingling amongst the crowds.

During the treasure fair, although the greatest auctions would come at the finale of the event, there were still many people trying to drum up interest in their own treasures, thus they participated in the treasure fair from the beginning.

They would display their treasures to attract buyers at the treasure fair. Then when the time for the auction came, they could sell for a good price.

There were even many things that were sold during the treasure fair.

Lin Ming had a specific goal – that was to find dragon saliva grass and a jade dragon horn. As for a heaven devouring snake gallbladder and a primal jade quintessence, those could be found within the Divine Runic Masters Guild’s warehouses.

Originally, with Lin Ming’s qualifications he didn’t have the authority to purchase such precious materials. But, his performance this past year was far too eye-catching. Within the entire Divine Runic Masters Guild there was no one that didn’t know of Lin Ming. This caused his status to be incomparable to what it was before.

In addition, Lin Ming contributed all of the ultimate final divine runic art techniques he obtained from Torchriver and the other two divine runic masters’ memories and completely handed them over to the Divine Runic Masters Guild. Through these techniques he was able to obtain the right to purchase the heaven devouring snake gallbladder and primal jade quintessence.

Walking through Divine Rune City, Lin Ming could feel the light being blocked out. Looking up, he saw a massive round structure floating high in the skies. This structure was a hundred miles wide! It was incomparably massive as it floated in the skies of Divine Rune City!

This building was built entirely with special obsidian. Beneath the bright sunlight it sparkled with an intense black light. This was a massive floating castle!

From far away, Lin Ming could see many martial artists passing in and out of this giant castle. They were like little bees flying in and out of a nest.

This giant floating castle was the listed address where the Divine Runic Masters guild held the treasure fair.

Divine Rune City was a city where the roads were already paved with gold. Every inch of land was developed and it was impossible to accommodate too many extra people.

Thus, holding the treasure fair in the skies was the most appropriate solution.

Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian flew up towards the floating castle.

After flying through the front gates, even though Lin Ming had been prepared he was still shocked by the scene occurring before him.

A hundred mile wide space was easily spoken, but the truth was that it was similar to a mortal city in size. A mortal city a few dozen miles wide was already considered large, but for a hundred mile wide city, one couldn’t even see the mountains from one side to the other.

This sort of hundred mile wide floating castle had an incomparably broad space within it, as if it were a separate world!

At this time, there was a massive channel in front of Lin Ming. This channel was enough to accommodate hundreds of flying individuals.

And both sides of this giant channel were packed with shops!

Every shop was the size of a palace. Their front gates were wide open as they faced the channel. Looking from afar, this place really did resemble the honeycomb structure of a beehive!

Many martial artists flew through this channel, stopping by any shops that they were interested in.

During this treasure fair, the cost to rent a space in this floating castle was astronomically high. Anyone that could afford it was a major seller.

As for those that couldn’t afford a shop, they also had a space. That was the giant market squares within.

The market squares within the floating castle were ten miles long and wide. They could easily hold 100,000 stalls.

“This is quite the grand event.” Lin Ming praised.

Xiao Moxian faintly smiled. “Indeed. The Asura Road may be smaller than the Divine Realm, but in terms of liveliness and number of masters, I fear that it is far superior.”

Within Demondawn Heavenly Palace, Xiao Moxian had seen many great scenes before. But to hold such an event where so many Divine Lords, Holy Lords, and World Kings converged, all of them bringing out treasures to sell, this was a scene that Demondawn Heavenly Palace wasn’t able to compare to.

“Young master, come and take a look at our clothes! Not only are they artistically crafted but they are also practical. Let that pretty lady beside you try one on and I’m sure her beauty will capture you!”

Lin Ming suddenly heard a sweet womanly voice sound out in his ears as he was speaking to Xiao Moxian.

Lin Ming turned his head. At some point, he and Xiao Moxian had unknowingly approached a clothing shop.

This shop had all sorts of robes and vestments on display. The worst of these were all medium-grade spirit artifacts.

If Lin Ming were back to the time when he bought the Boundless World Pill, these enhanced vestments would all be luxury items. But now, Lin Ming’s strength surpassed that of an ordinary World King and his wealth was countless times greater than that of an World King of the Divine Realm. Currently, buying a medium-grade spirit artifact vestment wouldn’t be anything at all.

“Do you have anything of a higher quality?”

Lin Ming wasn’t interested in these magic clothes but he remembered that he had never gifted Xiao Moxian anything. Although Lin Ming didn’t really care much for the quality of the clothes that this shop sold, the clothes themselves were actually quite artistic and beautiful. If Xiao Moxian were to wear them they would definitely look beautiful on her.

“Of course.”

Seeing Lin Ming open his pockets in such an extravagant manner, the saleswoman was even more attentive to him. She quickly brought out several of her shop’s best articles of clothing and Xiao Moxian chose one of them with a bright smile. To the current Lin Ming, 80,000 contribution points was nothing but a light drizzle.

Xiao Moxian happily went to try on the clothes. To her, although these clothes were quite good looking, the most important thing was that Lin Ming was buying them for her.

“Miss, I would like to ask you something. There are several rare and precious materials I want to buy at this treasure fair. Where would I be able to find them?” Lin Ming borrowed this opportunity while he was buying clothes to ask where the rare and precious materials were located in the treasure fair. He didn’t want to randomly wander about without aim.

“Rare and precious materials? How rare and precious?” The saleswoman enchantingly smiled. Lin Ming’s generosity had her treating him with a great deal of respect and joy.

“In contribution points, 10 million and above.”

Lin Ming didn’t want to sound too shocking thus he only said 10 million. But in truth, the materials he wanted to buy were in the hundreds of millions.

Even so, the young saleswoman covered her mouth in surprise. 10 million contribution points! Even some poorer World Kings only had around 20 million or so points of wealth.

And this young man in front of her wanted to buy materials that were 10 million points or above. Really, people couldn’t be judged by their appearances.

“Those types of precious valuables are all exhibited in the central VIP hall of the castle. Some things are even in the hundreds of millions of points. But to enter the VIP hall, you’ll need VIP status or at least 50 million points…”

The young saleswoman looked at Lin Ming with awe and gave him a map of the floating castle.

“Thank you.”

Lin Ming glanced through this map. There was an extremely detailed explanation of every area and it was highly helpful to Lin Ming. After leaving the shop, he and Xiao Moxian flew to the central VIP hall.

The entire VIP hall was made with timeless god stones. Lin Ming showed a jade slip with at least 50 million contribution points and smoothly entered.

As soon as he entered the VIP hall, everything became completely different.

The VIP hall lacked the ruckus from outside and there weren’t as many people. Within the entire hall, a rich medicinal fragrance wafted about; this was the fragrance of the heavenly materials everywhere.

Lin Ming took a deep breath. He had high accomplishments in alchemy and immediately ascertained that the pills which could release such a smell would sell for at least 50 million.

This filled Lin Ming with anticipation as he entered the VIP hall. Here, perhaps he really could find the dragon saliva grass and jade dragon horn he needed.

Chapter 1620 – Divine Void Duke

“Sir, may I ask how I can help you?”

After Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian entered the VIP hall, a beautiful maid welcomed them. The treatment within the VIP hall was completely different from the outside.

“I want a list of the treasures in the VIP hall.”

Lin Ming glanced at the maid. The maids in the VIP hall all wore uniforms and they had the emblem of the Runic Pill Trading Company embroidered on their chests.

Soon after, the maid handed a jade slip to Lin Ming. Just as Lin Ming was about to search through it, his heart chilled. In that moment he had felt someone’s sense pass swiftly and gently over him.

This sense was decidedly covert. If it wasn’t for Lin Ming’s powerful soul force then he wouldn’t have noticed it.

Lin Ming frowned. Just who was investigating him?

That brief sense just now was icy cold, as if it harbored dark intentions.

Lin Ming held the jade slip and quietly swept his sense outwards, probing the crowd in the hall. But, he wasn’t able to determine where this sense had come from.

This caused Lin Ming to be increasingly wary. This meant the person’s strength was even above his!

“If this person is so strong, could they be a Great World King?”

Lin Ming was left puzzled. He had lived in seclusion within the Blue Moon Sect for over 20 years, only studying the divine runic arts and alchemy. After he left he went to Divine Rune City where he painstakingly researched for over a year.

During this time period, Lin Ming didn’t think that he had provoked any enemies. As for his previous enemies, Tian Mingzi and Naqi had already been killed by him. As for Heaven’s Net, they shouldn’t have any reason to keep focusing on him after 20 years of not doing anything. Moreover, if they wanted to do anything to him they would have to heavily weigh the consequences.

Lin Ming felt that there shouldn’t be anyone focusing on him, so how come there was someone locking onto him as he was buying materials?

“Brother Lin, what is it?”

Xiao Moxian asked. She discovered that there was something unusual with Lin Ming.

“Nothing, there’s just someone snooping on me and their boundary is very high.” Lin Ming said, keeping an eye out for anyone strange, “But there’s no need to worry about this person. As long as we’re in Divine Rune City there’s nothing he can do against us. We just need to pay a little attention to this and we’ll be fine. This person will jump out on their own volition sooner or later.”

As Lin Ming spoke, his eyes brightened. Because of that unfriendly sense he hadn’t paid much attention to the jade slip. But now that he looked at it again, there were several things listed that caught his interest.

Among these items was a top spirit treasure called a Dragon Contract, and the material used to refine this spirit treasure was the jade dragon horn that Lin Ming needed!

“A hundred million year Jade Dragon and the blood marrow within the dragon horn is completely preserved, that’s extremely rare! Unfortunately it was already refined into a spirit treasure so it is far more expensive than the original materials. Even so, I must buy it. This type of rare and precious material can only be found through a stroke of fate.”

Lin Ming only wanted to take the jade dragon horn for alchemy. As for the spirit treasure, he would need to discard it no matter how good it was. It was truly a pity.

“It looks like the 2 billion contribution points I’ve gathered won’t be enough… there are many things on this list that I need. At that time, if I spend all my points on materials and miss out on all the other good things, that would be too unfortunate…”

Lin Ming made a quick calculation. The 2 billion points he gathered suddenly wasn’t enough.

He lacked too many contribution points!

“Xian’er, let’s see what quality that jade dragon horn is like.”

“Okay!” Xiao Moxian said. Like this, the two of them walked towards the exhibition of the Dragon Contract.

And as Lin Ming walked away, not too far from them there was a VIP rest room, covered with intricate array formations that isolated all sense.

The stylized floor was covered with fur rugs made from ancient vicious beasts. There was a tea table placed atop the rugs and this tea table was surrounded by several men and women, all of them slowly sipping tea.

A beautiful maid knelt on the rug, pouring tea for those present. Her tea skills were intricate and beautiful.

“I just bought some dark rain flower tea at this treasure fair. 100,000 points for one tael. Dark rain flowers can only be picked once every 10,000 years, and only after being cooked together with 72 different kinds of heavenly materials can this type of top grade dark rain flower tea be made. This tea is wonderful. The points spent weren’t wasted at all.”

The one who spoke was a blue-clothed man. He was dressed ordinarily and looked like a mortal scholar. His cultivation was obscured and it was difficult to see his depths.

And sitting beside him were several young men and women. These people all wore top grade vestments and golden crowns. Their foundations were solid and their looks were outstanding; it was clear they were elites among elites, and even so these people clearly looked towards the blue-clothed man with respect.

Around the tea table, besides the several young men and women, there was also an old man wrapped in a black cloak. His entire body exuded a grim atmosphere and he seemed profoundly mysterious.

“Old Shadow, what is it… you seemed to have something on your mind…” The blue-clothed man looked at the black-cloaked old man, smiling as he spoke. “This is wonderful tea, it will cool soon…”

“It’s nothing. I just saw someone I’m not too happy about…” The black-cloaked man grimly said. Although his face was cloaked in darkness, one could still see a pair of sharp eyes like those of an eagle.

As the black-cloaked old man spoke, the blue-clothed man’s eyebrows arched up. “What person could make Old Shadow be so unhappy?”

“Hehe…” The black-cloaked old man’s lips twitched and he dismally chuckled. “A young boy who came from who knows where, he was able to create a fourth grade divine runic symbol that could be used multiple times. It’s called the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol. Duke Fullmoon, you must have heard of this person already.”

“It’s Lin Ming?”

“Right, it’s him!” The black-cloaked old man said, not too willing to mention this name. This person called Duke Fullmoon began to laugh, “Old Shadow, it seems you’ve taken your defeat of copying the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol to heart. You can be called the number one master amongst dark divine runic masters, but the reason you failed can’t be blamed on yourself. I estimate that it must be an issue with the inheritance of this young man called Lin Ming...”

Duke Fullmoon candidly said. The black-cloaked old man sitting in front of him was Grandmaster Overflow, who had failed to copy the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol over half a year ago.

Grandmaster Overflow’s name was Shadow Overflow. It was just that very few people knew his name.

The treasure fair held by the Divine Runic Masters Guild was one of the grandest events of the inner Asura Road. As a dark divine runic master, Overflow naturally wouldn’t miss out on such festivities. He was also counting on this treasure fair to find some rare and precious materials as well as other treasures.

But, the reputation of a dark divine runic master was too sour to the ears. Many orthodox divine runic masters who considered themselves righteous were nearly unable to coexist with dark divine runic masters. As someone who lived in the dark world, if Shadow Overflow wanted to attend the treasure fair he could only hide his status.

“Inheritance…” Shadow Overflow’s eyes shined with a cold light. He had also thought of this point before.

Shadow Overflow’s feelings towards Lin Ming could be described as utter hate.

Although Lin Ming had never deliberately provoked Shadow Overflow, it was because of Lin Ming’s Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols that Shadow Overflow lost 200 million points in array discs! Not just that, but his reputation had suffered a massive blow!

Now, it had become known in the entire dark divine runic master community that Grandmaster Overflow had lost to a brat in the divine runic arts. This left him even more depressed.

And as representatives of the Divine Runic Masters Guild, those orthodox divine runic masters all viewed Shadow Overflow as a joke.

How could Shadow Overflow be happy with all of this? All of the unfortunate events that happened to him had been thanks to Lin Ming. Thus, even if Lin Ming hadn’t left the Divine Runic Masters Guild for over a year, he had still somehow managed to inexplicably make an enemy.

In these past several months, Shadow Overflow specifically gathered information related to Lin Ming. He was able to see Lin Ming’s appearance through a phantom image and thus was able to recognize him.

“Lin Ming… Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol…” Duke Fullmoon stirred his tea with the cup lid, his lips curving up in a grin.

Seeing Duke Fullmoon’s expression, Shadow Overflow’s thoughts stirred as he guessed something.

“Duke Fullmoon, have you taken a liking to Lin Ming’s inheritance?”

“Haha!” Duke Fullmoon laughed out loud. “That’s right, this young man called Lin Ming seems to have started studying the divine runic arts not too long ago. He should be in possession of a unique inheritance completely different from what is known today. And, I value this inheritance very much! If Lin Ming was able to improve the Havoc Flame Symbol, it must be because of this inheritance. Old Shadow had never come into contact with Lin Ming’s school of technique and thus didn’t understand his type of inheritance, so it’s natural for you to have failed.

“So, Old Shadow didn’t lose to a young man like Lin Ming, but to the mysterious inheritance behind him!”

As Duke Fullmoon said this, Shadow Overflow’s complexion became slightly better. After all, he didn’t believe that a junior like Lin Ming could surpass him in attainments of the divine runic arts. If he lost, it had to be because of this strange inheritance.

Duke Fullmoon said, “I suspect that this inheritance Lin Ming studies has a special method that allows divine runic symbols to be used repeatedly. But, Lin Ming has only managed to transform a Havoc Flame Symbol and the value of that isn’t too heaven-defying. No matter how strong a peak fourth grade divine runic symbol is, it is still a fourth grade divine runic symbol.

“For this inheritance to be left in Lin Ming’s hands is too great a waste. But if it were in my hands then I would be able to display its full abilities!”

As Duke Fullmoon spoke, his eyes shined with a dazzling light.

Shadow Overflow cackled, his heart moved to happiness. “Duke Fullmoon is indeed bold. I also wish to obtain this boy’s inheritance, but it seems there is a powerful master standing behind him, thus I haven’t dared to act rashly.”

Hearing this, Duke Fullmoon laughed dismissively, thinking little of it. “His master is just an Empyrean, right? Even a great influence like the Divine Runic Masters Guild or the Extreme Star Holy Lands wouldn’t dare to offend an Empyrean, but for my Divine Void Divine Kingdom, it’s just a little bit of trouble. It’s not considered much at all.”

Duke Fullmoon was fully confident in his words and he had the capital to be confident. Although his strength was only that of a World King, he had the backing of Divine Void Divine Kingdom. And, Divine Void Divine Kingdom was a True Divinity level influence!

In the past, the two greatest peak Empyreans of the spiritas were Divine Mist and Divine Void!

These two peak Empyreans were blood brothers, but afterwards, Divine Mist went missing and Divine Void stepped into the realm of True Divinity. From that point on, the myth of Divine Void Divine Kingdom was born!

Speaking to here, Duke Fullmoon stood up and said, “We’re leaving. Old Shadow, let’s go and meet this Lin Ming!”

Chapter 1624 – Soul Recovery Symbol

Within the divine runic room, the air was hot like boiling magma. The heat manifested in curling crimson red undulations of energy, the temperature so high it left one staggering for breath.

Even the light within this room was twisted like waves due to the high heat.

Even though this was a seventh grade divine runic room with many spells and array formations surrounding it, a massive amount of the power of fire still radiated outside.

And the source of this tremendous power of fire was the discarded pieces of materials scattered over the floor, materials used for the Heavenly Fire Symbol.

Lin Ming was far too exhausted. Even a thin layer of salt had appeared on his eyebrows from the amount of evaporated sweat.

In these past several days he had almost never closed his eyes. The closer the treasure fair was, the more he was forced to seize every second of time available to him. Without the wealth of a powerful influence backing him, he could only rely on himself.

To Lin Ming, the spirit medicines and spirit treasures at the treasure fair were all astronomically expensive!

Soul force continually flowed out from his fingertips, manipulating the divine runic pen as it left traces of light and shadow in space. Using the extracted juice of materials, Lin Ming left behind lines of tiny runes in the void.

Every tiny line left behind a glowing brilliance and emitted a power of fire that wilted the mind.

Every single stroke of the runes required an immaculate level of technical skill. The tiniest deviation would lead to the flame patterns coming into conflict with each other and then exploding.

After Lin Ming absorbed the memories of three divine runic masters, when combined with his profound understanding of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws as well as his current skill in the divine runic arts, theoretically speaking his chances of failing to successfully draw up a divine runic symbol were extremely low. Moreover, he had also successfully drawn up the improved Heavenly Fire Symbol and Heretical God Symbol before.

But the production of these two divine runic symbols was the pinnacle of Lin Ming’s understanding into the theory behind divine runic symbols as well as the peak of his current skill level.

Thus, if he wanted to draw up the improved Heavenly Fire Symbol and Heretical God Symbol once again, every step he did would push him to the limit.

Constantly chasing after his limits was a rapidly tiring matter.

These two divine runic symbols had an extremely high fusion compatibility with the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws. Every tiny stroke of the runes formed a mosaic that was able to combine and shift together to form an exponential number of changes.

The slightest mistake would create damage to the overall structure of tiny runes, possibly even causing an explosion.

This meant that Lin Ming needed to invest every ounce of focus into his work, to concentrate every thought into controlling the divine runic pen.

During a sustained period of high concentration it was easy to consume a massive amount of soul force. If Lin Ming hadn’t cultivated Empyrean Divine Mist’s soul force cultivation method and had his previous soul force intensity, he would definitely be far too tired to do anything and might have even caused permanent damage to his soul!

In the history of divine runic arts, there were some divine runic masters that in order to draw up a peerlessly powerful and infinitely marvelous divine runic symbol, would directly consume their mind and soul and die in their divine runic room.

The improved Heavenly Fire Symbol that Lin Ming was drawing, in terms of difficulty and finesse required, was enough to annihilate the mind of a fourth grade divine runic master.

The original Heavenly Fire Symbol had more than 800 flame-based tiny runes combined, and there were countless array formation marks within. But, Lin Ming’s improved Heavenly Fire Symbol had over a thousand flame-based tiny runes added within, as well as over 10,000 elaborate array formation marks interspersed throughout. This allowed the Heavenly Fire Symbol to have channels that were able to absorb the power of fire even more smoothly.

These profound changes made the difficulty of drawing up a Heavenly Fire Symbol exponentially greater than before. All of these new additions required Lin Ming to consume an enormous amount of soul force.

There was no need to mention the changes Lin Ming made in the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws. The original Heavenly Fire Symbol had an extremely rough and crude implementation of the Asura Heavenly Dao. Within it, only several rune paths conformed with the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws.

As for Lin Ming’s changes, he completely eliminated all previous rune paths that corresponded to the Asura Heavenly Dao, and planted in 108 new rune paths in their place.

These modifications, if seen by other divine runic masters, would truly shock the world. Some lower level divine runic masters would find it impossible to understand.

The consequences of these complex changes were a massive increase in the use of soul force as well as endless and constant calculations during the drawing process.

Even if Lin Ming had successfully produced a Heavenly Fire Symbol once, there would occasionally be a slight deviation in the flame-based runes at the start, finally causing there to be a conflict with the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws that were fused into it.

Finally, a massive fire dragon would blow up from the tiny runes, causing the entire divine runic symbol to be ruined.

If it weren’t for Xiao Moxian standing guard on the side and quickly responding, and swallowing the fire dragons with the Darkness Laws, then Lin Ming’s eyebrows and most of his hair would have been burnt away.

“3972 flexible array lines, conforming to the right spiral revolution of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws…” Lin Ming mumbled to himself, all of his concentration focused on the floating lines of flames in the air.

Finally, the long lines of flames were pulled into the top of the Heavenly Fire Symbol.

The entire Heavenly Fire Symbol erupted with a blazing light. The lines of the flame runes rapidly decomposed, gathering onto the tiny runes within and then combining once more…

Another two hours passed.

The reformed flame runes began to fuse with the lines of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws in the air.

With a brief flash, all of the surging energies vanished at once.

All that was left in Lin Ming’s hand was a simple and plain Heavenly Fire Symbol that sparkled with a strange light.

The Heavenly Fire Symbol seemed ordinary and rough, without even the slightest power of fire leaking out.

If other divine runic masters were to see this, they would certainly sing praises to the heavens! To create a Heavenly Fire Symbol that didn’t have the slightest bit of energy flowing out, this required a deeply profound understanding and control of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws. All of that power of fire needed to be forcefully locked inside.

Pada!

A drop of sweat fell down from the tip of Lin Ming’s nose. Before it hit the ground, the drop of sweat was already evaporated by the high heat.

Lin Ming finally opened his eyes, letting out a long breath of relief.

Xiao Moxian smiled like a blooming flower, finally relaxing a little.

“The Heavenly Fire Symbol is finished… do you want to rest a little?” Xiao Moxian’s worried eyes looked at Lin Ming.

Lin Ming confidently smiled. He shook his head and said, “No need. I’ll be fine after I practice the Divine Mist Heart Mantra.”

“You’re being too hard on yourself…” Xiao Moxian whispered. But, she knew that once Lin Ming decided to do something it was nearly impossible for anyone else to change his mind.

Moreover, she also knew that he was pressed for time. Every step Lin Ming made was to prepare for the future war with the saint race in the Divine Realm.

Thinking of these future matters, a desolate and sad look passed through her face. Divine Realm… saint race… monster race… to her, this was a knot in her heart that she couldn’t undo.

Dong! Dong! Dong!

A knocking sound echoed out from the front door.

“Sir Lin.” Suya’s dark and sensual voice transmitted from the other side of the door.

Xiao Moxian suddenly frowned deeply, her body immediately straightening up. A faint sense of hostility flashed over her face. When a beautiful woman met another beautiful woman, it wasn’t unlikely for sparks to occur, especially when there was a man involved.

Lin Ming also wrinkled his eyebrows. He didn’t like being disturbed by outsiders when he was deep in drawing up divine runic symbols.

“What is it?” Lin Ming coldly asked, patiently holding back his temper.

“The great lord Empyrean of our Extreme Star Holy Lands knows that Sir Lin has been busy with many matters these days and has been working hard on the divine runic arts, so he has bid me send you some Soul Recovery Symbols.”

Soul Recovery Symbols?

Lin Ming was startled as he heard this. A Soul Recovery Symbol was an extremely complex divine runic symbol. In order to create one, one needed the special condensed soul crystals of the spiritas and then to add in the Soul Recovery Laws of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws.

This sort of divine runic symbol was expensive and not too practical. Normally, only divine runic masters near the seventh grade, half-step spiritas Empyreans, or other characters of that level would use these divine runic symbols, because drawing one up required a peak sixth grade divine runic master.

For the current Lin Ming, meditating on the Divine Mist Heart Mantra was a waste of his time. If he had these Soul Recovery Symbols to supplement him then it would really be a useful gift that came at the right time.

As long as this type of supportive divine runic symbol was fused into his body he would be able to rapidly recover his soul force.

Without needing Lin Ming to speak, Xiao Moxian had already opened the front door without reservation.

Her hostility to this seductive temptress Suya was one matter, but these Soul Recovery Symbols that could help Lin Ming were another.

As long as it was something that could help Lin Ming, she wouldn’t refuse it.

As the front door opened, a strange and intoxicating scent rushed in, accompanied with the gentle tinkling of bells.

Suya’s casual dress was provocative enough, but today she was especially dressed up. She wore a long and silky dress that was cut low at the chest, exposing her curvy figure. Her majestic chest was proud and full as a startling amount of snowy white skin was exposed.

Her earrings were made from strange crystals, mysteriously polished so that they exuded a dazzling light. When combined with her pouty looks, every movement of hers exuded a captivating scent.

She carried a plate with both hands that was stacked with divine runic symbols carrying a dark strength.

Slowly stepping into the room, Suya maintained a trace of a smile. Her star-bright eyes were mesmerizing.

Of course, this brilliant gaze was focused on the improved Heavenly Fire Symbol that Lin Ming just drew up.

Suya had stayed in the Divine Runic Masters Guild for a long time and experienced many things. As she saw the improved Heavenly Fire Symbol and the complex runes that still floated like rivers of stars in the sky, her eyes shined even brighter. This divine runic symbol was absolutely not simple.

Suya smiled and then placed the plate of Soul Recovery Symbols in front of Lin Ming. Behind her, Xiao Moxian was running out of patience.

As Xiao Moxian saw Suya’s round and perky bottom from behind, she couldn’t help but feel inexplicably annoyed.

“Miss Suya, we are currently in the process of researching and developing a new divine runic symbol, so we are a little busy at the moment. We thank you for the favor of sending these Soul Recovery Symbols and we will remember this.” Xiao Moxian was well aware that the goal of Suya sending Soul Recovery Symbols here was nothing more than an attempt to curry favor with Lin Ming in order to obtain even greater benefits in the future. If Lin Ming wasn’t anybody at all, they definitely wouldn’t bother with him.

Thus, although Xiao Moxian’s words were polite, they had an undertone of seeing a guest out.

Chapter 1625 – The Auctions Begin

Suya wasn’t some weakling to be pushed around. She could hear the meaning behind Xiao Moxian’s words and tone so she turned to Lin Ming and cast him a winsome smile. “Sir Lin, this is quite embarrassing to ask, but may I ask what divine runic symbol you are researching right now?” As she spoke she bent down and curiously looked at the improved divine runic symbol.

Suya propped her hands against the divine runic table. Her plunging deep neckline originally revealed a deep snow white valley, and after bending down, her large and explosive mountains swayed back and forth like surging pendulums.

Sitting on the other side of the divine runic table, Lin Ming never imagined he would see such a scene. He was slightly surprised as he inevitably got a clear look at Suya’s beautiful scenery. This sort of temptation, if a young divine runic master were to see it, would cause their blood to boil. And even though Lin Ming wasn’t too affected he was still momentarily stunned by what he saw.

At this time, Suya was simply far too close to Lin Ming. As for Lin Ming, he simply had nowhere to look away to. And as he was wondering what he should do, he suddenly noticed a chilling cold rise up. He couldn’t help but look at the direction of that icy cold air.

All he saw was Xiao Moxian glaring at Suya, her entire face covered with black lines, seeming as if she was on the verge of storming out. To attempt to seduce Lin Ming right in front of her, this woman simply didn’t place her in her eyes!

As Lin Ming felt Xiao Moxian’s burgeoning anger, he coughed loudly and pushed himself away from the divine runic table, quickly retreating. “Miss Suya, I am indeed trying to revise a divine runic symbol. If there aren’t any other matters, I want to try to grasp the time to draw up several more. These Soul Recovery Symbols have come at the perfect time. I will remember this sentiment.”

Lin Ming was also hinting for his guest to see her way out. It wasn’t only because of Xiao Moxian, but also because he really was far too busy.

“Heavenly Fire Symbol? This is a Heavenly Fire Symbol? There isn’t any power of fire leaking out!” After entering Lin Ming’s divine runic room with great difficulty, Suya naturally wouldn’t leave until she investigated for some information. She couldn’t help but gently touch the improved Heavenly Fire Symbol. As she discovered the peculiarities inside, she exclaimed out loud.

In her opinion, every Heavenly Fire Symbol would inevitably have a certain amount of energy flowing out of it. The higher the grade a divine runic master who created the divine runic symbol was, the more complex the rune structure would be, the more exquisite the Law lines, and the less strength that would flow out. This was a manifestation of a divine runic master’s ability to control a divine runic symbol.

She had rarely encountered this situation before where there wasn’t any energy flowing out from a divine runic symbol. This proved to her that Lin Ming’s ability to confine the energy of the divine runes had reached an astonishing degree.

Suya suppressed her surprise; she had already accomplished her goal for coming here. She faintly smiled at Lin Ming and said, “Sir Lin, then I will not disturb you from drawing up divine runic symbols.”

Then, her eyes narrowed, curving up like crescent moons in the skies, enchanting and alluring. “I would also like to ask Sir Lin to consider our Extreme Star Holy Lands and sell this improved Heavenly Fire Symbol to us in the future. The price can be further discussed.”

Lin Ming thought for a moment. The Extreme Star Holy Lands could be considered an old customer of his. If he really did sell divine runic symbols, he would have intentions of selling to them. But, he had a special plan for these two divine runic symbols that he was creating now.

“I am not too familiar with producing these divine runic symbols. If I can produce them en masse I will consider you.” Lin Ming didn’t confirm anything as he kept his words ambiguous.

Suya’s eyes shined as she heard this. As long as Lin Ming said this, she would have something to report to the Extreme Star Holy Lands.

The previous batches of Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols had miraculous and wondrous effects on the battlefield. This caused Suya to withstand a great deal of pressure from the high level figures of the Extreme Star Holy Lands, making her feel pressed for time.

Now, all she could do was keep track of Lin Ming.

“Then I won’t disturb Sir Lin. If there is anything you need, please inform me. As long as I can accomplish it, I will definitely try to help Sir Lin as much as I can.” Suya threw one last smile towards Lin Ming. Lin Ming nodded in return. Then, with a twirl of her dress, Suya turned and left.

It was only that as Suya passed by Xiao Moxian, her eyes flashed and she raised her proud swan-like neck, her gaze touching upon Xiao Moxian.

Xiao Moxian returned this gaze with eyes that could kill. Her small canines were sharp like a little tiger’s, reflecting an icy cold brightness.

As the two women’s eyes met, an intense electric light sparked in the void.

With a bang, the door closed.

As Suya’s footsteps gradually faded away, Xiao Moxian slowly pursed her lips. She shot Lin Ming a look, her complexion still gloomy. She didn’t think that Suya was more beautiful than she was, but Suya’s figure had the flavor of a ripe peach, explosive and bursting from the seams. This was an attribute that Xiao Moxian completely lacked; her figure was more slender and smooth.

“Disgusting woman.” Xiao Moxian indignantly sputtered out.

Lin Ming coughed. Without saying anything, he picked up a divine runic pen.

Over the next half month, Lin Ming invested all of his time and focus in producing the improved Heavenly Fire Symbol and the Heretical God Symbol.

These divine runic symbols were far more complex than the previous Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol.

Every time he drew one up he would have to put in seven to eight times the effort of producing a Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol. Moreover, what gave Lin Ming a headache the most was that the failure rate was far too high!

In the first few days the failure rate reached as high as 70-80%. With this rate, Lin Ming could only draw up a single divine runic symbol in one day.

Even half a month later, his failure rate only fell to 50%.

This was also with the batch of Soul Recovery Symbols that Suya had provided. With their wonderful effects of revitalizing the divine soul, every time Lin Ming felt his soul force on the verge of collapse he would absorb one Soul Recovery Symbol and feel his soul force rapidly restore itself.

Time quickly passed.

In the final two days before the treasure fair began, Lin Ming didn’t take a single moment of rest. Every time a Heavenly Fire Symbol failed and exploded, not only would Lin Ming’s clothes tear apart but even the nearby strange and amusing Xiao Moxian would find her face completely blackened with soot. When combined her two white canines, this was an especially entertaining sight.

But in the end, Lin Ming still produced 10 improved Heavenly Fire Symbols and 10 Heretical God Symbols.

In the early morning of the next day, as the sky was bright and the sun was dawning, countless crowds of people had gathered in Divine Rune City.

As Xiao Moxian and Lin Ming left the Divine Runic Masters Guild they were able to see the tides of people flying through the skies, like swarms of locusts!

Only during the period of the treasure fair would Divine Rune City allow martial artists to fly, because the treasure fair was held in the floating castle. Due to this, this miraculous scene could be viewed.

The floating castle was a hundred miles wide and flew high in the air. Even so, the innumerable martial artists surrounding it were like motes of dust!

Although he had barely managed to catch a night of rest, Lin Ming was still feeling the aftereffects of overdrawing his soul force for an entire month. Now that he suddenly left his room, the dazzling sunlight made even Lin Ming feel a bout of dizziness. It took him a moment to adapt to the brilliant dappled sunlight.

“There really is a great deal of people here.” Looking at this scene in front of him, Lin Ming was startled. With so many people it was hard to imagine just how high the volume of trade transactions would be.

Taking Xiao Moxian’s hand, Lin Ming once more flew into the treasure fair in the flying castle. At this time, he suddenly had a strange feeling.

He could clearly feel that as he arrived at the treasure fair, the entire floating castle rippled with a thick power of divine runic symbols.

These were a type of hidden defensive divine runic symbols that were fused into the spirit stone of the castle. If anyone attacked this castle, these defensive divine runic symbols would erupt with a terrifying defensive barrier.

Rows upon rows of stores were everywhere, with the treasures inside all outstanding. Compared to the last time Lin Ming was here, there were many more good items.

Just by smelling the rich medicinal fragrance in the air, he could tell that there were far more spirit medicines for sale.

However, the sale square which had been there before had been cleared out.

A massive complex hung in the center of it, shaped like an eight-sided honeycomb.

This building was like a miniature sun. it was covered with radiant glowing stones, swallowing up all surrounding shadows and shining with a noon light.

On all eight sides of this honeycomb structure, around every 10 miles, there was a giant massive illusory mirror that showed what was occurring within.

It was clear that this was an auction site. The staff inside were busily bustling about in preparation. However, it was clear from the hourglass that hung above the structure that there was only an hour left until the auction began.

Lin Ming had already received the news. From today forth, the most precious items of the treasure fair would all be sold in the auction.

As for the item shops outside, the things they sold were far from comparable to the heavenly treasures sold in the auction house.

It was inevitable that the jade dragon horn he needed would appear there, and it was even possible that the dragon saliva grass would too. After all, these were materials that top divine runic masters wanted and their price would definitely soar as the divine runic masters fought for them!

As Lin Ming was thinking, he heard a giggle burst out from the entrance.

“Duke Fullmoon also came, haha… the pressure on a little girl like me is far too great. I hope that Duke Fullmoon won’t snatch something from my hands…”

Duke Fullmoon?

This laughter was also quite familiar. Lin Ming couldn’t help but follow these sounds and be surprised as he caught sight of a few familiar faces… how could these people have gathered together?

The few people at the entrance were surrounded by a group of extremely muscular and vigorous guards.

Of the people being guarded, one of them was a tall and graceful woman, a peerless beauty of her generation. She had been the one smiling and laughing – it was Miss Suya from the Divine Runic Masters Guild.

Beside Miss Suya was a blue-clothed man, a faintly happy smile on his face. His eyes burned as they occasionally dipped down to her swaying figure before slowly coming back up to her face.

Behind this blue-clothed man was a slow and creeping black-cloaked old man.

The old man’s complexion was gloomy and dark. It was only when Suya and the blue-clothed man occasionally laughed out loud that the old man would join in with a few terse and hollow laughs. It was hard to tell from his complexion whether he was irritated or not.

The blue-clothed man and the black-cloaked old man were the two people that Lin Ming bumped into when he last visited the treasure fair.

For them to meet again was also inevitable, because there were many treasures at this auction that the blue-clothed man had to obtain no matter what.

Chapter 1629 – Ancient Pill In Hand

“Hehe… Duke Fullmoon has calculated well. If I’m not wrong then this Lin Ming needs the nameless ancient pill. He is a human as well as someone who dual cultivates body and energy; this ancient pill could be called perfectly suited for him. Because of that, it will be easy to ruin him!”

In the VIP suite, Shadow Overflow cackled. His laugh had a strangely eerie feel to it.

According to their information, Lin Ming’s wealth didn’t surpass 2 billion. If Lin Ming were to buy the ancient pill for over a billion then there wouldn’t be any threat from him later on.

“900 million!”

Lin Ming suddenly increased the bid by 50 million.

However, Duke Fullmoon didn’t stop here. He shouted out, “910 million!”

The two times he bid were only 10 million higher than Lin Ming’s bid price. It seemed that he intended to purposefully hinder him.

“950 million!” Lin Ming shouted out again.

“960 million!” In the VIP suite, Duke Fullmoon laughed out loud. To have Lin Ming spend even a hundred million more with just a little bit of effort, this caused him to be in a very good mood.

And at this time, in an ordinary room, Xiao Moxian’s face was cold to the point of developing frost. She was just a step away from violently rushing out.

“Big Brother Lin, this damned dead fly is deliberately targeting you! He doesn’t want to buy that pill, he just wants to waste your points. If this continues then you are only throwing away your hard earned wealth.”

Lin Ming nodded. “That’s right. He wants to annoy me and use up my resources, but he won’t have the courage to continually follow me.”

Lin Ming had a set price in mind for this pill and that was that he wouldn’t surpass 1.2 billion. This was a limit that Duke Fullmoon wasn’t aware of.

Lin Ming could use this to his advantage.

“990 million.” Lin Ming added another 30 million. He called out this bid so that Duke Fullmoon would bid a billion.

According to Lin Ming’s estimate, a billion points surpassed the limit that this pill would sell for at the auction.

And Duke Fullmoon did as Lin Ming thought he would. He drawlingly called out, “One billion. Haha, that friend in the ordinary room, do you really want to struggle with me?”

Duke Fullmoon insolently said. His voice spread far as if he were intentionally trying to anger Lin Ming.

He thought that Lin Ming would shout out another price and then he could disturb Lin Ming several more times, causing him to lose even more wealth, but he didn’t think that Lin Ming wouldn’t speak up again.

Lin Ming seemed to suddenly quiet down in the ordinary room he was in, no longer shouting out a price.

“Guest #24 has put forth a bid of one billion! The first item of this auction has already broken through a billion! Is there anyone willing to bid higher?”

On the auction stage, Song Wen spoke with zealous fervor.

However, no one in the auction seats responded. The psychology of people was quite subtle. 990 million was only 10 million away from a billion, but crossing this gap gave two completely different feelings.

To spend a billion points to buy this ancient pill, the price to performance ratio of this was far too low.

Song Wen shouted out one more time but there still wasn’t a response. When it came to some auctions of the highest caliber like this one, even a magnificent auctioneer could only play a limited effect in increasing the price.

Let alone Song Wen, even if Suya put on her most sexually appealing attire and did her best to arouse enthusiasm and seduce the audience, she still wouldn’t have much of an effect.

The VIP guests who could afford to bid upon this nameless ancient pill were all powerful figures of their great influences or were absurdly strong. So, which one of these people would toss away a billion points just to win the smile of a beautiful woman?

“One billion, going once!”

Song Wen began to announce.

Hearing these words, Duke Fullmoon felt his heart skip a beat.

He didn’t want to buy this nameless ancient pill. This was something used by humans and was suited for martial artists that dual cultivated body and energy. As a spiritas, whether it was him or the Divine Void Divine Kingdom behind him, no one needed this ancient pill.

If he bought something that wasn’t of much use he could only pay for it from his own pockets. It was impossible for him to use the wealth of Divine Void Divine Kingdom to pay for this ancient pill and his pockets weren’t so large that he could disregard a loss of a billion points.

If he obtained the ancient pill the only thing he could do was resell it. But no matter who he sold it to, he wouldn’t be able to match the price that it sold for at this auction.

But this wasn’t the crucial issue. The key problem was that it would take a long time afterwards for him to resell this nameless ancient pill. This would make it so that the wealth he had to spend in this auction would diminish by a great deal. If something truly amazing were to appear later he might not be able to afford it!

And even if he thought of using Divine Void Divine Kingdom’s wealth to buy something he wanted, that would be something that belonged to the Divine Void Divine Kingdom, not him.

“One billion, going twice!”

Song Wen counted down once more. Duke Fullmoon’s pulse began to race. He looked up towards the top two VIP suites, hoping that Empyrean Lionheart or Empyrean Minor Violet would be interested in this ancient pill. However, the two VIP suites were quiet from beginning to end, as if they never even heard anything.

To an Empyrean, this nameless ancient pill wasn’t of much use at all.

Empyreans could refine their own transcendent divine pills, but more than that, eating up a transcendent divine pill wasn’t too beneficial to their own cultivation.

Many Empyreans had been stranded at their boundaries for a long time and had been unable to break through. Wanting to rely on a simple transcendent divine pill to make massive leaps in their cultivation was the talk of a babbling moron.

Seeing Song Wen count down a third time, Duke Fullmoon felt as if he had eaten a fly.

He felt like he had been stupidly tricked.

He thought of ruining Lin Ming but he hadn’t considered Lin Ming’s wealth enough.

Although Lin Ming wanted this nameless ancient pill, he might not be able to afford that sky high price!

“That poor fool, he doesn’t have any capital to struggle with the Duke. What an idiot to compete for treasures.” Nestled in Duke Fullmoon’s chest, Junior-apprentice Sister Qing had a proud expression as she tenderly smiled. Her talent could only be considered decent and wanting to stand out in Divine Void Divine Kingdom was impossible. If she wanted to rise above the crowds she needed to attach herself to someone with authority and potential, such as Duke Fullmoon. Now, she had increasingly felt that she had chosen the correct person.

With such a grand auction that gathered innumerable heroes and even two Empyreans, the man she chose had domineeringly bid on the first item of the auction, forcing out all people so that no one dared to shout a higher price.

Originally Duke Fullmoon was already upset, but now this brainless woman was trying to flatter him for no reason at all, causing him to be even more irritated and ashamed of himself. He shoved the flirting woman away, roaring, “Get out!”

Junior-apprentice Sister Qing was pushed rolling away and nearly struck the wall. She was frightened; she had no idea just why Duke Fullmoon had suddenly become so angry.

And at this time, just as Song Wen was about to begin his final countdown, someone shouted out a bid from the ordinary rooms. “One billion… and ten million!”

This voice was heavy, as if the bidder couldn’t bear this price at all.

And as this voice entered Duke Fullmoon’s ears, it was like the melodious call of heaven.

He let out a long sigh of relief, finally saved at the last moment. He looked towards the room that shouted out this price and saw that it was indeed Lin Ming.

Duke Fullmoon’s complexion darkened. This item had finally been won by Lin Ming.

At this time he didn’t dare to continue a bidding war with Lin Ming. With Lin Ming’s current wealth, this bidding price was likely his limit.

“This poor fool!”

Duke Fullmoon cursed out loud. He wanted to rip off Lin Ming some more, but he didn’t think Lin Ming would be so poor. Duke Fullmoon simply didn’t have the courage to continue.

After shouting out three bids and having to experience a brief bout of fear and trepidation only to cause Lin Ming to lose a hundred million plus points, Duke Fullmoon wasn’t too happy.

Then, Shadow Overflow chuckled. “The truth is that Duke’s goal has already been accomplished. During this first auction, 60-70% of Lin Ming’s wealth has been removed… after this he shouldn’t pose much of a threat anymore.”

Even though this was true, Duke Fullmoon didn’t feel too great.

“This brat Lin Ming seems to have already given up on the jade dragon horn. He’s smart enough, at least he knows when to give way. But, the only problem is that if he gives up the initiative like this then I can’t step on him later.”

Duke Fullmoon’s complexion sank. He wanted to roll over Lin Ming in the auction for the jade dragon horn, but now he felt as if he were punching nothing but pillows.

And at this time, Song Wen counted down a third time. The first item in this auction had been won by Lin Ming!

“Congratulations to this guest in ordinary room #36 for winning this nameless ancient pill from the Drifting Islands!” Song Wen loudly announced. There was a smattering of applause throughout the audience. Many people were startled. They didn’t think that there would be crouching tigers and hidden dragons amongst the ordinary rooms.

Chapter 1630 – Violet Gold Spear

According to the rules of the auction, the deadline for payments was ten days after the end of the auction.

If one took the treasures but didn’t pay, one would receive the severe retribution of Divine Rune City. Punishments involved being imprisoned for thousands or even tens of thousands of years.

Generally speaking, no one would do such a thing. This was because before entering the auction, one had to verify their identity with a status card. Those people with considerable status and weight in the world certainly wouldn’t do something so shameless.

“Then, onto the second auction item!”

Several elegantly-dressed women brought out a tall sandalwood box that was dozens of feet high. As Song Wen opened this box, everyone could see that it was a portable cave dwelling.

Lin Ming didn’t have any interest in this sort of thing; he already had Primordius Heavenly Palace.

The starting price of this cave dwelling was 20 million points. After the auction began, scattered bids arose from the audience. Finally, the one to win was a martial artist in an ordinary arena seat. This item was won with 35 million points.

After the cave dwelling, there were mystical treasures, contract beasts, medicines, pills, magic weapons, and all sorts of other things that were brought out one after another.

Of these items, some aroused Lin Ming’s interest. But as he considered the values of the items, he didn’t bid as he thought they weren’t worth the price.

This auction would continue for an entire month and was divided into several parts. Just the first round of the auction would last for three days and three nights.

To a martial artist, three days and three nights was less time than one spent in a bout of meditation.

As Lin Ming paid attention to the items that were being auctioned he also practiced the Divine Mist Heart Mantra. The reason Lin Ming was able to arrive at where he was, besides his luck and will, all of this was related to his diligence and hard work. Now, Lin Ming’s cultivation was a race against time. If this auction was to last for an entire month he naturally couldn’t stop cultivating.

But at this time, Song Wen brought out a black stone chest that piqued his interest.

This stone box seemed ordinary and simple, but Lin Ming could feel a faint and vast aura exuding from it.

As Song Wen slowly opened the stone box, a faint black light shot straight out, illuminating the arena. A cold killing intent spread out with it and Lin Ming’s body shook. As he gazed at that black light, he could feel something that resonated with his soul… spear potential!

“That’s a spear…”

Lin Ming was a professional veteran of spears. Before, the saint artifact Phoenix Blood Spear had accompanied him through his battles, slowly being tempered until it was finally reborn into a spirit treasure. It was a powerful spear that would continue to grow with him.

Thus when it came to spears, Lin Ming had a startling sense of acuity.

In the VIP suites, Duke Fullmoon stared at the item in the stone box, equally excited. It was just that the resonance in his heart was weaker than Lin Ming’s and he also had a sense of uncertainty.

“Empyrean level spirit treasure spear?”

Duke Fullmoon’s eyes shined.

“Empyrean spirit treasure? Duke, you are already at the World King realm and you also wield spears. The spear you’ve been using is nothing but an ordinary spirit artifact that cannot follow your rapid ascent. Now, this treasure here seems perfectly suited for the Duke. You must succeed in obtaining it!”

Junior-apprentice Sister Qing leaned into Duke Fullmoon and giggled. Even though she had been violently shoved away by Duke Fullmoon, she didn’t dare to display any temper at all. Her relationship with Duke Fullmoon was just like a mortal emperor and their concubine; since when would a concubine dare lose their temper with the emperor?

Duke Fullmoon didn’t seem to hear her words. He only continued staring at the black box.

Song Wen fiddle with something on the black stone chest. Then, strange runes lit up all around the black box, surging about with waves of energy as it automatically opened. Then, an intense brilliance exploded outwards like a dazzling sun as torrent of essence energy shot up into the skies!

A dragon-like golden spear burst out, humming in the void, emitting a pressure as deep as the sea!

“This is another precious item to be sold today, an Empyrean spirit treasure excavated from some Empyrean ruins – the Violet Gold Spear! The starting price is 800 million points!”

800 million was an extremely exaggerated number. But, an Empyrean spirit treasure was indeed worth this price!

A so-called Empyrean spirit treasure was not a treasure forged by an Empyrean, but a treasure that was raised and cultivated by an Empyrean.

It needed to be carried with an Empyrean, passing through millions of years of nourishment as it slowly transformed. In their lives, an Empyrean would raise at most several Empyrean spirit treasures. With their 100 million year lifespan, they wouldn’t produce over 10 such treasures.

For instance, Lin Ming’s Phoenix Blood Spear. When Lin Ming became an Empyrean and used all sorts of additional heavenly materials to refine his spear, he could receive it into his inner world and nourish it with his essence energy until it became an Empyrean spirit treasure.

But this was a very long process. It was impossible to do this without waiting millions of years.

It could only be said that Lin Ming grew too quickly. Even though Lin Ming’s Phoenix Blood Spear crossed through heavenly tribulation with him and developed an artifact spirit, when compared to Lin Ming’s heaven-defying growth, even the Phoenix Blood Spear couldn’t keep up.

When an Empyrean was living, they wouldn’t sell the Empyrean spirit treasures they cultivated even if offered 10 billion points. This was because only a weapon they raised themselves would be best suited for them.

It was only when an Empyrean died and their Empyrean spirit treasures become masterless treasures would these items be dug up from ruins by their descendants and then sold.

Song Wen took the gold spear in his hands. Holding this spear, the feeling was like he was grasping onto a golden dragon.

This spear was 12 foot long and was an overlord spear. In a sense it was more appropriate to call it a lance.

The golden spear’s shaft was covered with mystical lines. The spear head was dark black and red, emitting a sharp light that cut into the eyes.

“The spear shaft is covered with Asura Law lines, but what a pity… there are some places that are lacking…”

Lin Ming’s understanding into the Asura Heavenly Dao became increasingly deep with every passing day. He could see with a single glance what was wrong with the patterns on the golden spear shaft.

The Asura Heavenly Dao was incomparably mysterious to the martial artists of the Asura Road; no one could solve it. Even a seventh grade divine runic master could only summarize the knowledge of their predecessors to engrave array formations, but the truth was that they didn’t understand the essence of the Asura Heavenly Dao.

Because of this, it was impossible for them to draw up perfect Asura Heavenly Dao patterns.

“How unfortunate. That spear’s Buddha-killing aura is absolute and I have no idea how many powerhouses’ blood it has drunk. In addition, it was carried by an Empyrean level character for million of years and has developed a terrifying killing intent. It is wonderful in nearly all aspects. If only the Asura Heavenly Dao patterns on it were perfect then it would undergo a qualitative transformation!”

Lin Ming deeply sighed, feeling a bit regretful. The structure of this spear had already been finalized and it was impossible to change the Asura Heavenly Dao patterns on the spear shaft. Otherwise, if he were to try it would only cause more mistakes, resulting in an opposite effect and worsening it.

Moreover, there was something else. This spear shaft was forged with violet red golden crystals. These crystals were extremely expensive and extremely hard. If supported by an array formation then even a Great World King could give up all thoughts of crushing it.

Even so, violet red golden crystals lacked any elasticity. In other words, this violet gold spear was a hard spear. This meant that in Lin Ming’s eyes, its functionality dropped a great deal.

A hard spear without flexibility meant that there was no cushioning force. In a head-on collision of toughness, it was easy to be struck and injured by the shaking force.

Of course, even with these two disadvantages, this Violet Gold Spear was still far superior to Lin Ming’s own Phoenix Blood Spear!

If Lin Ming could switch spears he would certainly be willing to. After all, the Phoenix Blood Spear would take far too long to grow.

Currently, Lin Ming estimated that the final price of this spear would be around 1.2-1.4 billion points. But to Lin Ming, this price was far too high for the value he would receive. The most he could accept was a billion points, but this amount could only buy a spear shaft.

Lin Ming glanced outside his room at everyone else in the arena. He could see a fanatic greed in the eyes of the other martial artists as they stared at the Violet Gold Spear. It was clear they had a strong desire to buy that Violet Gold Spear!

A weapon on the level of an Empyrean spirit treasure was surpassingly rare! Even in this auction there wouldn’t be more than a few of them.

To find an Empyrean spirit treasure that suited oneself, this could only be called a stroke of fate.

“Let the auction begin!” Song Wen loudly proclaimed.

But just as Song Wen’s voice fell, someone shouted out loud from the VIP suites. “850 million!”

“860 million!”

There were many people that wanted to buy this Violet Gold Spear.

These people were mostly World King powerhouses, even Great World King powerhouses. Only this type of person had the ability to just barely move the powers of an Empyrean spirit treasure. As for those people of a lower boundary, they weren’t able to afford it.

“900 million!”

The bid continued to climb. Although the martial artists in the VIP suites were all high level figures, none of them understood the Asura Heavenly Dao like Lin Ming did, thus they couldn’t see the flaws in the Violet Gold Spear. To them, this Violet Gold Spear was the peak level that a weapon could obtain. Even if they were to expend every cent of their wealth to buy this spear they would still think it was worth it!

As the bid price rose like increasingly strong waves, this caused Duke Fullmoon’s blood to boil with ambition. He definitely had to win this spear.

“You aren’t going to bid?” Shadow Overflow smiled. He could see that Duke Fullmoon wanted to obtain this spear no matter the cost.

“Hehe, there’s no need to be in a hurry. Those shouting out bids right now are just being noisy. This spear is definitely worth more than that! Even buying it for 1.5 billion or 1.6 billion isn’t anything at all!”

Duke Fullmoon’s judgment was much worse than Lin Ming’s. To him this spear could sell for 1.5-1.6 billion, but to Lin Ming it could only sell for 1.3-1.4 billion.

“I’ve heard that Lin Ming also uses the spear. I was hoping to roll over him in this auction but he hasn’t even said anything. How boring…”

“Duke, how many points could that poor idiot have? To a little nobody like him, this Empyrean spirit treasure is just something to look at, how could he possibly afford it?” Junior-apprentice Sister Qing giggled from Duke Fullmoon’s chest.

“Heh, you’re right my little darling, he definitely won’t dare do anything at this price range.” Duke Fullmoon grinned. He reached out a hand and began to recklessly knead Junior-apprentice Sister Qing’s plump chest.

“1.2 billion!”

Duke Fullmoon suddenly shouted out.

A sudden bid of 1.2 billion caused many people to lose the courage to bid higher. For a time, the entire arena calmed down.

Duke Fullmoon was more than satisfied with this effect. He looked towards Lin Ming’s room, a meaningful smile crossing his face.

But in the next moment, his smile froze. From Lin Ming’s ordinary room, another bid was clearly shouted out, “1.21 billion!”

Chapter 1633 – Promissory Note

“Fifth grade divine runic symbols? Are you sure?”

Someone asked the fifth grade divine runic master who spoke with astonishment in their voice.

“Definitely.” The divine runic master stared back at the person ill-humoredly. “I have already been drawing up fifth grade divine runic symbols for over 5000 years, so how would I misread them?”

As the divine runic master spoke, many people saw the divine runic master badge on his chest. Although it wasn’t one issued by the Divine Runic Masters Guild, it still clearly identified him as a fifth grade divine runic master.

Originally, some people thought that the divine runic symbols Lin Ming took out were some top level inheritance he found somewhere, but they were actually so low level!

“He wants to sell fifth grade divine runic symbols on Divine Rune City’s auction stage? Is that boy playing jokes on us?”

“I think he might really be a ‘bid manipulator’ hired by the Divine Runic Masters Guild. He’s probably hired to wildly shout out prices and cause a ruckus to raise bids. This type of person will definitely be jailed by them later. I think that maybe even those 10 blood red jade slips might be fakes!”

If one didn’t understand the divine runic arts, it would be hard to judge whether the jade slips that Lin Ming took out were real or not.

“These people are really annoying brain-dead dogs, I can’t believe they would actually question the legitimacy and value of Big Brother Lin’s divine runic symbols…” Xiao Moxian growled from within the ordinary room.

However, even though she said this she was still feeling uneasy. Just what was the value of these 20 divine runic symbols?

It was true that Lin Ming’s revised divine runic symbols were fierce, but there were still only 20 of them.

Towards all these questions and doubts, Lin Ming remained silent. All around him, the divine runic symbols floated up and down, shimmering with a deep brilliance.

But this silence caused the audience’s suspicions to be even deeper.

As these people were increasingly crude with their language, a faintly seductive voice echoed out from within the sea of doubts, seemingly especially noticeable.

“The lot of you are truly ignorant and unlearned. Have you never heard of the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol before?”

This magnetic and captivating voice echoed out from a VIP suite.

Everyone’s gaze followed the voice to see a beautiful figure stand out.

“Who is that woman?”

The great majority of people present didn’t know of Suya, but they knew that the VIP suite Suya came from was rented by an Empyrean Holy Land. In other words, this woman likely came from an Empyrean Holy Land.

“She is the Extreme Star Holy Lands’ Miss Suya. The Extreme Star Holy Lands are at war with the Heaven Strife Holy Lands and Miss Suya is responsible for managing the acquisition of divine runic symbols at the Divine Runic Masters Guild.”

Someone who knew Suya explained.

Everyone was startled. Suya could be considered as someone with status. For her to speak out now, her words naturally carried a certain weight to them.

Suya seemed to not hear the discussions around her. Her eyes remained bright and pure throughout. To her, there was no doubt of Lin Ming’s value in her mind, and this was the perfect time to speak out for him. Giving help when needed was always better than attempting flattery later.

Seeing Suya stand up for him, Lin Ming faintly smiled and politely nodded towards her in the distance, expressing his thanks.

“Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol? What is that?”

Many people were confused. In truth, one couldn’t blame them for not knowing. Those that came to Divine Rune City for the auction were either extremely wealthy characters or rulers of their own domains. However, these people were separated by mountains and rivers and many of them weren’t too understanding of the world of divine runic masters. And there were also some people that weren’t spiritas but were of other races. The Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols were earth-shaking amongst divine runic masters and particularly in the Divine Runic Masters Guild, but outside martial artists didn’t know too much about this.

The inner Asura Road was simply far too large. Even those people with a vast degree of experience would find it hard to know that a small divine runic symbol was able to create such a tremendous change in the war between the Extreme Star Holy Lands and Heaven Strife Holy Lands.

“Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol? This woman seems to value it a great deal?”

Although these people didn’t know what the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol was, if this woman held this divine runic symbol in such high esteem then it was clearly something extraordinary. Did this youth create this divine runic symbol?

As many bidders were whispering their suspicions to each other, Suya opened her mouth and said, “Sir Lin, if you must compete for the Violet Gold Spear then I can lend you one billion points in advance.”

Although Suya’s voice wasn’t loud it still spread through the auction arena like a rolling thunderclap, smashing into everyone’s ears. For a time, the noisy auction arena fell silent.

Miss Suya was going to lend this young divine runic master a billion points?

A billion points was not a small number. To lend this amount so easily, this proved that Suya clearly trusted this young man named Lin Ming a great deal. She trusted his moral character and trusted in his ability to repay her!

Many people didn’t know of the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol that Suya spoke of. And even though there were people present who knew what this divine runic symbol was and began explaining its fierceness to others, these other people still only half believed their words.

But now, with Suya directly lending Lin Ming a billion points, this was clear proof of how valuable this Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol was! If it wasn’t then there was no way Suya would have lent this tremendous amount of money.

At this time, in the VIP suite that Suya was in, a man that looked to be in his thirties had a very ill complexion. “Junior-apprentice Sister Suya, please come back in first.”

This man was Suya’s senior-apprentice brother and also someone that the Extreme Star Holy Lands sent to Divine Rune City to bid for items in the auction.

With Suya, the two of them were responsible for winning a material called a ‘white birch spirit root’. And this material was something directly named by the Palace Master of Extreme Star Heavenly Palace!

Just what sort of character was the Extreme Star Heavenly Palace Master? His strength was considered top level even amongst Empyreans and he was the god of the entire Extreme Star Holy Lands. Normally, just mentioning his name would cause all disciples of the Extreme Star Holy Lands to fall silent.

The reason that Suya was able to stand out and have such success in the Extreme Star Holy Lands was in truth partially because the Extreme Star Heavenly Palace Master recognized her ability to communicate and negotiate with others.

However, just because the Palace Master recognized Suya’s talents didn’t mean that she was allowed to arbitrarily make decisions on her own! The current Extreme Star Holy Lands was stretched for resources. Suya and her senior-apprentice brother had been given authority to use 2.5 billion points in this auction and this was the personal wealth of the Extreme Star Heavenly Palace Master. This wealth was for the express purpose of acquiring the white birch spirit root, something that the Palace Master needed to upgrade his vital origin magic weapon!

If there were any delays and the Palace Master’s enhancement in strength was affected, then Suya and her senior-apprentice brother could die 10,000 times without being able to make up for it!

Now, Suya lent out a billion points in a single breath. This left them with just 1.5 billion points, an amount insufficient to win the ‘white birch spirit root’!

And according to the rules of the auction, all debts had to be paid in full within 10 days of the auction ending.

If Suya were to lend these points to Lin Ming and also simultaneously win the ‘white birch spirit root’, that required Lin Ming to pay back the billion points in a short period of time.

And Lin Ming himself had a great deal of things he needed to buy.

Suya knew that besides the 2 billion points on Lin Ming’s body, he really did only have these 20 divine runic symbols. If Lin Ming had other sources of wealth, why would he have a condition of borrowing 800 million points from the Extreme Star Holy Lands for taking on the mission of drawing up Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols?

But Suya still lent Lin Ming these billion points because she mistakenly believed that he really wanted to purchase this Violet Gold Spear.

After all, Lin Ming was a spear-wielding martial artist and Suya could approximate that Lin Ming really should trade in the Phoenix Blood Spear he used.

“Junior-apprentice Sister, have you gone mad!?” Suya’s senior-apprentice brother had an extremely ugly complexion. As he spoke, he was left a bit breathless from anger.

“Senior-apprentice Brother, you must trust me just this one time. Although I haven’t come into contact with Lin Ming much, I have a clear grasp of his character. He never does anything without certain belief that he can accomplish it. In the past I underestimated him a few times. I thought he had taken on missions that were impossible for him to complete, but the result was that I ended up black and blue with shame. In the end, I had to ignore the shame I felt to apologize to him. He is the type of man that will always be true to his word.”

Suya’s tone indicated she wasn’t worried at all. But, although she seemed calm on the surface, her palms were actually wet with sweat.

At this time she had truly made a great gamble. She was betting everything on the hope that Lin Ming could create a miracle with those 20 divine runic symbols.

Suya had already thoroughly investigated Lin Ming’s background and discovered that he was someone who couldn’t even be described as a freakishly monstrous genius.

Over 20 years ago he had only been a talented third grade divine runic master. But after just a mere 20 some years, he was able to create the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol that not even Shadow Overflow was able to unravel.

There was absolutely a secret hidden on Lin Ming’s body!

However, even though Suya made repeated assurances, her senior-apprentice brother turned a deaf ear to all of this. “Junior-apprentice Sister, you have become obsessed with phantoms. I do not agree with you lending out these points. Stepping back, even if Lin Ming could really use those 20 divine runic symbols to earn back the points, Honorable Master will still punish us because we arbitrarily used the points he gave us for buying the white birch spirit root for other purposes. This is a grave crime that you are committing.”

As Suya’s senior-apprentice brother was speaking, Lin Ming suddenly smiled. “Thank you Miss Suya, but the auction for this Violet Gold Spear has yet to end, thus the auction of my divine runic symbols must be after the Violet Gold Spear. Mister Song, do you think… you can arrange it for me?”

Lin Ming said, turning towards Song Wen.

Song Wen narrowed his eyes as he looked at the divine runic symbols in Lin Ming’s hand. Although he could feel that there was something extraordinary about them, he thought the entire situation was absurd. Even if he knew about the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbols, no matter how heaven-defying Lin Ming’s new divine runic symbols were, it was impossible to sell 20 of them for several hundred millions of points. After all, they were only fifth grade divine runic symbols.

“Little Brother Lin…”

Song Wen had a look of embarrassment on his face. He was afraid that Lin Ming was too overconfident in his abilities and had set the base price for his divine runic symbols too high. If no one were to end up bidding on them then that would truly be a joke.

Lin Ming naturally knew what Song Wen was thinking. He smiled and said, “Mister Song, feel relieved that I am not just auctioning these 20 divine runic symbols. I am also auctioning promissory notes for more. I can sell hundreds or even a thousand. Whoever is willing to purchase in advance, whoever pays.”

As Lin Ming spoke, many bidders almost fell off their chairs.

Promissory notes!? Purchase in advance!?

For several hundred million points to only buy a promissory note? Who did he think he was? Only an idiot would buy these!

Since this auction first began, no one had ever heard of taking money first to buy a promissory note!

Chapter 1636 – Test

To have a zero base price on promissory notes, the truth was that Divine Rune City didn’t want the associated infamy. The general meaning of it was that all transactions for this auction were completely voluntary. The base price would be set to zero and whoever wanted to bid could bid whatever they wanted and the Divine Rune City Auction House would take on no responsibility for this matter.

Although the Divine Rune City Auction didn’t publicize the auction of the ‘promissory notes’ and had no intention of doing so, they had still made it explicitly clear that the auction of the promissory notes would not take place if Lin Ming’s 10 Heavenly Fire Symbols sold for less than 40 million. Even so, news of this auction still spread through the city!

Moreover, this news spread like wildfire!

Many martial artists and many influences learned that the Divine Rune City Auction, which was famed throughout the entire inner Asura Road for having anything up for sale as long as one had the money, was actually selling promissory notes.

Moreover, what left one dumbstruck was that the person selling these promissory notes was a Divine Lord realm junior who was less than a hundred years old!

And, this Divine Lord realm junior also didn’t have any great influence backing him. He was nothing but a loner, and although there was said to be an amazing master standing behind him, this master had never appeared.

He had seemingly produced a mysterious divine runic symbol and was considerably well known in the world of divine runic arts. But outside of this small community, there hadn’t been anyone who had heard of him.

If such a junior were to write down a promissory note and sell it, then others would definitely say that whoever bought this promissory note was an idiot.

If one could sell empty promises at an auction then they too would want to do the same!

They could write down a promissory note for 10 Empyrean spirit treasures, 10 transcendent divine pills, or even 100 seventh grade divine runic symbols, and would they be able to sell this note for 10 billion points?

Many other colleagues in the auction industry were waiting to have a good laugh at Divine Rune City Auction House’s expense.

The business of auction houses was highly competitive. The more transactions an auction house had, the more sky high prices they could sell items for, then the more clients and bidders they could attract! Clients would always want to go to an auction house that would auction off their items at the highest price possible! There were many auction houses that could find buyers but not a source of goods!

Divine Rune City Auction House was extremely reputable and even if other auction houses worked together and hired a batch of bid manipulators, they still couldn’t shake the iron-fisted monopoly that Divine Rune City Auction House held over the auction business. And now, these other auction houses were all waiting for the Divine Rune City Auction House to fail.

However, no matter what the news was or how many people were waiting to see this bumbling failure occur, the second round of the auctions began on time.

This time, there were even more bidders on the scene.

Many people heard about the sale of promissory notes and wanted to join in on this new experience.

Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian had already entered the auction arena earlier. As they were about to enter their private room, Lin Ming could feel a swift and violent cold light shoot towards them. Lin Ming turned to see Duke Fullmoon appearing like a vengeful ghost in the windows of his VIP suite. The light inside his room was dark, causing Duke Fullmoon to look especially grim and ghostly.

“This stupid fly also came early. But he’s already gone bankrupt so what’s the point of putting on airs.” Xiao Moxian pouted her lips, speaking with disdain.

Lin Ming faintly smiled. “He’s also representing his sect to purchase items, so he likely still has many points in his hands.”

Lin Ming didn’t bother with Duke Fullmoon and went straight to his private room. As he flew up into the skies, many people were looking towards him. By this time, Lin Ming had already become famous!

Today, if he could sell the Heavenly Fire Symbols for at least 40 million then he would be able to accomplish the unprecedentedly magnificent feat of selling promissory notes. But if he sold the Heavenly Fire Symbols for less than 40 million he would become an utter joke.

The first item in the second round of the auctions was 10 zenith black level god runes.

Zenith black level god runes were necessary materials for crafting seventh grade divine runic symbols. There were even some peak sixth grade divine runic symbols that required zenith black level god runes. Thus, these 10 zenith black level god runes were in high demand. In the end, they were bought by a peak sixth grade divine runic master in the VIP suites.

Following that, all sorts of different items were sold. At the sixth auction, Song Wen calmly took out a jade box. After opening it, one could see 10 light and thin symbol papers within.

These were Lin Ming’s Heavenly Fire Symbols!

During the previous round of auctions, Lin Ming had taken out the Heavenly Fire Symbols once, thus many people were able to recognize what these 10 symbol papers were.

“It’s here! Haha, to sell promissory notes, I came today just to watch this event!”

“He’s been crazy after thinking of money too much; to think he actually dares to sell promissory notes!”

All of these words came from spies sent from other auction houses in the inner Asura Road. Now they mixed themselves into the crowds of bidders and their mission was to gather as much information as they could so they could later propagandize this ridiculous matter.

Towards these people beneath the arena stage that had ill intentions, Song Wen ignored them all. He indifferently said, “Ladies and gentleman, these are fifth grade divine runic symbols, Heavenly Fire Symbols produced by a young and rising talent of my Divine Runic Masters Guild. In the last round of auctions you all saw that these were not ordinary Heavenly Fire Symbols. These Heavenly Fire Symbols have undergone many improvements and their effects are far superior to normal. For these 10 Heavenly Fire Symbols, the base price is 20 million points and each increase cannot be any lower than one million points.”

Song Wen lightly spoke these words that had no persuasive power at all. Young and rising divine runic master, many improvements, effects far superior to normal, all of these words seemed untrustworthy to the audience.

And, the most absurd point was that these 10 fifth grade divine runic symbols were being sold for a total scam price of 20 million points!

Fifth grade divine runic symbols usually sold for tens of thousands, and buying 10 of them for a million points was already a tremendous loss. Yet, Song Wen listed the base price of these 10 divine runic symbols as 20 times that ridiculous price.

Setting up such a starting bid was simply a death wish. Many people were looking to see which idiot would bid on these.

However, Song Wen didn’t start the auction. Rather, he pressed some switch on the auction stage and with a loud rumbling sound, the entire auction stage was split apart as the ground sank in.

At the same time, a massive black altar slowly rose from the ground!

This black altar was an array formation!

Its use was to test the various characteristics, might, and attributes of a divine runic symbol.

In the Divine Rune City Auction House, sometimes there would be special divine runic symbols sold. At this time, these divine runic symbols would need to be tested in order to demonstrate the various aspects of a divine runic symbol.

Hu - !

With a powerful grinding noise, the array formation activated!

The entire altar was shrouded in a shimmering white light. A chubby old man with a white beard guffawed as he hopped onto the altar. This old man was no one else but Lin Ming’s old friend – Old Xue.

At this auction, Lin Ming specifically asked Old Xue to test the divine runic symbol!

Chapter 1637 – Heavenly Fire Symbol

Old Xue’s appearance immediately attracted the gazes of everyone present.

“Who is that old man?” Most of the audience didn’t know who Old Xue was.

“He is Elder Xue of the Divine Runic Masters Guild, a sixth grade divine runic master.”

The reputation of a sixth grade divine runic master was irreproachable. To have a sixth grade divine runic master test a fifth grade divine runic symbol, this left everyone waiting for the results with wide eyes.

Although they didn’t know if these fifth grade divine runic symbols could sell for tens of millions of points, if Lin Ming had dared take them out in this auction then they should be spectacular.

At this point, Song Wen took out a soul crystal and placed it in the eye of the testing array formation. In that instant the brilliant light around the altar became even more blazing, shooting up into the world like a column of evanescent light, scattering out everywhere.

The auction arena was extremely broad, but after the array formation on the auction stage activated, the dazzling light covered the entire auction hall arena!

This was a titanic illusory magic array. Once it started, every person within the auction hall arena would fall into the illusory magic array and would find it difficult to discern between reality and illusion.

Boom - !

The scenery in front of everyone suddenly changed.

What entered the eyes of everyone was an endless sea of green foliage that stretched to the furthest horizons.

They were surrounded by dense grass that brushed against the waist, vast and limitless.

Every guest in the auction house, including those in the ordinary rooms and VIP suites, instantly arrived in an ancient primal grassland!

Here, the scene was like the endless Great Desolate that parted the inner and outer Asura Road.

And within these grasslands, the earth began to tremble.

From far away, one could see massive forms appear on the horizon. These forms were like mountains as their vague figures solidified as they closed in.

Rumble rumble rumble!

As these giant monsters approached, the audience discovered they were all vicious beasts.

Their bodies were as heavy as mountains. Every time they stepped forwards the ground would shake like a beating drum, incomparably horrifying.

“That… that… that is a deep blue crystal beast. I heard that two Divine Lord squads from the Blue Lotus Holy Lands perished, and it was likely they encountered a deep blue crystal beast…”

“Seafall beast…”

“Mystic thunder beast…”

“That… that is a Golden Phoenix Crow… it is a variation God Beast that has existed since ancient times and is said to be able to contend with a Great World King and emit true essence heavenly flames…”

As each vicious beast appeared they were soon identified by the audience. With each new creature that arrived, the audience became increasingly pale. These vicious beasts were all found within the Great Desolate!

In particular, the giant Golden Phoenix Crow whose wings blocked out half the sky. As the audience saw this beast, their complexions became even uglier.

Although everyone was well aware that these vicious beasts were only phantoms produced in the illusory magic array, each one of these phantom beasts had extraordinary strengths.

Each bidder was able to clearly perceive the aura of these vicious beasts. They could judge that these vicious beasts were not superficial fakes. Rather, by relying on the accurate simulation of the large-scale array formation, the defensive powers of these vicious beasts were almost the same as in reality.

“Elder Xue, please test the divine runic symbol.” Song Wen was a bit surprised as he saw that Elder Xue had stepped forth to test the divine runic symbol. To ask a divine runic master like Elder Xue to personally test his creation, Lin Ming must be confident in his works.

Elder Xue nodded and happily took a divine runic symbol from Lin Ming who had already flown down from his room. He asked, “Before the test begins, are there any special instructions you need to tell me?”

Lin Ming thought for a moment and said, “During the test it’s best to be careful. When the input of power reaches through the 2320th tiny rune, increase the flow of energy. The effect will be much better.”

“2320th tiny rune?” Elder Xue was startled. After a brief pause he nodded.

Standing on the side, Song Wen’s complexion immediately changed. Although he didn’t understand how to draw up divine runic symbols himself, he was still the president of the Runic Pill Trading Organization. Even if he had never eaten pork meat before he would still know how a pig ran.

He had seen sixth grade divine runic symbols before, and the average peak sixth grade divine runic symbol would have around 1500 tiny runes, yet this mere fifth grade divine runic symbol had over 2000 tiny runes?

It seemed this Heavenly Fire Symbol was well worth anticipating.

However, the spies that came from other auction houses, as long as they understood even a little about divine runic arts, were surprised by Lin Ming’s words. Shadow Overflow frowned. This brat, the divine runic symbols he drew up were always so ridiculous!

“I want to take a good look and see just what sort of effect a divine runic symbol with so many tiny runes will have!”

Judging the value of a divine runic symbol, especially an extraordinary divine runic symbol, was an extremely complex and burdensome process.

The average person only knew whether a divine runic symbol was strong or weak, and that was by looking at its grade. But when looking at those especially amazing divine runic symbols that had special effects, although the grade of the divine runic symbol was important, it wasn’t the most important factor.

The reason that Elder Xue agreed to help Lin Ming and test out his divine runic symbol was the shockingly special Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol that Lin Ming produced before. He wanted to see what was so special about this new divine runic symbol.

Like an entertainer preparing his show, Elder Xue began to take out all sorts of strange magic tools and array discs in front of everyone.

One of these magic tools was a set of black gloves, knit with mysterious silken threads.

“I shall begin.” Elder Xue nodded towards Lin Ming.

As Song Wen heard this he drew some circles in the air. Then, ripples began to appear in the void.

Thick and viscous bubbles surrounded everyone, covering them within.

The reason for this was that there was always some risk that came with testing a divine runic symbol. As the auctioneer here, Song Wen had to minimize all chances of an accident occurring as much as possible.

Once all the preparations were complete, Elder Xue no longer bothered with the others. He completely immersed his mind into the fifth grade divine runic symbol in his hands, carefully filling it with his energy.

Looking in from the side, as Lin Ming saw Old Xue earnestly testing his divine runic symbol, he felt a bit unsure in his heart. Although he was confident in the improved Heavenly Fire Symbol that he created, the true might and value of it would depend on the actual results of this test.

Everyone’s eyes focused on Elder Xue’s body, all of them waiting with breath abated.

They were all aware that if this test wasn’t a joke, then they would be witnesses to the birth of a miracle.

As Elder Xue was inputting his energy into the improved Heavenly Fire Symbol, his complexion began to gradually become more dignified over time. After such a long period of time, there was actually no movement from the Heavenly Fire Symbol!

Shadow Overflow grinned a gloating smile. Smelly brat, this time it was his turn to suffer…

But that gloating smile soon froze on his face. Deep in concentration, Elder Xue flicked a finger upon the divine runic symbol, seeming as if he were pulling out a string. Then, a blazing red trail of fire rushed out from the divine runic symbol.

This power of fire flew in the skies like a phoenix, a beautiful vision in the air. Suddenly, the surrounding space seemed to bubble up like boiling water.

Shadow Overflow felt that something wasn’t right. At this time, five of the giant vicious beasts that Song Wen created suddenly started rushing towards Elder Xue together.

“Deep blue crystal beast, bone devouring beast… these are all peak Holy Lord level beasts, even beasts that approach a World King. With these several vicious beasts together, even an ordinary World King would feel fear!”

As the vicious beasts wildly rampaged forwards, the entire audience could feel a dreadful pressure. Even if they knew these vicious beasts were formed by the illusory magic array, their aura was still horrifying.

This was also the fierceness of an auction house’s array formation. This array formation could be called the most realistic simulation testing array within the entire inner Asura Road.

At this time, a brilliant light exploded from Elder Xue’s eyes. The Heavenly Fire Symbol in his hand suddenly scattered out. With a loud rumbling sound, a pillar of flames shot into the skies, forming a mushroom cloud as a sea of flames surged out in all directions.

As a vicious beast broke into the midst of these flames, it suddenly emitted a miserable howl.

Another pained howl sounded out from a different direction. Everyone turned towards this cry. As their eyes focused on what was happening, all they saw was a column of flames shoot straight into the sky.

Under the watchful gaze of everyone, the vicious beasts that seemed as if they could tear open the heavens were drowned in this sea of raging flames. At a speed visible to the eyes, these vicious beasts were slowly charred into a pile of skeletons.

The people looking on were panic-stricken. For a time, the entire arena was left silent, without a single word spoken.

The only sound was the tumbling waves of flames burning in the distance. Even the earth below was melted away into shining lava, shimmering like metal.

It was like an apocalypse of heavenly flames had descended from above.

Shadow Overflow’s eyes nearly popped out of his sockets. Even a lofty and conceited dark divine runic master like himself, one of the giants of the dark world, was shocked by this scene.

“This… is this really the might of Lin Ming’s fifth grade Heavenly Fire Symbol?” He clenched his fists together. After the shock passed, an unexpected surge of bitterness and jealousy filled his heart… he feared that even a medium sixth grade Heavenly Fire Symbol might not possess such might!

A sixth grade Heavenly Fire Symbol was one produced by a World King! A peak sixth grade divine runic symbol was one created by a Great World King and could be used to contend with Great World King enemies!

Xiao Moxian also gripped her fists tightly, her smile as beautiful as a fire. Her cute canines glittered beneath the light of the raging flames. With this, all of the worries in her heart disappeared, replaced with nothing but pride. As she looked at Lin Ming with both eyes, her eyes shined like little stars.

After some time, the shocked people began to regain their composure.

But, before they could say anything, a deafening phoenix cry filled the air.

Everyone was stunned once again. Above them, the skies suddenly turned overcast, dimming down to shadows.

They looked up and nearly cried out. The hell!? That Golden Phoenix Crow couldn’t resist waiting and was rushing out!

Seeing the Golden Phoenix Crow diving downwards, many people paled from fear.

Then, another strange sound caught everyone’s attention.

They saw the raging sea of flames that scorched those five vicious beasts to nothing begin to stir up once more. The flames wildly burned, revitalized with new life as they began to swallow all of the power of fire from within a hundred miles.

Every pillar of flames danced like flame phoenixes in the skies, their strength amazing.

Within this cataclysmic crimson sea, a brilliant runic symbol shined like a star from within the center of the seething flames.

This was the fifth grade Heavenly Fire Symbol that had just been used!

The Heavenly Fire Symbol actually reformed itself!

“This… this powerful Heavenly Fire Symbol… can actually reform itself and be reused!” At this time, even Elder Xue who was responsible for the test couldn’t help but cry out in praise.

Chapter 1639 – Doubts

At this time, the entire auction was stirred into a frenzy!

Many people stretched out their necks, waiting for the sale of the Heavenly Fire Symbol to begin!

“How come it hasn’t started? I have to buy a Heavenly Fire Symbol no matter what today!” A peak Holy Lord martial artist secretly swore to himself as he gripped his fists. He had a half-step World King blood enemy. If he had this Heavenly Fire Symbol then he would have the capital to take revenge!

It wasn’t just him who had this idea, but many others in the audience. At this time, many people who had mocked Lin Ming’s fifth grade Heavenly Fire Symbols before were now eagerly waiting to buy one of them.

There was also another group of people that were hoping to buy these fifth grade divine runic symbols and then gather a team of researchers to unravel them. If they could somehow encounter a stroke of luck and crack open its secrets then that would be worth a massive amount of wealth!

Of course, if they knew the fate that had befallen Shadow Overflow, they might not have had such thoughts.

Everyone had different thoughts, but without exception all of them were looking forwards to the auction of the Heavenly Fire Symbol, a look of hope and greed in their eyes. At the same time, the suspicious and derisive color in their eyes had transformed into respect.

The Asura Road was a world that revered the strong. If one displayed a mighty enough performance, a shocking enough performance, then one could earn sufficient respect.

This was the fairest law of all.

Song Wen was happy to see such powerful divine runic symbols. But, he also didn’t forget what his responsibilities were.

“Elder Xue, can you judge the value of Sir Lin Ming’s fifth grade divine runic symbols?”

Everyone calmed down, all of their eyes focusing on Elder Xue.

No matter how powerful this fifth grade divine runic symbol was, the main purpose of this test was to evaluate its price.

Elder Xue thought for a moment. Then, he slowly said, “The potency is equal to a medium sixth grade divine runic symbol, but when factoring in its ability to rebirth itself as well as the lowered requirements for maximum use, its value far outstrips that of a normal sixth grade divine runic symbol by several dozen times. There has never been a similar case before this so it is hard for me to put forth an accurate value. That will be something that must be determined through the auction…”

“Dozens of times over a sixth grade divine runic symbol!?” Someone gasped, their voice shaking. If this were true then many people present wouldn’t be able to afford it!

Song Wen faintly smiled. He swept his eyes over the impatient bidders. Seeing the desire thick in their eyes, Song Wen had already begun planning in advance.

He struck his auctioneer mallet on the podium and then stretched out his words as he said, “Sir Lin, our Runic Pill Trading Organization will purchase your 10 Heavenly Fire Symbols! As for the price, that can be discussed later…”

As Song Wen spoke, the entire arena hall was left stunned!

Even Lin Ming was startled. He thought that Song Wen was going to continue with the auction of the 10 Heavenly Fire Symbols, but he never thought that the Divine Runic Masters Guild would want to buy them up instead!

What was the meaning of this?

Could it be that the Divine Runic Masters Guild wanted to buy these Heavenly Fire Symbols to study and collect them?

Lin Ming didn’t believe that the Divine Runic Masters Guild, with its countless masters, needed to use these 10 Heavenly Fire Symbols to fight off some enemy force. Moreover, without an auction it would be difficult to set an appropriate price. After all, this was the first time this sort of Heavenly Fire Symbol had ever appeared so it was impossible to set a base price; everything would have to be determined by the market.

But as Song Wen finished speaking, the arena hall actually exploded in rage!

“Are you joking with us!? You had us watch this scene for half a day and now you aren’t selling them!?”

“You motherfucker, I am going to buy a Heavenly Fire Symbol no matter what, so what is the meaning of your Divine Runic Masters Guild buying anything!?”

“You had us watch this show and then came up with these tricks at the end, it's as if you think we are monkeys!”

Many of the martial artists present were rough desperados. After being stunned by Song Wen’s words, they became livid with anger! Martial artists often had short and explosive tempers. Once Song Wen lost control of the scene, this would not be a joke.

However, Song Wen remained calm and composed as he faced this scene. He faintly smiled and said, “Please be patient everyone. I am not saying that there won’t be any sold, only that these 10 finished divine runic symbols will not be sold. Didn’t we say that there would be a sale of promissory notes? Those can be exchanged for the improved Heavenly Fire Symbols produced by Lin Ming. If any of you wish to purchase in advance then you may bid during the auction for them.”

What? The auction for promissory notes would begin like this!?

Many of those present were apoplectic with rage, feeling as if all of their blood was rushing to their head! The completed divine runic symbols wouldn’t be sold but the promissory notes would! They all had the impulse to rush up the auction stage and punch Song Wen in the face!

However, this was a seller’s market and there was only one place to purchase these divine runic symbols, nowhere else. Even if the Divine Runic Masters Guild played this dirty trick and only sold promissory notes, everyone could only eat their dissatisfaction.

Seeing the audience’s reaction, Xiao Moxian’s heart blossomed with joy.

“Hehe, look at those snobby fellows who dared to look down on my Big Brother Lin. Now there’s nothing to sell to them and they can only pay in advance before receiving anything! This feels great!”

Seeing everyone’s resentful expressions, Xiao Moxian couldn’t help but gloat a little.

And standing near Xiao Moxian, Lin Ming naturally didn’t have these playful thoughts. Rather, he looked towards Song Wen, trying to figure out what his intentions were.

The more he thought, the more Lin Ming couldn’t help but praise in his heart. This was truly a skillful move!

If those 10 completed Heavenly Fire Symbols were sold at the start, then because the quantity was too low, the ones buying them would mostly be peak Holy Lord martial artists.

These people would buy them for their personal use. Because they didn’t have much wealth, the price wouldn’t be too high.

And once they bought them, this would set an approximate base price for Lin Ming’s Heavenly Fire Symbols.

Following that, it would be difficult for the auction of the Heavenly Fire Symbols promissory notes to surpass this price.

This was because in everyone’s hearts, buying the finished product should definitely be more expensive. As for selling promissory notes, they would be cheaper. After all, this was the risk one paid for promissory notes!

Thus, the sale of these 10 complete divine runic symbols would inevitably affect the auction of the promissory notes. Once an approximate price was formed in everyone’s mind, it would be impossible to sell for a sky-high price. It had to be known that these promissory notes would form the bulk of Lin Ming’s income, and having such a situation would cause him to suffer a great deal!

On the other hand, if the promissory notes were sold first and not the completed ones, then the promissory notes would sell for a great deal. This was the so-called hunger marketing strategy.

Even though this was a simple matter, Lin Ming could sense how crafty and intelligent Song Wen’s decision was. No wonder the Divine Runic Masters Guild would allow Song Wen, someone who wasn’t a divine runic master and who also had a low cultivation, to become the president of the Runic Pill Trading Organization.

“Everyone, let us begin the auction of Sir Lin’s promissory notes. These promissory notes will be guaranteed with the reputation of my Divine Runic Masters Guild. Sir Lin, how many Heavenly Fire Symbols do you plan on selling in advance?”

Song Wen slyly smiled as he faced Lin Ming. Facing the disdainful eyes of the crowd, Song Wen turned a blind eye to them all, and in fact became even more confident of himself. The main purpose of this treasure fair was to earn money. As the president of the Runic Pill Trading Organization, he had to place the duty of making money as his top priority.

As for others looking down on him and cursing him in their hearts, he didn’t bother caring at all.

Lin Ming narrowed his eyes. He thought about the amount for the moment and then said to Song Wen, “First sell 500. I will place a soul mark on a divine runic symbol as a promise of debt and when the time comes the person can exchange this divine runic symbol for the promised goods.”

Lin Ming’s voice wasn’t loud, but his words spread to everyone in the audience.

500 promissory notes?

Everyone was stunned. Just how many points was this!?

This motherfucker, wasn’t he earning points too easily!?

Moreover, if this concerned 500 promissory notes, then the final price would involve hundreds of millions and billions of points! This caused many people to almost faint from anger!

If Lin Ming had said these words not too long ago then he would have been called an idiot by everyone. But the current situation was different. After going through the testing array formation, everyone was able to see just how powerful this fifth grade Heavenly Fire Symbol was!

A fifth grade Heavenly Fire Symbol was able to severely wound a World King level vicious beast. If such a thing were placed in a battlefield and used en masse…

Thinking of this, some people began to stream with a cold sweat.

Such powerful divine runic symbols… if an influence were to possess these items then they would absolutely be weapons that could change the tide of a war. And the most important point was that these fifth grade Heavenly Fire Symbols had to be grasped in their hands; they absolutely could not allow enemy forces to obtain them!

Many people realized this point. But… with such a large transaction and also buying only promissory notes… many people were lacking the confidence to bid on them!

What if they couldn’t cash them in later?

This was not a small amount. Even an Empyrean Holy Land had to mull over this massive wholesale trade!

As everyone was feeling faint of heart and wavering between bidding or not, a black-cloaked old man flew out like a ghost from the VIP suites.

His long robes trailed behind him as he flew high into the skies above the arena hall. His entire body was covered in a thick black fog, hiding his appearance.

He was Shadow Overflow!

Shadow Overflow’s appearance caused Lin Ming to frown. Although he didn’t know who Shadow Overflow was, he knew that this fellow was the old man who always followed behind Duke Fullmoon and was extremely hostile to him.

Shadow Overflow’s appearance attracted everyone’s eyes.

Beneath his voluminous black cloak, Shadow Overflow’s lips moved. His hoarse throat began to squeeze out words, “I acknowledge that the might of these Heavenly Fire Symbols is unparalleled! But because this is a massive transaction that has no real items and only promissory notes, I have my suspicions… do these Heavenly Fire Symbols originate from your hands?”

Shadow Overflow’s words were forceful and menacing. As he looked at Lin Ming, the air between them turned cold!

As this was said, many bidders frowned. They also had these doubts in their hearts. In truth, many of them also thought of this. They thought that these Heavenly Fire symbols were not drawn by Lin Ming but were obtained by him from some mystic realm, or, perhaps they were inherited and there were only these 10 and no others.

If so, then these promissory notes written by Lin Ming were nothing but pieces of scrap paper! As for the guarantee of the Divine Runic Masters Guild, so what?

In truth, what Shadow Overflow was really saying was that he found this entire situation hard to accept. A young junior like Lin Ming had actually demolished him when it came to the divine runic arts!

Not only did Shadow Overflow think this, but many other people skilled in the divine runic arts found it hard to believe that Lin Ming could have such attainments in the divine runic arts. It was simply unreasonable!

The appearance of the black-cloaked man didn’t surprise Lin Ming. Even if the black-cloaked man didn’t appear, there would be someone else that stood up to question him.

To sell promissory notes on the stage of the Divine Rune City Auction House, and for an amount that would even give Empyrean Holy Lands pause, this was not an easy matter at all. The representatives of the large influences would be ruined if they were deceived!

Lin Ming moved. His clothes fluttered as he flew through the air and fell atop the auction stage. He faintly smiled and said, “Since you have such doubts, how about I draw one in front of the audience!”

Chapter 1640 – Exposed

As soon as Lin Ming finished his words, Shadow Overflow’s lips twitched; he hadn’t thought that Lin Ming would suggest such a thing.

This sort of suggestion was simply being more courageous than the heavens.

When a divine runic master drew up divine runic symbols, they usually did so in the peaceful environment of a divine runic room. Even then, there was a considerable failure rate.

Moreover, this sort of improved Heavenly Fire Symbol had over 2000 tiny runes; the complexity in drawing one up surpassed the majority of sixth grade divine runic symbols!

Under the watchful gaze of the audience, what would Lin Ming do if he failed!?

If his mindset was poor then he would panic after the first failure. Moreover, in order to draw up such a complicated Heavenly Fire Symbol it would require a massive amount of Lin Ming’s soul force. Even if a peak fifth grade divine runic master were to try, they could likely only attempt it once. If they failed they would have to wait several hours for a second try, and the success rate would drop even lower!

In this sort of situation, there was no divine runic master that would attempt to draw up a divine runic symbol that reached the limits of their skill in front of a giant audience. There was only a single explanation for this, and that was Lin Ming had reached an ultimate peak of confidence in his divine runic arts skills!

If Shadow Overflow could think of this, so could the other divine runic masters in the audience. All of them were frightened by Lin Ming’s words. He was simply being far too confident. Wasn’t he afraid that he would fail?

“It seems that this Heavenly Fire Symbol… is really made by this brat…” Shadow Overflow couldn’t help but accept this blow to his self-confidence. But, he didn’t think that Lin Ming would dare to boast at such a time.

But, suddenly…

Shadow Overflow’s originally gloomy and decrepit face suddenly lifted up with a bizarre smile. Hidden beneath the shadows of his black cloak, his eyes began to shine with a brilliant light.

“Although it may be true you drew up those divine runic symbols, you are far too young and far too arrogant and cannot stand others questioning you. However, what you don’t know is that as a peak dark divine runic master, I have special methods to observe and copy the technique of other divine runic masters! If you draw up a divine runic symbol in front of me then that is the same as revealing all of your secrets to me!”

Thinking of this, the avaricious greed in Shadow Overflow’s eyes became increasingly thick. When a normal divine runic master drew up a divine runic symbol they would always reveal some secrets. And for these secrets, while orthodox divine runic masters might not be able to discern anything, if they were to be seen by a dark divine runic master, they would be far more easily understood! And Shadow Overflow was someone who was particularly skilled in this field!

In particular, Shadow Overflow had already tried to unravel Lin Ming’s Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol before. At the time, Shadow Overflow had already obtained a thorough understanding of the tiny rune system and overall structure of the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol. The only question that baffled him was how to fuse in the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws. Now, Shadow Overflow believed he would be able to find the hints to doing so by watching Lin Ming!

Even if Lin Ming failed, Shadow Overflow would still be able to see many things. Moreover, he could even kick Lin Ming while he was down and send that brat rolling off a cliff.

At this time, in the auction hall arena, there were many other dark divine runic masters that had the same thoughts as Shadow Overflow.

These dark divine runic masters all needed to buy materials so they definitely wouldn’t miss Divine Rune City’s treasure fair auction. Of course, they had hidden their status before entering. Some of these people had even been part of Shadow Overflow’s team that tried to copy the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol.

They all held the same thoughts that Shadow Overflow did in their hearts. Many of them were secretly celebrating this event.

“This bull-headed youth is far too hot-blooded and arrogant, he can’t even withstand a few insults! To dare to draw up a divine runic symbol publicly, good! Very good!”

“Haha, the master who passed down their inheritance to this brat must be feeling stupid. This brat wants to show off and even have a demonstration of his skills in front of everyone, he’s just waiting for us to unravel his inheritances. Once we figure out how to create this Heavenly Fire Symbol, we’ll have our own open auction! At that time, not only will money be rolling in but our futures will be limitless! Hahaha!”

Some divine runic masters thought. Their faces began to burn red with excitement and their breaths quickened.

For a time, many dark divine runic masters reached out faint threads of soul force that lingered around Lin Ming. The frenzy in their hearts had been ignited by Lin Ming and they were eagerly awaiting his performance.

These dark divine runic masters that coveted the peak fifth grade Heavenly Fire Symbol had to be at least peak fifth grade; in other words, a peak Holy Lord realm cultivation. Some of them were even World Kings.

These people observed Lin Ming’s actions with their dark divine runic secret techniques. They emitted their soul perception, taking note of his every movement. This was an extremely impolite action but none of them were worried because their cultivations were far higher than Lin Ming’s, and in addition to their unique dark divine runic techniques that spied on others, even if they were to spy on people with a similar boundary they still wouldn’t be discovered.

“Hehe… if you can really prove that then I will certainly believe you will honor those 500 promissory notes. I have no problem with that.”

Shadow Overflow licked his withered lips, tamping down the excitement and hope in his heart. He agreed to Lin Ming proving himself by drawing up the divine runic symbol in front of everyone.

“Then hurry up and begin!”

Many people urged from beneath the auction stage. Many of these people were part of the ordinary audience who shouted out purely because they wanted to experience the birth of a miracle with their own eyes. But, many of them were also dark divine runic masters hidden in the crowd.

“Alright.”

Lin Ming languidly laid out a divine runic pen as well as a simple array disc commonly used to draw divine runic symbols. But, he didn’t immediately take out the materials. Rather, he stood there, his hands behind his back as he slyly smiled at Shadow Overflow.

Seeing Lin Ming’s eyes on him, Shadow Overflow felt his heart skip a beat. He didn’t know why, but Lin Ming’s eyes seemed to see through him, causing a chill to creep up his back.

“W-what are you…”

Shadow Overflow saw Lin Ming stare at him for several breaths of time and faltered a little. He frowned, “How come you aren’t drawing the Heavenly Fire Symbol? Were you just bluffing all this time?”

He was deliberately stirring up Lin Ming, but how could Lin Ming fall for this bait?

Lin Ming suddenly smiled and stared at Shadow Overflow’s obscured face. After a long pause, Lin Ming then slowly said, “Yes, I do believe… I know who you are…”

Shadow Overflow never imagined that Lin Ming would say such words. His body shook and he nearly lost his balance as he floated in the air.

His eyebrows wrinkled together. He pretended to be calm, “I have no idea what you are speaking about!”

“Mm, it’s fine as long as you know who you are… isn’t that right, Grandmaster Overflow…?”

Lin Ming unhurriedly said without a hint of doubt in his voice. His lips curved up in a playful smile. With this, the entire audience was stunned!

Shadow Overflow had risen to fame many years ago and was far more famous and well-known than Lin Ming was!

Even those that didn’t belong to the world of divine runic arts knew the name of Shadow Overflow. Or better to say, they knew of his infamy. He was a notoriously cruel character, evil and vicious, a completely abhorrent person!

Not only did he copy the divine runic symbols of others, but his character was poor and he was sinister and vicious, a bloodthirsty and lustful man!

He plundered the proud young female disciples of small sects to use as his living furnaces, and killed off tens of millions of mortals as a sacrifice to refine his ghost streamer. In short, he was a man that stooped to any evils!

It was also said he gathered thousands of proud women to establish his harem. Wherever he went he would have squads of golden-armored warriors following him as well as dozens of charming maids. He would have flood dragons pulling his carriage and spirit flower petals would sprinkle the ground ahead of him. This opulent transportation was just like a divine emperor travelling abroad!

Towards this type of person, many people felt nothing but utter scorn.

Shadow Overflow’s complexion became increasingly ugly. He couldn’t figure out how Lin Ming had discovered his identity!

He had never met Lin Ming openly face-to-face, and even when they briefly bumped into each other he had used all sorts of arcane techniques to conceal his cultivation and aura. In this situation, Lin Ming was still able to recognize him!

Could it be that… he had sensed his divine runic arts technique?

How was this possible… he was only a Divine Lord and also a mere human, so how could Lin Ming discover his sense!

Shadow Overflow could not believe this!

And his guess was right; Lin Ming had discovered Shadow Overflow’s dark divine runic arts technique!

Lin Ming had inherited Torchriver’s memories. Torchriver was not some good or righteous individual and he also had an understanding of the spying arts of dark divine runic masters. As for Lin Ming, because he had a powerful soul force and he also cultivated the Divine Mist Heart Mantra, he had an extremely keen sense. He was able to instantly catch onto Shadow Overflow’s spying sense and then contrast it with Torchriver’s memories to understand what it was.

A dark divine runic master that he couldn’t see the cultivation of, they had to be at least at the sixth grade or peak sixth grade.

Such a dark divine runic master was hostile towards him and had been targeting him from the very start of the auction fair. When all of these factors were combined, Lin Ming didn’t need to be a genius to know it was that Grandmaster Overflow who had tried to rashly unravel his Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol and had lost several hundreds of millions of points as a result!

Seeing Shadow Overflow continue putting on an act at this moment, Lin Ming smiled and said, “Grandmaster Overflow, I’ve heard so much about your grand name before, but, I must apologize for meeting you under such circumstances. I wonder, have you fixed those array discs you broke when you tried to unravel my Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol?”

Lin Ming’s words were brutal enough, especially to be said in the presence of everyone. No matter how patient Shadow Overflow was, even he couldn’t withstand such shame.

The defeat of that research team was an eternal pain in his heart. Not only was it a loss of wealth but more importantly a loss of his reputation and an impact on his confidence!

From the depths of his soul, he wished that he could flay Lin Ming alive!

And at this time, all of the other dark divine runic masters in attendance felt a foreboding premonition rise over their hearts. Seeing the situation turn bad, all of them withdrew the spying sense they had cast on Lin Ming and restrained their auras in fear of being discovered.

But this sudden change left Lin Ming chuckling. He walked forwards several steps and swept his eyes over the entire audience.

His eyes paused in several places before he slowly said, “I haven’t even started to draw anything so why would all of you retreat like this? Just now it seems there were… 19 senses… hmm, I wonder if I missed any?”

As Lin Ming spoke, all of the dark divine runic masters in the audience felt their hearts skip a beat, a cold sweat forming on their backs!

They had stretched out their sense to peek at Lin Ming, but their sense had been noticed by him. It was just like a few thieves entering a mansion to steal some items. Even if they tried to cover their tracks there would still be clues.

Although they knew there were over a dozen some people that had also stretched out their senses, they couldn’t affirm whether it was truly such a precise number like 19!

Chapter 1642 – Lin Ming VS Shadow Overflow

Lin Ming took out a specialized divine runic table from his spatial ring as well as various piles of materials.

As Lin Ming took out the materials, he no longer concealed any of his actions from the spying Shadow Overflow. Shadow Overflow’s neck was stretched out like a rooster as he licked his dry lips. His complete focus was concentrated on Lin Ming’s every move lest he miss a single detail.

“The materials he uses aren’t strange; they are all materials required for drawing a Heavenly Fire Symbol. There are also several more types…” Shadow Overflow mumbled, “They aren’t too cheap but they aren’t too expensive either.”

Shadow Overflow instantly judged.

At this time Elder Xue had already picked up some of the materials and began processing them with precise skills. He removed the inferior parts of materials and then broke them down…

Lin Ming took out some nine-flame grass. His fingertips were like precise scalpels as he made an accurate cut on each blade of grass.

His soul force merged into the nine-flame grass, immediately drawing out the essence of the juice.

A strange tractive force emerged from Lin Ming’s palm, cleanly pulling out every drop of essence juice. His fingers seemed to dance in the air, every movement he made like passing clouds and flowing water, smooth and clean, giving off a whole and balanced feeling.

As they said, laymen watched for fun, experts watched for interest.

In the eyes of ordinary people, Lin Ming’s movements only had a faint aesthetic sense.

But for some divine runic masters, the more they watched the more immersed they were. Without knowing it, they began to mimic Lin Ming’s movements, drawing their hands in the void to capture the precise trajectories of his movements.

They knew that these ghostly movements involved the subtle changes in angle and power of extracting the juices.

These changes seemed ordinary but there was actually a profound meaning behind them. Only these divine runic masters were able to sense some of the mysteries within.

Shadow Overflow’s face darkened. Just Lin Ming’s movements in extracting the essence of the juice were enough to leave many fifth grade divine runic masters red with shame!

Drawing up a divine runic symbol was in many ways a form of art.

Lin Ming focused all of his concentration into drawing the divine runic symbol. After completing the first step of extracting the essence of the materials, he directly stepped into the next stage.

The divine runic pen dipped into the juice essence and drew a bright path through the air like a chain of stars. A brilliant soul force spilled out into the void, marking the juice essence.

As Lin Ming began to draw up the tiny runes, he perfectly calculated every small change in his mind.

These deductions were accumulated over the last several months. Even the slightest possible change was recorded in his mind. Now, all he needed to do was to perfectly display them.

Every tiny rune was like a tiny flower that bloomed on his fingertips.

Small lines of soul force appeared between the tiny runes, interspersed, connecting them together, revealing a sense of mystery and beauty.

Even for those that didn’t understand the divine runic arts, this was a shockingly beautiful scene.

To think that the decidedly dull divine runic arts could be so enchanting.

At this time, Shadow Overflow’s eyes were fanatical. His body shivered as he held his breath and focused on Lin Ming’s every moment, recording even the smallest detail into his mind.

The other divine runic masters who had spent points all remembered Lin Ming’s movements with everything they had.

However, they discovered that they weren’t able to follow him!

It wasn’t that they couldn’t remember Lin Ming’s movements, nor was it that they couldn’t see the tiny runes he drew up, but because they didn’t know what the meaning behind his drawing was!

Even if they used all sorts of dark divine runic analyzing techniques, they still couldn’t analyze just how these tiny runes were connected.

Once they missed the tiniest detail, it was easy to be lost on every following stroke.

Some dark divine runic masters had already begun dripping with a cold sweat!

Lin Ming took a long time to draw up the Heavenly Fire Symbol. In the blink of an eye, six hours had passed.

This wasn’t an easy process for Lin Ming. His forehead was dripping with crystal clear beads of sweat. As for Xiao Moxian standing beside him, she didn’t even dare to help wipe Lin Ming, lest she disturb him.

After those several months of attempts, Lin Ming’s chances of drawing up those two improved divine runic symbols had greatly increased.

For the Heretical God Symbol, he had a 60-70% chance of success. As for the Heavenly Fire Symbol, he had a 90% chance of success.

A 90% chance couldn’t be considered a guaranteed 100% success rate. But, if Lin Ming revolved the Divine Mist Heart Mantra to the limit and didn’t hesitate to consume every last bit of his soul force to draw up the Heavenly Fire Symbol, then he could bring the success rate up to 100%!

As the last tiny rune appeared in the void, the 2000+ runes seemed to come to life. As they floated in the air, they looked like a galaxy, exuding a vast aura of energy.

Om ~ !

A pitch black power of fire submerged into the middle of the runes, carrying with it a strange aura of Laws.

This flame was the nirvanic flames that Lin Ming possessed!

“Xian’er!” Lin Ming said. In truth, he didn’t need to say anything; Xiao Moxian was already transferring the nirvanic flames into him where they gathered into the divine runic symbol.

Xiao Moxian’s nirvanic flames were far purer than Lin Ming’s.

This scene left many in the audience startled with amazement. This black-clothed young girl had followed Lin Ming everywhere. They originally thought she was only a flower vase that was there to look good, but they never imagined the flames she commanded could be so pure. Moreover, her attainments in the Fire Laws seemed to have reached… the seventh level Concept!!

This was a boundary that left many fire-attribute World Kings weeping with shame! And this young girl also seemed to be of similar age and cultivation to Lin Ming.

Just what in the world was this? Wasn’t this just a match made in heaven? This was too odd!

At this time, Lin Ming’s actions sped up. His hands left afterimages in the air as he fused tiny bits of pitch black flames into the center of each rune.

All of these runes seemed to have been gifted with life. A small dark phoenix was stored into each one, shaking as if they wanted to spread their wings and soar away.

Dark flames jumped over all the runes, dancing amongst them.

Everyone watched with bated breath, not even daring to blink their eyes in case there was the smallest change in the flame runes.

Shadow Overflow watched all the more intensely. He even stopped breathing. The most critical time had come!

What he didn’t understand the most was how Lin Ming fused the Asura Heavenly Dao into the divine runic symbol. But now, Lin Ming was beginning this third step, the fusion of the Asura Heavenly Dao!

Lin Ming flicked his finger and a deep blue god rune shot out. This was a rare blue soul level god rune and one of the necessary materials.

At this time, the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws descended, drawing unbelievable lines in space. The path of these lines was elusive and unpredictable. Ordinary people only needed to glance at them a single time to feel dizzy.

“This is it! This is it!”

Shadow Overflow widened his eyes so much that they nearly popped out of their sockets. This was the moment he had been waiting for! But, he was completely unable to understand the pattern of these Laws at all! He wildly roared in his heart. At this time, a brilliant white light flooded out, covering Shadow Overflow’s field of vision. Even so, he wasn’t willing to close his eyes. He stubbornly persisted even as the light scorched him and his eyes turned blood red!

This was a brilliance radiated by the Asura Heavenly Dao. Even a World King powerhouse would feel pained by staring into this light. As for a Divine Lord or Holy Lord realm powerhouse that didn’t understand the Asura Heavenly Dao, they might have simply lost their eyesight by now!

Shadow Overflow’s eyes began to drip blood. He naturally knew that these strange patterns were the true reason as to why Lin Ming’s divine runic arts were so powerful!

However, even though he used all the dark divine runic arts techniques at his disposal, even though his eyes bled, he still wasn’t able to read the patterns or comprehend what was happening!

“How could this be!! Where have I gone wrong!?!?”

Shadow Overflow nearly went crazy as he tried to grasp something. However, time was rapidly passing.

When that endless brilliant glory condensed together, it converged with all the strange Heavenly Dao Law patterns, condensing onto a single ordinary symbol paper.

Heavenly Fire Symbol – complete!

Lin Ming let out a long breath of relief. He had consumed a great deal of energy just now. In order to guarantee a 100% success rate with this Heavenly Fire symbol, Lin Ming hadn’t held back any use of his soul force. This also made the Heavenly Fire Symbol he just drew even more perfect!

After finishing all of this, Lin Ming fell onto the divine runic table, propping himself up with his right hand.

As for Old Xue, he had already hurriedly received the divine runic symbol.

Closing his eyes, Old Xue sensed the runic structure within and sighed in praise!

“Good brat, this Heavenly Fire Symbol is even better than the first one I used!”

Old Xue’s words caused the audience to gasp in marvel. At this time, without saying a word further, Song Wen immediately activated the testing array formation!

Even though no one suspected Lin Ming any longer, only by witnessing the truth for themselves could they be shocked!

When the dreamscape of the Great Desolate appeared and the vicious beasts manifested, a dreadful explosion filled the air and roiling flames surged forth. Old Xue’s actions were quick and decisive. He used the Heavenly Fire Symbol that Lin Ming just made to burn down a World King vicious beast!

This power was far too terrifying! It was even stronger than the first test!

If this were used by a peak Holy Lord, then although the strength would be weaker than that displayed by Old Xue, as long as it struck it wouldn’t be a problem to severely wound a World King!

At the conclusion of the test, Old Xue glanced at Shadow Overflow with relish in his eyes. He cheekily grinned and said, “I must say Old Shadow, I think you nearly snapped your neck in half trying to get a good look just now. Tell me, did you discover anything interesting?” Although Old Xue wasn’t a dark divine runic master, he could tell from Shadow Overflow’s grim complexion that he hadn’t had any harvests at all. At this time, Shadow Overflow’s face was darker than the bottom of a pot!

Shadow Overflow didn’t say anything. He composed himself, deeply staring at Lin Ming, not bothering to conceal the deep killing intent in his eyes. Then, without further ado, he silently returned to his VIP suite.

“I won’t see you off.” Song Wen faintly smiled. He stepped onto the auction stage and loudly said, “Everyone, the auction will begin soon. Little Brother Lin…”

“Of course.” Lin Ming responded. He took out a special symbol and used a divine runic pen to leave behind a soul force mark. This mark had Lin Ming’s unique soul fluctuations within it; it was impossible to fake.

Song Wen used this light promissory note that Lin Ming just drew up and placed it on the auction stage platform. He said, “Everyone, my Divine Rune City Auction House will now auction off Mister Lin’s promissory note. If there is no objection, then we shall begin!”

Chapter 1643 – Sky High Auction Bid

“President Song, hurry up with the auction. Sir Lin has already proven his strength. If he wishes to sell those promissory notes then Setting Sun City’s Far East Family is willing to bid!”

“I am Great Yang City’s Ouyang Hou, I am also willing to…”

For a time, many people were shouting out loud, urging Song Wen to hurry with the auction.

Seeing this, Song Wen faintly smiled. “Since everyone feels this way I won’t waste your time with idle talk. The auction shall now begin. The base price is zero! Every increase in price cannot be less than 20 million!”

Zero base price?

As Song Wen’s voice fell, everyone was stirred into an uproar.

Song Wen starting the base price at zero was in order to have all the bidders lose any sort of standard in their heart. It was impossible for them to weigh the value of these 500 Heavenly Fire Symbols. Like this, it was possible to produce a sky high bid!

On the other hand, setting a high base bid at the start would cause many people to lose all courage to bid. This would dampen the atmosphere and prevent the fiery competition required.

This was the first time that Song Wen was auctioning promissory notes; before this, he had never tried before. This was simply an amazing precedent, especially for the Divine Rune City Auction House that was renowned throughout the entire inner Asura Road.

If these promissory notes had sold for a low price then the Divine Rune City Auction House would be mocked by their peers. But now, it seemed the chances of that were extremely low!

And once sold for a dramatic amount, Divine Rune City Auction House would actually create a legend!

“100 million!”

Someone shouted out from the lower seats.

“150 million!”

“200 million!”

Just as that person finished bidding another person immediately increased the bid. There were even several people shouting at once.

As the auction started, many of the martial artists in the scattered lower seats were impatiently bidding.

100 million? 200 million?

“This is just a joke!”

The first person who urged President Song, Far East Miao from Setting Sun City, suddenly sneered.

Lin Ming had just drawn up a divine runic symbol and had even received an 800 million advance to do so. Wasn’t it just an insult to bid 100-200 million?

At this time, Far East Miao stood up and loudly shouted, “My Far East Family bids 1.3 billion!”

Those with different status and perspective often had decidedly different judgments.

Many people in the lower seats were shocked. They had shouted out 100-200 million just then, but now someone had shouted out a bid of over a billion. This was just a bit too odd for them.

“1.4 billion!”

An indifferent voice shouted out from the VIP suites. It was unknown who the bidder was.

“1.5 billion!” Suya’s senior-apprentice brother suddenly shouted after a moment of silence,

The Extreme Star Holy Lands definitely wouldn’t miss out on shouting a bid!

As it was, they had already missed a chance to be on good terms with Lin Ming. After experiencing Lin Ming’s monstrous talent in the divine runic arts, who would miss out on a second time?

And, what was even more important was that if they obtained these fifth grade divine runic symbols from Lin Ming, the effects they would have on their war against the Heaven Strife Holy Lands would be immeasurable!

Of course, Suya’s senior-apprentice brother knew that 1.5 billion was only the start. Wanting to buy these Heavenly Fire Symbols with this amount was far from enough.

“1.8 billion…” On the west side, a crisp voice sounded out from a mysterious VIP suite. As Suya’s senior-apprentice brother thought, 1.5 billion fell far short of being enough.

At this time, no one in the lower seats was able to speak.

This was now a battle between the VIP suites!

The shouts of bids had already slowed down. It wasn’t that 1.8 billion approached the upper limits of the Heavenly Fire Symbols’ value, but because many people in the VIP suites were using secret techniques to contact their headquarters.

Of these people, many of them had tools similar to the Thousand Mile Heartlink. As long as they were all in the same universe they could contact each other no matter how far they were.

“High Elder, there is an urgent matter I must report to you. There is a talented divine runic master that has produced a batch of divine runic symbols… these are promissory notes. Don’t be startled, please allow me to explain…”

“Open the image transmitting array. I must transmit an image of the fifth grade Heavenly Fire Symbol to the Sovereign… I must ask the Sovereign to authorize at least 2.5 billion points for us to bid with…”

When Old Xue tested the Heavenly Fire Symbol, there was a good number of people who were interested and had recorded a phantom video with array discs.

As multiple sound transmission stones lit up throughout the VIP suites, more and more influences joined in on the auction!

“I haven’t even finished speaking with headquarters and the bid has risen to 2 billion! These damned people!”

Suya angrily thought. She had just applied for 2 billion points with some difficulty, but just as she was about to call out a bid, the current bid had surpassed 2 billion! It seemed that even 2.5 billion wouldn’t be enough!

“Junior-apprentice Sister Suya, don’t worry. The Sovereign is already contacting several Elders of the Heavenly Palace to have them help.”

Because of the war against the Heaven Strife Holy Lands, the sect reserves of the Extreme Star Holy Lands had nearly run dry.

To increase the bid again, that would be with the Elders taking out their own private wealth and adding it together. Once the sect regained their strength these Elders would naturally be repaid.

As the bid climbed to 2.3 billion, the entire auction hall arena had calmed down.

To bid 2.3 billion for promissory notes written by Lin Ming, this was simply a crazy scenario!

“2.5 billion!” Setting Sun City’s Far East Miao shouted out between clenched teeth. However, even though he had tossed all his chips onto the table, he still wasn’t able to stop the price from dramatically rising.

And 2.5 billion wasn’t even high enough to give Song Wen a chance to start a countdown. At this time, Suya emerged from her VIP suite. She gracefully floated in the skies of the arena hall and clearly said, “2.6 billion!”

Suya had already applied for all the points she could. Originally, she thought that it was enough but now she realized it wasn’t. The points she had requested had all been reserved. If she had used too many then they really wouldn’t be able to win the white birch spirit root later!

However, the Vice Palace Master had informed her that they could find other solutions to search for points for the white birch spirit root.

Seeing Suya push the bid to nearly 3 billion points, Far East Miao’s complexion changed. Even 2.5 billion wasn’t enough to shake off these competitors. He had wanted to obtain these 500 Heavenly Fire Symbols no matter what and had applied for a massive volume of points to do so. But, he never thought that the auction battle for these promissory notes would intensify to such a brutal degree!

He lifted his hand, wanting to bid once more. However, his hand was shaking already. This was not a small number! It wouldn’t be something their Far East Family would be able to easily withstand.

He grit his teeth, wanting to raise the bid once more. But at this time, from the highest sections of the VIP suites, a dignified voice echoed out. “3 billion!”

This voice shocked everyone. They all looked towards the VIP suite that shouted this price and as they did they all sucked in a breath of cold air.

Those were the rooms of Empyrean Lionheart!

Empyrean Lionheart had actually shouted out a price!

Since the auction started, the two Empyreans here had yet to say a single word. It was clear that up until now, there was nothing that was able to arouse their interest.

But now, Empyrean Lionheart actually spoke for the first time, and his first words were to issue a mindboggling bid!

Before this, who would have thought that an Empyrean level character’s first words at the Divine Rune City Auction would be to call out a sky high bid, and all for the promissory notes of a Divine Lord realm junior!

“3… 3 billion…”

Hearing Empyrean Lionheart’s voice, Far East Miao paled and slumped back into his seat. 3 billion was a bid that caused him to lose all heart to continue bidding. With the background of their Far East Family, they had no qualifications to struggle with Empyrean Lionheart.

To compete with an Empyrean… not everyone had the courage to do so. This was not just pressure that came from a high bid, but pressure that came from strength. How could common martial artists dare to struggle with an Empyrean?

But at this time, from another VIP suite, Suya bit her lips. With an unwilling expression she took a deep breath and called out, “3.1 billion!”

This feminine voice had a powerful piercing strength, spreading through the entire audience. For a time, Suya caught the attention of everyone!

The audience was shocked. This woman dared to challenge Empyrean Lionheart!

At this time, Suya’s milk-white breasts were violently heaving. Her back and her palms were both wet with sweat! To compete with an Empyrean was to directly face their majesty and dignity; this was an incredible level of pressure.

“3.2 billion!”

Empyrean Lionheart spoke out again, raising the bid once more!

“3.3 billion!”

Suya seemed to have been roused to anger. She refused to concede!

“Oh?” Empyrean Lionheart’s eyebrow arched up. He fell quiet for several breaths of time, and then his voice once again spread through the entire audience. “3.6 billion!”

Empyrean Lionheart had poured a powerful momentum into his voice, making anyone who listened feel afraid to disobey.

As soon as this bid of 3.6 billion was called out, everyone in the audience felt their hearts shake!

Suya was also pale white. Through today’s sudden development she had been keeping in contact with the Extreme Star Holy Lands even as she engaged in a bidding battle with an Empyrean; she was already unable to continue!

“Junior-apprentice Sister, please give up! Don’t fight anymore, we’ll have more opportunities in the future.” Suya’s senior-apprentice brother said, feeling a little bitter.

At this time, Suya’s cheeks were blushing red and she was dripping fragrant sweat.

She bit her lips as if she wanted to bid again but she didn’t have the energy to break past the barrier of 3.6 billion that Empyrean Lionheart had set up.

At this time, her eyes touched upon Lin Ming. Although his expression was indifferent, his lips still moved as he spoke two simple words to her.

Suya was stunned. Lin Ming had said, “Don’t worry.”

With these two simple words, Suya felt the tight pressure over her heart lighten.

She knew that Lin Ming would certainly have another way to help her so that she wouldn’t need to struggle with something she couldn’t win against.

Suya’s heart warmed. Her nose burned just a little.

“Thank you…”

Suya replied as she slumped down in her VIP suite. Even if Lin Ming didn’t say anything she truly didn’t have the means to continue competing for the bid.

“3.6 billion, is there anyone willing to bid higher?”

Song Wen’s eyes flitted over the audience. His gaze stopped on the VIP suite of another Empyrean – Empyrean Minor Violet. However, this famous woman Empyrean had yet to say a single word.

He counted down. No one challenged the current bid price.

“Then, I declare that Lin Ming’s promissory note of 500 Heavenly Fire Symbols has sold for 3.6 billion points! Congratulations to Empyrean Lionheart!”

Song Wen loudly proclaimed as he struck his mallet against the podium. At this time, even his hands were shaking!

In Song Wen’s life he had already presided over countless auctions. There were even many treasures he had auctioned off which sold for far more than 3.6 billion. But, to auction a promissory note for 3.6 billion, that was definitely a first!

That meant that on average, every Heavenly Fire Symbol sold for 7.2 million! This was a truly mindboggling price!

By relying on these Heavenly Fire Symbols, Lin Ming had drawn up a single one and had auctioned off 500 in advance for a total gain of 4.37 billion points!

Earning this amount of points so quickly couldn’t even be described as crazy!

The final bid price of 3.6 billion left the entire audience stewing in silence for some time.

After a while, there was a round of applause from the audience that originated from their innermost respect and shock.

Afterwards, through the representatives sent to the auction by the various influences, this news spread out via a variety of means!

If these were ordinary times, then people would suspect this was just some fake hype being created, or that the one buying was an idiot. But, the final bidder to win was Empyrean Lionheart!

Who would dare say that Empyrean Lionheart was an idiot? Empyrean Lionheart’s judgment was far from what an ordinary person could compare with!

Moreover, with the status of an Empyrean, how could they possibly work with an auction house as a bid manipulator?

With this, no one dared to question the veracity of this news!

The Divine Rune City Auction had originally been under the attention of many people and had been a great topic of discussion. But after this event, it was like a wildfire had been set off!

The one to sell the promissory note was only a human, Divine Lord realm junior!

Not just that, but this Divine Lord realm junior had drawn up a divine runic symbol in front of an audience of hundreds of thousands, including even Grandmaster Overflow and over a dozen other dark divine runic masters!

And what was even more ridiculous was that not only did this Divine Lord realm junior not fear these dark divine runic masters copying his techniques, but he instead forced them to hand over almost 800 million points as a viewing fee!

From the complexions of Shadow Overflow and those dark divine runic masters, the audience had been able to speculate that they hadn’t been able to learn anything at all, even after paying the fee to spy!

This left many people even more panic-stricken, causing the news to spread further out!

For a time, news of ‘an Empyrean spent 3.6 billion points buying a promissory note’, and ‘a Divine Lord realm junior spent less than a day to earn 4.37 billion points’ spread throughout the various intelligence networks. Many people spoke of this in restaurants and city squares. This news could be said to overwhelm the world!

This also caused the popularity of this year’s Divine Rune City Auction to dramatically rise!

Because of this news, many people began to rush towards Divine Rune City. Seeing was believing. All of them found it hard to believe that a Divine Lord realm junior was able to accomplish such miracles.

However, matters didn’t end here!

As everyone believed that the auction of the Heavenly Fire Symbol promissory note was the greatest and most explosive news of the Divine Rune City auction, and would even surpass all other news that the other surrounding auction houses would be able to come up with, the Divine Runic Masters Guild actually released yet another astonishing burst of news!

It was that, in half a month, the creator of the improved Heavenly Fire Symbol would hold an auction for another improved version of a divine runic symbol – the Heretical God Symbol!

As for this Heretical God Symbol, its power even surpassed that of the Heavenly Fire Symbol! All representatives of great influences were invited to attend the Divine Rune City Auction!

For a time, many great influences within the inner Asura Road began to stir.

Even many Empyrean level characters started to quietly enter Divine Rune City…

Chapter 1645 – Offensive and Defensive

Deep in the yellow sands, one could see two faint tornado-like things sweep up into the air.

In the depths of these yellow tornados, two eyes shined like lanterns in the dark.

As the tornados appeared, one could see an approaching creature whose entire body was wrapped in thick earth-yellow scales, bizarre and otherworldly.

“That’s a mystic yellow tihu!”

In the audience, many people immediately recognized the vicious beast produced by the illusory magic array. The mystic yellow tihu didn’t possess a strong striking power but its defenses were extremely formidable.

Deep in the distant Great Desolate, there were powerhouses that used this vicious beast as a moving castle to lead their people around.

The defensive capabilities of this creature were several times that of an ordinary World King! It even achieved the standard of a weak Great World King!

The Divine Rune City Auction House was actually testing the Heretical God Symbol with this kind of vicious beast. If so, that meant they had full confidence in the strength of the Heretical God Symbol!

“Could it be that this Heretical God Symbol can injure a Great World King?”

The entire audience fell quiet. Many people looked at Lin Ming with rapt attention, waiting for the answer to be shown.

Lin Ming took up the Heretical God Symbol in his palm. Pitch black flames and blazing purple thunder flashed together. At the same time, countless Asura Heavenly Dao Laws gathered together, connecting with the thunder and fire in Lin Ming’s palm.

Seeing as the power of thunder and fire fused together with the Asura Laws, in that moment, Lin Ming’s sense and the perception of time seemed to slow down to a crawl, like the slowly flowing grains of sand in an hourglass.

Pulled up by Lin Ming’s soul force, the Heretical God Symbol floated up in front of him.

Lin Ming raised his left and right hands. Using his two index fingers, he pierced towards the Heretical God Symbol, causing two light ripples to spread out like a rock hitting a lake surface.

His two pupils immediately flashed with a jolt of electricity that twined around one ripple.

Then, a thin strand of black fire twined around the other ripple.

In front of him, waves of substantialized soul force appeared. The two ripples began to twist in the air as if they were being manipulated by an invisible hand, quickly twisting until they seemed like images of blooming flowers.

The entire process seemed very slow, but it was also completed almost instantly.

And just a few miles away from Lin Ming, at the edges of the desert, one could see those two faint tornados rolling towards him, leaving a swallowed world in their wake.

As for Lin Ming, he remained motionless. All that remained in front of him were these two flashes of thunder and fire.

The auction house’s testing array formation was different from the rented testing array formation at the Divine Runic Masters Guild. The rented testing array formation was only an illusory magic array, but this one being activated right now was actually a true illusory killing array!

If one stood motionless and allowed the array formation to freely attack them then they would definitely be grievously wounded!

“What is Lin Ming doing? Has he not activated that Heretical God Symbol? That mystic yellow tihu is about to trample over him!”

But as everyone saw Lin Ming control the faint circles of thunder and fire around him and yet the Heretical God Symbol didn’t activate, some people began to develop doubts. Just what was Lin Ming doing?

If Lin Ming was luring the mystic yellow tihu to close range before he detonated the Heretical God Symbol, then he too would be affected by the explosion if the beast was too close!!

Then, people watched as the mystic yellow tihu crossed the 100 foot line from Lin Ming. That distance was the best chance to detonate the Heretical God Symbol!

At this time, the two groups of energy around Lin Ming began to produce tiny patterns of energy composed of threads smaller than silk. These lines of energy pulled into the void, developing into numerous patterns.

In just a twinkle of the eye, a series of thin energy lines spread out, surrounding Lin Ming. Moreover, these energy lines were all different from each other. They were energy patterns that those present had never seen before, and seemed to contain tens of millions of possible changes within them. Each energy line seemed to entangle with the others, inspiring more and more changes. In just an instant, half of these energy lines that were drawn out developed into threads of shining lightning and the other half developed into glistening threads of fire, rapidly condensing into a red and purple two-colored array diagram.

At this time, the tyrannical tsunami of sand that rushed over struck Lin Ming, but was completely submerged into the thunderfire array diagram in his hand.

Seeing this, Xiao Moxian couldn’t help but cry out in alarm. Although she knew in her heart that Lin Ming was safe, she still couldn’t avoid her heart clenching upon seeing such a sight.

Bang!

A massive explosion occurred!

The mystic yellow tihu with its incomparably firm body and its maximum velocity crashed into the thunderfire array diagram!

It was a meteor impacting into the earth. A powerful impact swept outwards, bringing up waves of yellow sand that were tens of thousands of tons heavy!

This terrifying strength left the entire auction hall shaking! Everyone found it hard to remain still and some of the weaker martial artists couldn’t help but cry out in alarm.

Lin Ming hadn’t attacked from beginning to end. Instead, he used the thunderfire array diagram to block the frontal dash of the mystic yellow tihu!

As the yellow sands settled, everyone saw that the mystic yellow tihu had its head left bloodstained after colliding with the thunderfire array diagram. As for the thunder array diagram, it only slightly bent without any sign of breaking! By using the power of the Heretical God Symbol alone, Lin Ming had defended against an attack with the all-out strength of an ordinary World King.

Could this be a defensive divine runic symbol?

Everyone immediately thought. A defensive divine runic symbol was rarely seen and was often much more expensive than offensive divine runic symbols.

But when they heard the description from Divine Rune City, the Heretical God Symbol should have been an immensely destructive divine runic symbol!

Before people had more time to think, Lin Ming suddenly grasped the Heretical God Symbol with both hands and pushed it out.

The palm-sized Heretical God Symbol suddenly rose and countless threads of thunder and fire spun around until they formed a massive vortex, instantly covering the heavens and earth. This vortex formed a giant web that wrapped around the massive mystic yellow tihu.

In that moment, within the endless yellow sands, a brilliant light erupted like a rising sun.

In the middle of this light, crackling bolts of thunder twisted around with a conflagration of raging flames.

The flames and thunder twisted together, roaring like the birth of a fire dragon and thunder dragon.

Several hundred earth-shaking explosions echoed out from the midst of the giant vortex of raging flames and twisting thunder, illuminating the world like a descending apocalypse.

Thunder collapsed the earth as snakes of fire shot to the heavens.

Within this vortex, the mystic yellow tihu roared out again and again, but its howls slowly turned lower and deeper as it gradually faded away…

The explosions produced a brilliant light that formed an incomparably thick swirling column of thunder and fire. As it rapidly spun around, the world seemed to tear apart around it as the surrounding ground caved in, forming a massive crater hundreds of miles deep.

From where the explosions occurred, a pit so deep appeared that one couldn’t see the bottom.

The mystic yellow tihu’s scales had nearly all fallen off. Its giant tail dangled to the ground.

Although it was still living, it was on the verge of death, approaching death with every breath it took.

“Within the Heretical God Symbol, the mark of the Asura Heavenly Dao patterns will reverse in the void to reform yin yang patterns of the Asura Heavenly Dao… this also agrees with the true meaning of the Extreme Dual Polarity Symbol, the absolute polars of thunder and fire… the power is as expected. Moreover, with the revolution of yin and yang, it can attack but also instantly form a defensive barrier when the symbol is activated!”

Drops of sweat dripped down the tip of Lin Ming’s nose. He was extremely satisfied with the performance of the Heretical God Symbol.

In creating the Heretical God Symbol, Lin Ming had consumed a great deal of effort and diligent care. As he created the Heretical God Symbol, his comprehension of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws also became much deeper…

At this time, in all the rooms and seats, everyone had forgotten how to speak.

This was a dual offensive and defensive divine runic symbol!

Normally, divine runic symbols were one-time use items that could either be used to defend or attack. But, the net of thunder and fire formed by the Heretical God Symbol was an offensive and defensive form!

Imagine. Two martial artists were in a life or death battle and both had utilized all of their abilities and were completely exhausted.

At the end, they both used their ultimate finishing blows. But at this time, one side took out a Heretical God Symbol, defending against the opponent’s attack but also erupting with a terrifying attack, directly covering the enemy in a sea of thunder and flame! Just what sort of effect would that have?

Moreover, this Heretical God Symbol had reached a terrifying degree of strength whether it was in defense or offense. Even that mystic yellow tihu with an incredible defensive power comparable to a weak Great World King had been beaten half-dead!

In other words, even if one were a Great World King, if they didn’t understand the unique attributes of the Heretical God Symbol and were fooled, they would be placed in an extremely difficult situation, possibly even injured!

For a time, the entire castle fell silent. One could clearly hear the breathing of others even from a long distance.

And at this time, that brutal and violent power of thunder and fire in the skies began to gather together. The lines of the Asura Heavenly Dao condensed, forming endless starlight that sprinkled down.

The power of thunderfire and the Asura Heavenly Dao was sucked into a giant vortex. Then, it shrank until it finally transformed into a perfectly intact divine runic symbol that fell into Lin Ming’s hand.

The Heretical God Symbol was reborn!

Seeing this scene, although many people had expected it earlier, they couldn’t help but feel their jaws drop down, shocked speechless.

To be reborn and reused, this was the special attribute of the ‘Lin’ logo!

However, when one considered the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol that wasn’t much stronger than the original, it wasn’t too amazing even if it could be used multiple times.

Following that was the Heavenly Fire Symbol. It was ridiculously powerful, to the point of being obscene. Moreover, it could also be used multiple times. This was far more impressive and also the reason that they sold for a sky high price of 3.6 billion points.

But now, this Heretical God Symbol was both offensive and defensive, and in the attack process there seemed to be all sorts of incredible changes as if there were many more mysteries waiting to be unlocked, but Lin Ming simply hadn’t had the time to reveal them.

This divine runic symbol that could nearly bring the dead back to life in a dire situation, that was so abnormal that it could wound a Great World King, could actually be used multiple times!

This just destroyed all common sense! If one had several Heretical God Symbols in hand, then an ordinary World King would be able to challenge and speak the last words with a weak Great World King!

And if used in a war, there was definitely no need to speak of their efficacy! These were different from the Nirvanic Tribulation Flame Symbol because these Heretical God Symbols could be used in battles between high level figures of the sects. If using a Heretical God Symbol was able to turn certain defeat into victory between a battle of World Kings, then this would be worth an astronomical level of wealth!

It had to be known that every World King was formed by piling up an immense amount of resources!

Thinking of this, the complexions of the several Empyreans in the VIP suites began to change.

Chapter 1648 – All Materials Collected

“From 1.3 billion to 2 billion all of a sudden!?”

The bidders present looked towards the room that Lin Ming was in. To an Empyrean, 2 billion was an amount that would hurt but was still something they could take out. But, those that were competing for the Dragon Contract were mostly World King level characters. 2 billion points was definitely an amount that would bankrupt them.

Lin Ming had suddenly increased the bid by 700 million; it wasn’t a surprise that everyone was shocked.

“That is Lin Ming’s bid!”

“So it’s him…”

In these days, the location of Lin Ming’s ordinary room had already been memorized by many people. Lin Ming didn’t use an isolating array formation either so others were able to see him.

“Lin Ming’s bid will make anyone reconsider this auction. The highest bid Empyrean spirit treasure has only sold for 2 billion so far and that was because it was a battle between two tigers…”

The 2 billion point Empyrean spirit treasure that was referred to was the Violet Gold Spear purchased by Duke Fullmoon.

Besides Suya, no one knew that the reason the Violet Gold Spear sold for such a high price was because Lin Ming was deliberately conning Duke Fullmoon.

And in Lin Ming’s mind, the Dragon Contract was undoubtedly far more valuable than the Violet Gold Spear!

Just the materials used to refine the Dragon Contract alone were worth over a billion points in total.

Moreover, as the Dragon Contract appeared and Song Wen introduced it, Lin Ming had made a new discovery.

It was that sealed within the Dragon Contract, there was the spirit of a True Dragon. It was possible to summon this spirit to aid one in battle.

The so-called spirit of a True Dragon that Song Wen spoke of was in truth an incomplete dragon soul.

The Dragon Contract had a true wisp of an incomplete dragon soul sealed within it! This was why within the name of this spirit artifact there was the word ‘contract’.

A jade dragon horn plus a wisp of a dragon soul, these two divine things were greatly beneficial to Lin Ming. After all, he had the blood of the True Dragon within him. Thus Lin Ming had to win the auction for this Dragon Contract no matter what!

At this time, Lin Ming’s eyes moved over to the VIP suite that Duke Fullmoon was in.

In these past days, Duke Fullmoon had been keeping a low profile and was far more subdued than he was in the past. This was because other high level figures of the Divine Void Divine Kingdom’s Nine Nether Province had come to Divine Rune City and their goal was also to participate in the grand auction event for the Heretical God Symbol.

Through the array formation of the VIP suite, Lin Ming’s eyes and expression were all seen by Duke Fullmoon.

In fact, Duke Fullmoon knew that through the array formations of his suite, it was impossible for Lin Ming to see him. But for some unknown reason, as he caught Lin Ming’s gaze, Duke Fullmoon felt his heart chill and he found it hard to keep looking back at him.

This was the pressure that came from Lin Ming continually suppressing Duke Fullmoon all this time!

“This brat!”

Duke Fullmoon clenched his fists. In his eyes, Lin Ming was only a Divine Lord realm boy, and even with all things considered he was only comparable to a peak Holy Lord. Compared to him, the difference was far from being comparable. However, when he faced Lin Ming he actually felt a bit weak of heart. This feeling of inferiority was extremely uncomfortable to Duke Fullmoon.

At this time, Lin Ming’s lips moved.

Duke Fullmoon was startled. Even through the walls and the isolating array formation, he could still clearly sound out Lin Ming’s unspoken words.

“I indeed have a great interest in this Dragon Contract. If you’re thinking of bleeding me out then you can feel free to shout whatever price you want. But, I won’t guarantee that I won’t stop at any time I wish. If that happens, I hope you have enough points to be responsible for the bid you called out.”

Lin Ming said these words with a confident look. Duke Fullmoon felt ill.

His wealth had just been used to buy up the Violet Gold Spear. Anything left remaining was the wealth of Divine Void Divine Kingdom.

This wealth was all required to buy things desired by the Nine Nether King of the Nine Nether Province; he wasn’t able to use it as he pleased. If Lin Ming decided to give up the auction and Duke Fullmoon was discovered as having bid an exorbitant price on this Dragon Contract, then he would be deader than dead.

He didn’t know just how invested Lin Ming was in obtaining the Dragon Contract. If the events of the Violet Gold Spear were to replay themselves then he really would have no more tears to cry from grief.

If he wanted to struggle with Lin Ming, his entire total wealth now was only around 2 billion points; he simply didn’t have the will or the energy to continue competing. Moreover, his need of the Dragon Contract wasn’t that intense to begin with. Duke Fullmoon didn’t have the courage to play with his life on the line just to try and con Lin Ming out of several hundred million more points.

“Fullmoon, what is it? It seems that Lin Ming is targeting you?”

A blue-clothed old man asked from beside Duke Fullmoon.

This blue-clothed old man was one of the top aides of the Nine Nether King and also possessed a half-step Empyrean cultivation. Within the Nine Nether Province, his status was a level higher than Duke Fullmoon’s.

Concerning Duke Fullmoon and Lin Ming’s conflict, besides Suya and a select few others, no one knew of it. Thus, after the blue-clothed old man arrived at Divine Rune City, even he hadn’t heard any rumors about it.

This question left Duke Fullmoon looking a bit awkward. He vaguely mumbled, “I only competed for a spear against him…”

Duke Fullmoon said, concealing the fact of his conflict with Lin Ming. The blue-clothed old man nodded, “Mm… it’s best if you don’t have any conflicts with Lin Ming. This young divine runic master will have a limitless future! The Nine Nether King has a particular focus on this type of person. When I came to Divine Rune City, he advised me to be on good terms with him if possible; he will surely be a great help to us! You must know that between the Seven Provinces of Divine Void Divine Kingdom, the competition is extremely fierce…”

The blue-clothed old man seemed to guess what was happening. As he looked at Duke Fullmoon he spoke with deep hidden meanings in his voice.

Hearing these words, Duke Fullmoon felt as if he had swallowed a fly.

“What? You have grudges with Lin Ming?” The blue-clothed old man’s eyes were as bright and illuminating as torches. He could see that the conflict between Duke Fullmoon and Lin Ming wasn’t as simple as stated. “No matter what the reason is, it's best if you resolve these grudges if possible…”

Duke Fullmoon clenched his jaws. He tamped down the bitter sadness in his heart and tried to sound as sincere as he could as he said, “Yes… Fullmoon understands!”

After being maliciously tricked by Lin Ming and then reprimanded by this blue-clothed old man, Duke Fullmoon’s mood could be imagined.

……….

“2 billion points, is there a higher bid?”

Song Wen loudly spoke from the auction stage. Potential bidders looked at each other with dismay. Some hesitated, seeming as if they would shout out a higher bid, but eventually none of them could summon the courage to compete with Lin Ming.

Lin Ming’s wealth was well known by all. It was simply impossible to defeat him.

However, those with different boundaries had differences in vision. Some people had a highly exaggerated valuation of the Dragon Contract, similar to Lin Ming. In the eyes of some people, just that wisp of incomplete dragon soul was worth nearly a billion points!

“2.1 billion!” A pale man with red hair and a red beard, dressed in dark blue robes spoke up!

He was a half-step Empyrean powerhouse. In truth, he already possessed an Empyrean spirit treasure but was highly interested in this Dragon Contract!

He was a loner without any influence behind him. Thus, he didn’t care about access to Lin Ming’s divine runic symbols nor did he fear offending Lin Ming.

Originally, most people thought that Lin Ming’s ridiculous bid would already mark the end of this auction. But, they didn’t think that another change would occur.

“Oh? That person is…”

This other person was similar to Lin Ming and sat in an ordinary room without any isolating array formation. This allowed Lin Ming to sense a faint dragon aura coming from his body.

“I see, so this person has a dragon race bloodline relationship…”

Lin Ming frowned a little. There were far too many outstanding existences here. It wasn’t strange for someone to have a dragon race blood lineage.

This meant that to this other person, the Dragon Contract was no less useful than it was for Lin Ming himself!

“2.2 billion!” Lin Ming shouted out, his voice calm.

“2.3 billion!” The old man’s eyebrows jumped up. He knew that Lin Ming was rich but he didn’t know just how valuable this Dragon Contract was to Lin Ming.

This was because of the difference in their bloodline density and purity. The old man’s dragon bloodline was similar to a top figure from the Divine Realm’s Ancient Dragon Clan. But compared to Lin Ming who had absorbed the supreme dragon bone from the God Beast Mystic Realm, who had trained in the Eternal Demon Abyss and within Tragic Death Valley’s God Beast Array Formation where he had undergone a baptism of a Black Dragon’s aura, the differences in bloodline was far too vast. This allowed Lin Ming to sense the bloodline of a dragon within the old man but not the other way around.

“2.4 billion!” Lin Ming flicked his fingers. With this calm tone and expression, it was like points were nothing more than a number to him.

With the bid having reached this degree, the old man’s lips twitched. He gazed at Lin Ming’s direction and quietly said, “Young man, the Dragon Contract is inestimably useful to me. You had best not continue competing for it. If you obtain it you will only gain an Empyrean spirit treasure; that is simply a waste of heaven’s gifts! But if I were to obtain it, the benefits it will give me cannot be imagined by you. I know you are rich, but isn’t your strength limited? Gaining some grievances towards you, that might not best the best thing for you…”

The old man’s words were unhurriedly spoken but carried a faint threat to them.

He lifted his hand once more and grimly said, “2.5 billion!”

“Is that right?” Lin Ming chuckled. “I thought that someone else would be competing with me, but I never imagined it would be someone like you. What a coincidence. The Dragon Contract will also be extremely useful in my hands. As for you… you just have a little bit of a dragon bloodline lineage, do you really think it’s necessary to remain so mysterious about it?”

Lin Ming’s words shocked the old man. The old man immediately felt that this youth speaking to him couldn’t be understood. He had clearly restrained his dragon race aura and yet he had been seen through by Lin Ming. How was this possible?

Lin Ming smirked. “If you want to compete then let us do so fairly and openly. Threatening me? Do you think that’s useful?”

“3 billion!”

Lin Ming raised the bid by another terrifying amount, but his expression still remained calm!

This sort of expression, if placed on anyone else, would have felt like an act. After all, 3 billion was an amount that even an Empyrean would have to mull over.

But for Lin Ming, this expression that didn’t seem to care about money at all was actually reasonable.

Everyone had already witnessed Lin Ming’s horrifying ability to gain wealth. In just half a month and with 2 promissory notes he had earned 10 billion points in wealth. Just who could compare with him?

“You…!”

The old man clenched his teeth and glared at Lin Ming with resentment. But, he remained silent.

No matter how much he desired the Dragon Contract, he could only watch helplessly on as Lin Ming carried it away. 3 billion points had indeed surpassed the limits of his wealth.

“3 billion points, is there a higher bid?”

Song Wen asked several times. When no one put forth a bid, he began counting down from three. Then, in the end, the Dragon Contract was won by Lin Ming!

Hence, to Lin Ming, the Divine Rune City Auction had been perfectly finished. He had obtained everything that he wanted.

Although 3 billion points for the Dragon Contract was bit outrageous, Lin Ming could accept this trade. To him, the Dragon Contract was worth at least 2 billion points to begin with. And now that he had also learned it contained a wisp of a dragon soul, adding in another billion wasn’t too great a loss.

Chapter 1650 – Ancient Contract

Lin Ming’s mind stirred. He took out the jade dragon horn and black dragon egg from his spatial ring. After he obtained the jade dragon horn he had placed it in his spatial ring where he was momentarily keeping the black dragon egg. Because they were now in the same space, there was clearly some change that occurred because of the mutual attraction of their dragon race auras.

The snow white dragon horn was the height of a person. But, when placed next to the dragon egg it seemed the size of a dish.

The pure black egg shell was covered with strange patterns that shifted between light and dark as if the egg were breathing. In the darkness, a soft luster formed from energy surrounded the dragon egg, forming a faint black halo.

And beneath the dragon egg, the snow white dragon horn was emitting a gentle white light.

The sharp contrast of black and white was like a glossy black gem placed in snow.

“Big Brother Lin, I feel that… the jade dragon horn’s dragon spirit has been stirred… it’s likely resonating with the little thing in the black dragon egg…”

Xiao Moxian said from behind Lin Ming. In a daze, she walked forwards and stood in front of the jade dragon horn.

Her eyes were misty as she looked at the jade dragon horn and peaceful black dragon egg. Her hands were lifted in the air, gently weaving through the glossy light emitting from the jade dragon horn, as if she were running her hands in the waters of a lake.

“It’s true, it seems that the dragon spirit within the jade dragon horn is slowly gathering into the dragon egg…” Xiao Moxian dreamily whispered.

Lin Ming closed his eyes, also feeling the same thing.

The dragon spirit within the jade dragon horn was an extremely incomplete and flawed soul. It lacked nearly any sense of self. It was only because of the contract that it was controlled by the master of the Dragon Contract.

Now, although the little being in the black dragon egg wasn’t able to control the Dragon Contract, it seemed as if it was relying on the unique relationship between members of the dragon race to slowly absorb the ancient dragon spirit from the Dragon Contract!

And, this ancient dragon spirit didn’t seem to resist at all.

Lin Ming linked his divine sense with the Dragon Contract and seemed to sense a faintly sad and depressing atmosphere!

Lin Ming had the dragon race bloodline in his body and this allowed him to faintly communicate with the ancient dragon spirit. He could feel its hopelessness and sorrow…

Because the ancient dragon spirit was extremely incomplete, it lacked almost any sense of consciousness.

But, it still had its instinct.

Hundreds of millions of years ago, it had been caged within the jade dragon horn. Sealed by an ancient contract, it had become nothing but a contract puppet!

Time had passed, a hundred million years and then another hundreds million years, repeating again and again.

It had gone through many masters and had even gone into dormancy deep in the depths of ancient ruins. It had travelled through multiple universes and had taken countless lives. But no matter how long the lifespan of a Divine Dragon was, the end of its existence had finally neared. It had transformed into pure soul energy, but even so it was imprisoned by the contract…

It was still regarded as a puppet without a mind of its own, used as a killing tool for its ever-changing masters to fight again and again…

This type of life left the dragon spirit feeling endless sadness and despair!

And now, a familiar bloodline relation of its people was calling to it, summoning it. Without any resistance at all, the dragon spirit allowed itself to be summoned…

For this dragon spirit, rather than being imprisoned forever in this contract, forever unable to reincarnate, allowing itself to become a part of this new life was actually a kind of salvation…

Lin Ming closed his eyes for a long time. After several hours passed he finally opened them.

Amongst the God Beasts, their bloodlines were few and far between. In order to survive, it was much easier for them to trust each other than to trust a human.

Humans’ fighting amongst each other was a common occurrence. In fact, within the great 33 Heavens, whether it was mortals or martial artists of any race, countless lives perished every year.

To struggle for resources, to fight because of grudges, to rob others… innumerable reasons led to the extermination of innumerable lives.

But God Beasts would not do this in most situations. This was because their numbers were far too few. If they fought amongst themselves, it was likely they would all become extinct!

At this time, more and more gentle light emitted from the jade dragon horn. In the void of the divine runic room, the light transformed into a shimmering white dragon. In the midst of this glorious light, an untold number of strange dragon-shaped marks and even life essence began flowing towards the black dragon egg.

This was the essence of the dragon spirit that had been sealed in the Dragon Contract for an unknown number of years. In a sense, it was a type of inheritance.

This was the purest form of its life essence, containing all of its talent, supernatural powers, and so forth.

Lin Ming watched quietly. After a full day passed, the light of the dragon egg began to gradually dim down, and the pulsating lights on the dragon egg also disappeared. The strength of the dragon spirit had completed fused into the black dragon egg, seeming as if nothing had occurred.

Lin Ming silently waited as all of this happened. Even the drawing of the divine runic symbols was momentarily postponed. He was extremely patient. This black dragon egg was his contract beast and their spirits and lives were linked together. He could feel that after absorbing the dragon spirit, the black dragon egg was undergoing a tremendous series of changes!

To hatch a True Dragon, that was absolutely an unfathomably vast project!

Even under the nourishment of countless heavenly materials and limitless amounts of heaven and earth origin energy, this was still a process that required tens of thousands of years. But now, with the ancient dragon spirit fusing its essence into the black dragon egg, this greatly reduced the time it needed to incubate. At the same time, the life essence, talent, and supernatural powers that entered the dragon egg accelerated its growth. Once it hatched, it would definitely be far more powerful than Xiao Moxian’s hungry Big Yellow, a Taotie God Beast!

Time slowly passed, a breath at a time. Slowly, over the surface of the black dragon egg, a dazzling and mystical line appeared.

Then another strange and shimmering line appeared.

As these radiant lines slowly appeared, the pitch black dragon egg became crystalline and translucent.

Lin Ming could even faintly hear a small whisper from within the dragon egg, as slight and imperceptible as dust falling in the wind.

After that, vaguely, the outline of a little baby dragon appeared from within the glowing dragon egg, flitting in and out of sight, indistinct and hidden…

It was slowly absorbing the power of the dragon spirit like drinking from a trickling stream. Lin Ming could see at first glance that absorbing the ancient dragon spirit wasn’t something that could be accomplished in a single day. Rather, it would take a long time as the process slowly occurred.

This was just like a small little bug eating a massive cake.

After finishing eating and then also absorbing other heavenly materials, just what boundary would this little baby black dragon reach?

The life fluctuations of the black dragon egg began to die down as it changed back to its previous appearance. The only differences were the traces of life marked on the outside of the dragon egg; they still emitted a luminescent light.

This was clearly showing the pulse of life within.

“It seems it will need a much longer time before it can hatch…” Lin Ming gazed at the black dragon egg, satisfied with what he saw. He would allow that little life to slowly digest the power of the dragon spirit.

At this time he had to do his best not to disturb the black dragon egg; he also understood the common saying that one shouldn’t try to run before they could walk. This needed to be a progressive, gradual process.

Just as he put the black dragon egg and jade dragon horn in his spatial ring, there was the thumping of a knock on his door.

Who had come at this time?

Lin Ming wasn’t happy to be disturbed while he was drawing up divine runic symbols. Xiao Moxian frowned and opened the door. They could see two old men with strange smiles on their faces standing at the entrance. Beside them were two young divine runic masters; they were clearly apprentices.

“Who are you?” Xiao Moxian swept her eyes over them, her vision catching on their divine runic badges. Their divine runic badges were not in the style of Divine Rune City so they clearly weren’t divine runic masters of the Divine Runic Masters Guild.

“We felt a chaotic energy just now. It seems that…” The eyes of one of the old divine runic masters looked over Xiao Moxian and swept through the divine runic room. As he saw the messy and chaotic scene he knew that a considerably large explosion had occurred just now. Even the array discs might have been damaged.

“It seems that there was an explosion… is Sir Lin safe?” A tall and thin old man asked. Although he had a smile, one could clearly hear the anxiety and worry in his voice.

The other old man was short and fat. Although he didn’t speak, his distraught expression spoke more than enough for him.

These two people had clearly felt the strange fluctuations of energy in the air.

“You are not from the Divine Runic Masters Guild…” Xiao Moxian frowned. Just where did these two old fellows come from? Why were they here?

“I am Zhao Chang, a divine runic master from the Minor Violet Holy Lands. Before, hadn’t Sir Lin said that he would hand over the completed Heretical God Symbols every few months? Thus, Empyrean Minor Violet sent us here to be responsible for this matter and to lend any aid that we can. If there is any matter that you need help with, please feel free to look for us, we will do our best to help you in any manner we can.”

Divine runic master Zhao spoke with a close and friendly tone. As he spoke, he continued to sweep his sense across the divine runic room, trying to get a grasp of Lin Ming’s progress on the Heretical God Symbols.

Xiao Moxian was stunned for a moment before she recovered. It seemed that Empyrean Minor Violent didn’t trust them too much and had sent several supervisors to keep an eye on them!

This caused Xiao Moxian to feel extremely uncomfortable. Her eyebrows twitched and she nearly slammed the door shut. But at this time, Lin Ming stopped her and smiled at the two old divine runic masters as he said, “Please rest assured, I will turn in divine runic symbols every three months, on time. As for this divine runic room, the sound insulating array formation is quite good and it’s nearly impossible for the fluctuations of energy from an explosion to escape. Two sirs, perhaps you were living in the room next door?”

Lin Ming smiled, chuckling a little. He didn’t mind that Empyrean Minor Violet had sent these supervisors to watch over him. To be honest, if he were in Empyrean Minor Violet’s position, he would absolutely send people to keep a close eye on matters. After all, this was a total of 5 billion points added with a 2 billion point dragon saliva grass, and all of this was traded for a promissory note. How could Empyrean Minor Violet not be anxious about this?

Lin Ming’s words left the two old divine runic masters blushing red with embarrassment. Indeed, they were assigned to monitor him at all hours, every day. It wasn’t much different from having moved a bench right outside the door of his room.

However, they couldn’t disturb Lin Ming as he was drawing up divine runic symbols so they didn’t have the chance to enter his room. It was only with this explosion that they took this opportunity to see the progress of his work.

Chapter 1652 – Task Complete

“This… why is that little girl so angry?”

The two old men were somewhat depressed. It was rare for a junior to treat them like this. After such a cold reception they were really at a loss for words.

“She is complaining that we are staying out here and disturbing her.” The other old man bitterly smiled.

To squat outside one’s door every day, it wasn’t strange to arouse someone’s disgust and annoyance. If it weren’t for this being Empyrean Minor Violet’s personal command, they wouldn’t be willing to squat at the door like some beggars.

“Lin Ming seems to have pushed himself too far. I have no idea if it’s really like that little girl said and he’s investing a massive amount of energy in the improved Heavenly Fire Symbols. At the time, Empyrean Lionheart hadn’t stipulated any deadline so as long as Lin Ming isn’t foolish he shouldn’t take on too great a burden.”

“Lin Ming’s not an idiot. Empyrean Lionheart isn’t facing a war anytime soon so he has no urgent need for the divine runic symbols. To him, it shouldn’t matter if it’s three years or five years. My gut feeling tells me that there was a problem in the drawing process. That Heretical God Symbol alone has 3000 some tiny runes, enough to even cause a sixth grade divine runic master to feel fear at heart, so how could it be easy to draw up? Perhaps the previous explosion was because there was a problem with the runic structure. We can only hope that Lin Ming managed to solve the problem…”

As these two old men continued deliberating, they passed these mere 10 divine runic symbols to a messenger from the Minor Violet Holy Lands who passed through numerous channels to deliver them to Empyrean Minor Violet.

In three months, Empyrean Minor Violet had only received 10 divine runic symbols. This small amount caused her to slightly frown. However, it was only slightly frowning. She didn’t say much, only commanding that all the divine runic symbols be delivered to her every three months.

Lin Ming delivering 10 Heretical God Symbols in three months wasn’t a secret at all. In addition, with the numerous people who were paying attention to Lin Ming, this news soon spread.

If he spent three months to complete 10 divine runic symbols, how could he possibly complete 500 in three years?

These people couldn’t help but gossip quietly amongst themselves. Although Lin Min Ming was young, no one dared to underestimate him. At the Divine Rune City Auction he had obtained 10 billion points in just half a month. Whether it was in terms of will or mentality, he was absolutely top notch!

Since he had dared to make a promise that he would be able to fulfill the promissory note of 500 Heretical God Symbols in three years, he had to have some assurance in doing so. After all, if his confident promise at the time was just an act, the future price he would have to pay would be dreadful.

Thus, everyone felt that Lin Ming’s slow speed in drawing up Heretical God Symbols was likely because some accident had occurred.

If he could solve this problem then he might be able to increase his speed. But if he didn’t manage to do so then he would truly lose everything!

This news left many divine runic masters that were on good terms with Lin Ming worried for him. For instance, Old Xue and Old Su were both fretting over his problems.

But there were also many others taking this chance to gloat. They wanted Lin Ming to fail. The materials had been paid for using Lin Ming’s money, and if he were forced to pay back the 5 billion points and dragon saliva grass he earned, that would truly be tragic.

Old Su and Old Xue discussed the situation with each other. They figured that Lin Ming should have encountered some problem in the first three months that he wasn’t able to solve for the time being. After the first three months, his speed should have increased some more.

But, they never imagined that after six months of time, Lin Ming would only hand over three more Heretical God Symbols!

This left many people speechless. How come he would turn in less each time!?

Good heavens! Old Xue and Old Su were no longer able to sit still. This was not just Lin Ming’s problem but something that involved the honor and reputation of the Divine Runic Masters Guild. The three kinds of divine runic symbols that Lin Ming invented were his brand and also the brand of the Divine Runic Masters Guild.

Slowly, the divine runic masters that had gathered at the Divine Runic Masters Guild from all over the Asura Road felt the situation becoming more interesting.

This youth had spent half a month to gather 10 billion points and had made a great show of things. If he wasn’t able to fulfill his promises and lost everything, then the miracle of that time would turn into nothing but a joke.

After nine months, Lin Ming only delivered slightly more Heretical God Symbols – five of them!

When placed against the total requirement of 500, this was nothing but a drop of water in a bucket.

Time passed a day at a time. Lin Ming was deep in seclusion and didn’t leave. The divine runic symbols he completed were handed over to Xiao Moxian for processing. Lin Ming focused all of his heart and mind on drawing up the divine runic symbols and declined all disturbances.

No one knew that at this time, Lin Ming had already been able to draw up three improved Heavenly Fire Symbols in one day and his success rate had risen to 100%!

With his current soul force and control of the Asura Laws, Lin Ming believed that if he were to stop drawing up the Heavenly Fire Symbols now and immediately start on the Heretical God Symbols, his success rate would be above 95%.

During these nine months, Lin Ming had already completed 390 improved Heavenly Fire Symbols and had just a bit more than 100 left to do. He could complete that in a little more than a month.

Then, ten months passed.

Halfway through the 11th month, Lin Ming completed all improved Heavenly Fire Symbols. All 500 Heavenly Fire Symbols had been perfectly drawn up!

Following that, Lin Ming’s divine runic arts had risen to another level. With this experience at his back, he started his work on the Heretical God Symbols.

With the warm up of the Heavenly Fire Symbols, it had become far easier for Lin Ming to draw up the Heretical God Symbols.

From one a day at the start, after becoming more familiar with the process, he began to draw up three every two days.

In over 40 days, Lin Ming drew up more than 50 Heretical God Symbols.

With this, the 12th month had passed. An entire year had quietly slipped by.

The end of the 12th month also signaled the receiving of the completed divine runic symbols.

As many people thought that Lin Ming would complete Heretical God Symbols in the single digits, when Xiao Moxian took out the jade box and opened it, she actually revealed a thick stack of Heretical God Symbols within.

Zhao Chang was stunned as he saw this.

He quickly counted the Heretical God Symbols and noticed there were 52 of them. With a brief probing of his soul force, he could see that all of these were completed Heretical God Symbols!

How come Lin Ming had handed over three and five divine runic symbols, but now there were suddenly 52 divine runic symbols? Did Lin Ming finally manage to draw around one every two days?

As this news spread throughout the Divine Runic Masters Guild, Old Su and Old Xue were overjoyed. There was finally some good news about Lin Ming!

However, a speed of drawing up one every two days still wasn’t enough to complete 500 of them in the time left. They could only hope that Lin Ming would increase his speed yet again in the next two years. Only like this would he have hopes of completing the 500.

Old Xue held onto this hope. But, he never imagined that after another three months, Lin Ming would give them all another heaven-shaking surprise!

It had to be known that when Lin Ming drew up the 52 divine runic symbols, he had only used a month and a half to do so. The first half of the three months had been spent on drawing up improved Heavenly Fire Symbols.

However, during the next three months, Lin Ming was spending the entire timespan to do so. He invested all of his concentration in it, only thinking of drawing up Heretical God Symbols.

Thus, during these three months, Lin Ming drew up a total of 135 Heretical God Symbols! He had drawn up two divine runic symbols every three days, no more, no less.

When Xiao Moxian handed over these divine runic symbols, Zhao Chang was left dumbfounded for a long time.

“How come there are so many?”

To hand over 135 all of a sudden, this was over twice the total amount of all the Heretical God Symbols he had handed in before!

“Is it not good to turn in too many?” Xiao Moxian asked. She urged Zhao Chang to hurry up and inspect the goods.

Zhao Chang shook his head and regained his composure. He swept his sense through the Heretical God Symbols and saw that there was no problem with any of them.

How had Lin Ming drawn all of these?

As Zhao Chang was lost in thought, he dazedly passed the 135 Heretical God Symbols to headquarters. As this news spread, Old Su and Old Xue were ecstatic.

As for many other divine runic masters, they were left perplexed.

Lin Ming had handed over Heretical God Symbols a total of five times.

The first time he turned in 10, the second time three, the third time five, and the fourth time was the most normal at 52.

But the fifth time, he actually handed in a ridiculous number of 135.

Could Lin Ming have been deliberately holding back some divine runic symbols the first year? And then for some reason he decided to hand them over now?

Many people had this thought. This was also the most reasonable explanation.

Otherwise, to complete 135 Heretical God Symbols in three months, that was simply unbelievable.

Up until now, Lin Ming had completed 205 Heretical God Symbols in 15 months. If this number was averaged out, that would be around 13-14 completed every month. This was a perfectly acceptable number.

Even so, at this speed, it would still be extremely tight if Lin Ming wanted to complete 500 divine runic symbols in three years. It felt as if he were gasping for time.

Whether or not he could complete the task would depend on how many divine runic symbols Lin Ming would turn in the next time.

Time quickly passed. Soon, six months passed during the second year.

It was time again for the delivery of divine runic symbols.

And this time, when Xiao Moxian took out the divine runic symbols, Zhao Chang’s chin nearly hit the ground.

She took out 145 at once!

With this, Lin Ming had now delivered 350 Heretical God Symbols. He was only 150 away from 500!

Everyone didn’t even have the time to digest this news or to figure out how Lin Ming had managed to draw up 145 Heretical God Symbols in three months. And following this, after the ninth month of the second year passed, Lin Ming directly left seclusion and handed over the remaining 150 divine runic symbols!

With this, Lin Ming completely fulfilled his promissory note to Empyrean Minor Violet!

As Lin Ming stepped out of his room, his appearance was a bit haggard and exhausted. As Zhao Chang and the other old man saw him, they were both left panic-stricken.

In their eyes, this young man in front of them was no different from a monstrous freak.

The original deadline was three years, but Lin Ming had used a year and nine months to complete it.

As for the difficulty of the Heretical God Symbol, the two old fellows had a deep understanding of it. There were over 3000 tiny runes and innumerable connections and combinations between them; just looking at the possibilities gave one a headache. Even for a sixth grade divine runic master, their soul force might not be enough to complete the task. Moreover, the more and more soul force he used up, the higher the chances of failure became!

How had Lin Ming accomplished all of this?

As this news spread out, the divine runic masters in Divine Rune City were all left startled. In particular, those hoping for Lin Ming to fail and lose all the money he had used to purchase materials were left absolutely flummoxed.

However, they still had a great question in their minds. Lin Ming was clearly able to complete 500 Heretical God Symbols in a year and nine months, so in the first nine months, why had he only turned in such a small number of divine runic symbols every time?

Chapter 1656 – Legend of the Spiritas

Empyrean Divine Mist seemed to fall into a long period of recollection. He closed his eyes, deep in thought. After a long time he finally began to slowly say, “I cannot be sure, but if I’m not wrong, this should be the Stone of Eternal Life recorded within the Spiritas Holy Scripture. With this stone, your soul will become eternal and your life everlasting…”

“Spiritas Holy Scripture…” Lin Ming mumbled. He thought back to what he knew and faintly remembered that there was such a book.

Lin Ming had swallowed the memories of dark and perverse divine runic masters like Torchriver. And, these divine runic masters were almost nearly all spiritas. Some of them had even read duplicate copies of the Spiritas Holy Scripture and knew some of the records within. But because these memories weren’t too important to Lin Ming’s training of the divine runic arts, he hadn’t studied them, but he hadn’t tossed them away either.

Now that Empyrean Divine Mist spoke of this term, Lin Ming carefully went back through the memories he had of the Spiritas Holy Scripture.

The Spiritas Holy Scripture could be called the most mysterious and enigmatic sacred text of the spiritas. It was impossible to know just which supreme elder had written the Spiritas Holy Scripture, but there were many things recorded within it. Some things were secrets of the universe, some were notes on the Laws, and some were even prophecies of the future. All of this text had been slowly verified over time!

It was no longer known where the original Spiritas Holy Scripture was. According to some rumors, it was within the hands of a spiritas True Divinity level great emperor. As for the Spiritas Holy Scripture that spread out to the entire spiritas race, that was nothing but a duplicate.

Even though it was a duplicate, this text wasn’t something that everyone could read, simply because there were far too many secrets within that were related to the spiritas. It was a strange and mystical existence, and ordinary spiritas martial artists didn’t even know of its existence.

Those on the level of Torchriver were only able to come into faint contact with it.

The duplicate copies of the Spiritas Holy Scripture could only reproduce the text of the universe’s secrets as well as some archaic prophecies. As for the recordings of the Laws and other such things, those were impossible to copy.

Thus, there was simply no comparing the value of the duplicate of the Spiritas Holy Scripture to the original.

In Torchriver’s mind, if someone was able to obtain the original copy of the Spiritas Holy Scripture and also had extraordinary talent, they could cultivate the Laws within the text. They could rely on the information within the Spiritas Holy Scripture to avoid disasters and take control of the world, inevitably becoming someone that ruled the era!

At this time, Empyrean Divine Mist was still staring at the Magic Cube.

Whether it was the dark gray cube shape, the patterns on it, or even the aura that aroused the awe and reverence from the innermost soul of any spiritas martial artist, it was completely similar to the Stone of Eternal Life recorded within the Spiritas Holy Scripture.

This oppression of the soul ignored all boundaries and all cultivations. As long as one stood before this mysterious black cube, one would feel as if this cube was the master of all souls and be unable to resist it!

All of this proved that Empyrean Divine Mist’s guess must be correct!

“I never thought… that before I died… I would have the chance to see a divine tool like this. In my prime I could shake the earth and change the winds, but now in my old age I’m in such a sad state. Even so, in the depths of my despair, as my life approaches its end, I was able to catch a glimpse of the Stone of Eternal Life…” Empyrean Divine Mist sighed as he spoke to here. As he looked at Lin Ming, his eyes were shining with a brilliant light.

“Junior… it seems you have already had the Stone of Eternal Life for some time. Perhaps even your current achievements are greatly related to it. You should be well aware of how precious the Stone of Eternal Life is and yet you still took it out in front of me. Aren’t you afraid that I’m not actually as weak as I appear to be, and that I might try to wrest the stone from your hands?”

Empyrean Divine Mist suddenly said with a deep meaning in his tone. Even Xiao Moxian felt her heart shrink upon hearing this.

After all, an Empyrean level powerhouse placed far too much pressure on someone. Even an Empyrean on the edge of death was able to release a terrifying pressure, just like an injured tiger facing a mortal.

Lin Ming quietly said, “Senior Divine Mist truly likes to jest. Junior can feel that you really are near the end of your rope, and you simply have no reason to disguise yourself from us and pretend to be so weakened. If you don’t possess the power to kill me, then there is no meaning in disguising yourself. On the other hand, if you had the ability to kill me, you simply wouldn’t need to disguise yourself anyways. You would have simply just killed me. In fact, there is no need for you to have waited until now. When I first entered Tragic Death Valley and broke through the secrets of the God Beast Tomb array formation you could have finished me then. At that time I was even weaker and you were even stronger…”

As Lin Ming explained his analysis his voice was calm and placid, but he still retained full vigilance.

The truth was that even Empyrean Divine Mist found it hard to correctly judge Lin Ming’s strength. Although Lin Ming still wasn’t a match for a Great World King, he could use the special environment in Tragic Death Valley, his understandings of the array formations here, his divine runic symbols, and even his comprehension of the Asura Heavenly Dao to struggle with a Great World King and seek a path of survival.

An Empyrean sounded like a terrifying existence. But when compared to a Great World King, they were in fact only a large boundary higher.

How could a completely exhausted Empyrean Divine Mist on the verge of death be superior to a Great World King?

And most importantly, Lin Ming had a trump card in the Magic Cube. Against Empyrean Divine Mist whose mortal body was thoroughly ruined and had nothing left but his soul form, the Magic Cube was his ultimate nemesis.

It was with this guarantee that Lin Ming was willing to take out the Magic Cube. Otherwise, Lin Ming would have protected the Magic Cube until the end. The Magic Cube was his greatest secret. Besides Xiao Moxian and Mo Eversnow, no one else knew about it.

Empyrean Divine Mist gazed deeply at Lin Ming. Then he said, “You’re quite brave… in order to save me, you were actually willing to take such a risk. I will remember this favor…”

Empyrean Divine Mist slowly said. He was originally a top extreme figure and he rarely made such solemn promises. “I never imagined you would possess the Stone of Eternal Life. Perhaps… perhaps there really is a chance for me to find a turning point in my life… if I can recover, then I will help you with all my heart and soul!”

As Empyrean Divine Mist finished speaking these words he seemed to have used up all of his strength. His soul fluctuations became chaotic once more. He was simply far too weak. Even with the help of the Soul Recovery Pill, he couldn’t speak so many words.

“Senior, what does the Spiritas Holy Scripture have recorded about the Stone of Eternal Life?” Lin Ming asked. Torchriver’s memories about the contents of the Spiritas Holy Scripture were simply far too lacking.

Empyrean Divine Mist was deep in thought for some time, as if he were gathering his energy to speak. Then, in a slow and aged tone, he said, “The Spiritas Holy Scripture records that if one obtains the Magic Cube and then cultivates the Spiritas Heavenly Dao within the Spiritas Holy Scripture to the highest boundary, and then satisfies a few more conditions, there is a chance that they can control the strongest force in the world and live on in perpetuity. That is, an unaging immortality...”

“Unaging immortality…” Lin Ming whispered. Immortality was the dream of all living beings in the universe, the ultimate goal that martial artists pursued.

In a sense, the reason martial artists risked all sorts of life-threatening dangers and unendingly chased after higher realms of cultivation was because of the satisfactions brought from increased strength, but also because they earnestly desired life!

The higher one’s cultivation, the longer they lived. To martial artists, this was a fatal temptation.

Even Lin Ming desired immortality.

To be earth-shaking, to rule over the heavens and earth, to dominate all living beings, to live infinitely brilliantly, to feast upon all the pleasures of existence, just who was willing to then be finally defeated by the tides of time, falling to entropy, slowly weakening and decaying until they turned to dust?

The end of a hero’s road, the withering of beauty – when one imagined the eternal deep sleep and loneliness that came after death, every person would inevitably feel an indescribable fear.

In this world, the strongest person Lin Ming knew of was the Asura Road Master. Lin Ming wondered whether or not the Asura Road Master had broken through the barrier of immortality. Was he now dead, or was he existing in some hidden corner of the world?

Whether or not the Asura Road Master managed to achieve immortality, trying to break through the boundary of everlasting life was as difficult as ascending to heaven. But now, Empyrean Divine Mist actually stated that the Spiritas Holy Scripture recorded a cultivation method pertaining to immortality; how could Lin Ming not be startled!

He once again asked Empyrean Divine Mist about information related to the contents of the Spiritas Holy Scripture. However, the Spiritas Holy Scripture that Empyrean Divine Mist saw was only a copy; the original had been long lost.

Thus, even Empyrean Divine Mist didn’t know what one needed to achieve the realm of immortality. Besides possessing the Magic Cube and cultivating the Spiritas Heavenly Dao within the Spiritas Holy Scripture, just what other conditions were required?

……….

After his conversation with Empyrean Divine Mist ended, Lin Ming used three days to allow Empyrean Divine Mist to absorb all the essence energy within the Soul Recovery Pill. Then, Lin Ming shattered the decaying soul crystal and pulled Empyrean Divine Mist’s soul from his ruined body, receiving him into the Magic Cube and sealing him away!

With this, Empyrean Divine Mist’s soul fell into a completely dormant state, frozen within the Magic Cube.

After finishing all of this, Lin Ming didn’t yet leave Tragic Death Valley. Instead, he stayed there for some time.

He had many matters he needed to attend to.

One couldn’t instantly reach the late Divine Lord realm; time and patience were required. Lin Ming needed time to consolidate his cultivation and lay the foundation for his next breakthrough.

At the same time, Lin Ming needed to hone his skills in divine runic arts and alchemy in order to prepare for refining the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill. Before the final trial began, he had to break through into the second Dao Palace!

All of this required time.

As for Tragic Death Valley, it was the only place Lin Ming had ever seen which twisted the flow of time but didn’t distort the Laws. Cultivating here was the best place to do so.

Then, Lin Ming took out Primordius Heavenly Palace and flew in with Xiao Moxian, entering a long period of seclusion.

One month outside, one spring and fall in the valley. Training passed without sense of time. Year by year quietly passed.

Before coming here, Lin Ming had spent his contribution points on purchasing a seemingly endless pile of materials from the Divine Runic Masters Guild. And, these materials were all used by Lin Ming on the divine runic arts and alchemy.

If Lin Ming was going to enter the final trial, he needed to draw up some strong divine runic symbols to prepare for emergencies.

Chapter 1658B – Yin Yang Despair Valley

From a high and commanding position, Lin Ming could see that around a thousand miles away, there were several giants as high as mountains. They had lit up a raging fire that seemed to burn the heavens as they roasted a mountain-sized beast upon it.

“Brother Lin, haha! We’ve finally found the coiling ridge giants. This Yin Yang Despair Valley, Forsaken Valley Tomb is the place that they protect. We should be able to find it soon.” Xiao Moxian said, her smile reaching from ear to ear.

“Yes, but dealing with these wild giants will be troublesome…” Since Yin Yang Despair Valley was a totem-like existence that the coiling ridge giants protected, they naturally wouldn’t let outsiders enter it.

Moreover, these coiling ridge giants were one of the terrifying species that lived in the depths of the Great Desolate. Although they couldn’t be compared with God Beasts, a grown coiling ridge giant could still resist an ordinary World King. Lin Ming could deal with two or three of them, but it would be difficult if more appeared.

“We only need to follow them. According to Heaven’s Secret, the coiling ridge giants only have a small population and are almost always keeping guard over their nearby danger zones. I think the reason they came out this time is to hunt and after their hunt is complete they will return.” Lin Ming confidently said as his eyes passed over the mountain-sized beast that was being roasted.

Xiao Moxian nodded. They focused their attention, patiently waiting.

The three large coiling ridge giants ate for a full two hours, finally finishing eating up that massive vicious beast that hung over the barbecue fire.

Then, the coiling ridge giants burped out loud. They each carried a giant beast over their shoulders and started walking deeper into the Great Desolate.

Bang – Bang – Bang –

Each footstep rang through the air like the beat of a giant drum, shaking the air.

The land surged and shook.

Lin Ming put away Primordius Heavenly Palace, hid his aura, and carefully followed behind the three coiling ridge giants with Xiao Moxian close behind him.

The coiling ridge giants moved fast. Each step left behind a giant footprint in the earth.

After following for an incense stick of time, a ghostly black mountain peak began to appear in the distance.

A single step from a coiling ridge giant could cross over an entire mountain valley. Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian had to doggedly chase after them lest they be left behind.

Suddenly, Lin Ming detected something in the air. His surroundings had become much more humid, to the point where it seemed as if the air would begin leaking water.

“What thick air moisture.” Xiao Moxian commented, surprised.

The two of them flew 10,000 feet high to look further into the distance. As they saw what was several hundred miles away, both of them were stunned.

High in the sky was a titanic flood of water, endlessly falling. It stretched upwards to the heavens and even with Lin Ming’s current strength he couldn’t estimate just where it started. The massive deluge of water fell down like an infinite waterfall, with enough force to shatter the world.

Beneath this flood of water was a profound and unfathomable darkness.

Water vapor sprayed all around, turning the entire surrounding area into a wet climate zone.

It was unknown how deep that black abyss was, but even that seemingly inexhaustible flood of water couldn’t fill it. It was hard to imagine just how large the world beneath was.

“This is ‘where the sea falls from the heavens and into the endless deep’! But, where is this water coming from? Why would it be falling down from the skies?” Xiao Moxian muttered to herself, completely bewildered. This strange and amazing creation was simply incredible.

The three coiling ridge giants walked towards the massive sea of water.

Afterwards, with great steps, they walked into the endless waves. Their massive figures were drowned out by the waters.

“These great waters are falling from a mountain peak that is as high as the heavens!” Lin Ming’s soul force was keen and he could faintly feel that behind this endless deluge of water was a ghostly black mountain peak, one so high he couldn’t make out the top.

This massive mountain peak was so high that even several planets stacked together would seem tiny in front of it. It wasn’t something that mortal minds could comprehend.

And they especially couldn’t imagine where the source of this water came from.

“Follow them closely!” Lin Ming called out to Xiao Moxian. In order to prevent any mishaps, the two of them once again took out Primordius Heavenly Palace and began riding in it.

But this time, Lin Ming had shrunk Primordius Heavenly Palace much more than before.

Primordius Heavenly Palace itself contained profound time-space array formations within it and it could shrink or grow to whatever size was needed. Now, Lin Ming turned it into the size of a rock. As he followed behind the three giants, Primordius Heavenly Palace seemed quite common.

Woosh –

Primordius Heavenly Palace emitted a faint aura of grandmist energy as it broke into the rush of water with the three coiling ridge giants.

As soon as they entered the great waters, the endless waves, undercurrents, and massive strengths contained within began to unceasingly tear at Primordius Heavenly Palace.

However, how could an Empyrean spirit treasure be so easily destroyed? A vast strength surged out from the Heavenly Palace, immediately stopping these destructive waves.

Slowly, as Primordius Heavenly Palace cut its way forwards, the force within the waters became weaker.

Faintly, they could make out something a mile away.

A mile in front of them was actually a giant cave.

At the edge of the cave were dozens of coiling ridge giants kneeling on the ground, seeming as if they were worshipping something inside.

One of the coiling ridge giants appeared to be an old man. His body was ash gray and he lay on the ground, motionless.

Nearby was another old coiling ridge giant wearing a strange golden crown. This giant was muttering sacred words and constantly spitting out runes. As these runes appeared, they swallowed the endless spiritual power in the surrounding space and then turned solid gold as they fell onto the skin of the seemingly dead old coiling ridge giant.

Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian could both feel the great strength of the old coiling ridge giant that seemed to be offering a sacrifice.

Every rune that this giant read out would stir up phantoms in the void. These runes seemed to have been carved into the flesh and blood of the coiling ridge giant, just like the Laws that were carved into the flesh and blood of God Beasts. These types of existences were all favored children of the world!

With so many coiling ridge giants, Lin Ming naturally wouldn’t provoke them. This was already considered deep in the Great Desolate and there were countless horrifying and fantastical existences here. Even an Empyrean wouldn’t dare recklessly act as they wished.

For now, Lin Ming could only calmly observe what was happening. He couldn’t easily enter the cave.

Suddenly, that old giant that was praying shouted out loud. His voice was like a peal of thunder, and even though Lin Ming was hiding within Primordius Heavenly Palace, he still felt his ears shake.

A wave of grandmist energy surged out and only then was this powerful vibrating suppressed.

All of the coiling ridge giants stood up. Four of them were particularly tall and strong, their heads even disappearing into the shadows of the cave.

These four giants lifted up the dead old giant and brought him near the edge of the great waters. Then, they threw his corpse inside, seeming to be burying him this way.

But what was a coincidence was that this massive giant corpse actually started falling towards the area where Lin Ming was!

To Lin Ming, this coincidence was a tremendous misfortune!

The moment that the giant corpse struck the water, the grandmist energy that was being sent out by Primordius Heavenly Palace was also sensed by the worshipping giants.

A lightning sharp vision focused on Primordius Heavenly Palace.

The coiling ridge giants never imagined that there would be some foreign existence hiding in the waves of the water. Moreover, they could feel that this was a powerful entity!

They were angry – they roared!

The boundless soundwaves struck like endlessly crashing shockwaves as they hurtled at Primordius Heavenly Palace. Within these sound waves were also flashing golden runes.

Each rune contained the breath of the Great Dao, a powerful strength that seemed as if it could annihilate everything. This was the special talent of the coiling ridge giant race!

“This is bad!”

Lin Ming was panic-stricken. There were already far too many coiling ridge giants and above that, the old worshipping giant was incomparably formidable!

Luckily, Lin Ming had already achieved a mind state of one with Primordius Heavenly Palace. In this grave and critical moment, countless magic patterns appeared, combining with the surrounding grandmist energy to form layers of defensive barriers.

Rumble! Rumble! Rumble!

The layers of defensive barriers were crushed and torn apart by those strange golden runes. Finally, when the attack reached Primordius Heavenly Palace, it caused the entire palace to violently shake! After all, Lin Ming was weaker than a Great World King and he wasn’t able to reach the standards of an Empyrean managing Primordius Heavenly Palace. To persist against a barrage of attacks from these coiling ridge giants that weren’t much weaker than low level God Beasts was extremely difficult.

As the old giant was gathering the other coiling ridge giants to attack once more, Lin Ming controlled Primordius Heavenly Palace and dove deep into the endless black abyss along with the giant’s corpse.

The shrunken Primordius Heavenly Palace was sheltered by the corpse. The old giant was only able to roar out several times in vain, and in the end it could only watch blankly on, not daring to do anything else.

It was unknown how long they fell downwards into the abyss. It seemed as if ten days and ten nights had passed.

Lin Ming only felt that Primordius Heavenly Palace was pushed downwards by some massive impact force. At first all he could see around him was the endlessly falling water, but later his surroundings were only the endless dark.

It was like halfway down, the massive deluge of water had rushed into some other channel.

After another long period of time, there was a massive explosive sound. The entirety of Primordius Heavenly Palace finally struck the ground, causing a giant detonation.

Fortunately, Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian were already prepared. Their bodies were surrounded by layers of grandmist energy and the power of god runes.

Even with all these preparations, their defenses were still crushed beneath the powerful impact force. Lin Ming felt as if all the bones in his body were shaken up.

“Eh? What is this?”

As Lin Ming crawled out from Primordius Heavenly Palace, he could feel an exceptionally terrifying aura rush towards him from all directions.

There was the yin death energy, tyrannical fire energy, arctic ice energy, and even a vast and massive power of water…

He had actually arrived in an incomprehensibly large and mystifying valley.

One side of the valley burned with an inferno of raging flames. Giant skeletons lay within these fires.

Another side was covered with 10,000 year ice. Colossal icicles rose into the air, each one encapsulating a corpse – the corpse of a coiling ridge giant.

All throughout other areas of the valley, there were scattered corpses of coiling ridge giants, their bodies still weakly shimmering with golden runes.

And beneath their feet, they could clearly feel the turbulent waters rushing about.

“This is… Ying Yang Despair Valley, Forsaken Mortal Tomb?” Xiao Moxian’s eyes popped open as she took in the scenes around her, her mind incomparably shocked.

“Be careful!” Lin Ming suddenly felt a strength sweep towards Xiao Moxian.

This strength rushed out from the flaming mountain peaks on one side of the valley. It hurtled towards Xiao Moxian as if it had a mind of its own.

After stepping into the late Divine Lord realm, Xiao Moxian’s strength was beyond ordinary. With Lin Ming’s warning, jet black flames began igniting all over her body.

The flames turned into a black fire phoenix that collided with those mountain flames.

“Mm?” Xiao Moxian originally thought she could annihilate those flames with one strike. However, she never imagined that after those flames struck her own pitch black nirvanic flames, they would be equally matched and dissipate together.

Lin Ming couldn’t help but feel some dread. Xiao Moxian’s strike right now was one that even a World King would have to spend some effort to deal with and yet it had only managed to put those flames out. If those flames had really struck Xiao Moxian, then she would have been injured.

“Big Brother Lin, this is hellfire!” Xiao Moxian was a specialist of fire. She was able to sense the strangeness of those flames just now.

This sort of flame was naturally bred by the energy of the heavens and earth and signaled the presence of a Fire Elemental. If this were several dozen years ago, this sort of fire would have been greatly beneficial to Lin Ming!

But now, this hellfire wasn’t too useful to him. Still, its presence proved that Yin Yang Despair Valley was overflowing with energy. This meant that it would be greatly advantageous to Lin Ming for refining the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill!

Lin Ming closed his eyes and cast out his sense. In this mystic realm he could feel a powerful atmosphere of Laws – this was the Asura Heavenly Dao!

Chapter 1659 – Void Furnace

The Asura Heavenly Dao was spread throughout the entire Asura Road; this was the same in every single mystic realm.

After all, the Asura Road was created by the Asura Road Master. Although it was unknown how Yin Yang Despair Valley was formed, it should still be linked to the Asura Road Master.

“Let’s go…”

Lin Ming drew Xiao Moxian close and began moving forwards with her.

Lin Ming could clearly feel fluctuations from the wild space distortions all around.

It was obvious that the space here wasn’t stable.

According to the information he obtained from Heaven’s Secret Pavilion, the location of Yin Yang Despair Valley would constantly change within the Great Desolate, and the price to find out this information was considerably high. It seemed that this information wasn’t false at all…

However, this sort of danger zone was especially advantageous in helping Lin Ming refine the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill.

Of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, every Dao Palace represented a different true meaning of the universe, a different mystery.

The Ravenous Wolf Star corresponded with the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace. It was strange and cryptic, and of the nine Dao Palaces it could be said to represent the most elusive and nimble true meaning.

Heavenly Retribution – this referred to the power of the world. After a martial artist opened the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace they could rely on it to commune with the heavens and earth, integrating the power of the world into their mortal body and obtaining a terrifying strength, one that could annihilate all their enemies!

Opening the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace required tremendous momentum from the world itself. Only a suitable danger zone could provide them with the chance to succeed.

Lin Ming wasn’t in a hurry. He slowly scattered his sense outwards to find a place in Yin Yang Despair Valley that had a rich world strength so he could refine the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill there.

After finishing his plans, Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian walked together towards their destination.

Along the way there were many dangerous areas filled with space-time fissures. In addition, there were the dreadful surging flows of energy within the mystic realm. These turbulent flows of energy were similar to the hellfire that had rushed Xiao Moxian.

However, these flows of raging energy all followed the Asura Heavenly Dao. With this, it wasn’t difficult for Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian to avoid them.

They carefully arrived at the place that was rich with energy.

If the energy flows within Yin Yang Despair Valley were compared to a storm, then this place would be the eye of the storm. Although all sorts of world energies flooded the surrounding space, this place was actually extremely calm and most suited for refining a pill.

But just in case, Lin Ming still laid down protective array formations to prepare for all contingencies.

After finishing this, Lin Ming put forth a divine runic table and a variety of rare and precious materials. After laboring over the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill for so many years he was finally going to start refining it. Lin Ming was certainly thrilled by this prospect, but his movements were still orderly and calm, not hurried at all.

These were the habits that Lin Ming had picked up over the years by drawing the improved Heavenly Fire Symbols and Heretical God Symbols.

He needed to perfectly organize every detail in this process. Only this perfection would allow him to impact the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace.

His fingers cut a line through the void, drawing a wisp of heavenly tribulation fire towards it. He drew a curved path in the air.

Lin Ming’s hands seemed to fly. One at a time, strange energy patterns began to appear, condensing into all sorts of tiny runes.

Xiao Moxian stood on the side blinking, puzzled by this. “Big Brother Lin, aren’t you going to refine the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill? How come you are suddenly drawing up a divine runic symbol?”

“I have to refine the improved medicinal runic symbol first.”

Lin Ming lightly said. During the years in Tragic Death Valley he had used a full year to thoroughly research an appropriate medicinal runic symbol. This medicinal runic symbol was chosen after being checked for a number of criteria and would be the best one possible for supporting the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill.

Without this medicinal runic symbol, the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill that Lin Ming refined would have much weaker effects.

As Lin Ming spoke, the speed of his movements hastened. The movements of his hands in the air began to leave behind afterimages, as quick as lightning.

In Tragic Death Valley, Lin Ming had long accustomed himself with this medicinal runic symbol and had drawn up many test copies. But, to allow the medicinal runic symbol’s medicinal efficacy to reach the highest possible limit and also match the properties of the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill, he needed to draw support from the world momentum here.

In those 15 years within Tragic Death Valley, Lin Ming had reached even higher heights in drawing up a medicinal runic symbol. Now, all of that accumulated practice would finally reveal itself.

In addition with the memories of the three divine runic masters he had absorbed, this tremendous background allowed him to come up with many useful and fresh new ideas.

Moreover, this environment and the faint Asura Heavenly Dao Laws here would help Lin Ming a great deal.

He silently drew runes of the Asura Heavenly Dao towards the tiny runes, constantly transforming the medicinal runic symbol, allowing it to become far more complex and powerful.

Finally, after three days and three nights passed, strange and mysterious patterns appeared in the void where they were drawn by Lin Ming’s finger into the tiny runes.

In the blink of an eye, a brilliantly marvelous reaction occurred. A shimmering light bloomed like a lotus flower and all of the runes began to gather together, forming a divine runic symbol that appeared like a snow-white flower petal.

This divine runic symbol emitted a strange fluctuation of energy. Lin Ming finally relaxed, at last able to take a breath of relief. Then he carefully grasped the divine runic symbol – the improved medicinal runic symbol was finally complete. Within this divine runic symbol were the Laws of the Asura Heavenly Dao that existed in the surrounding environment. They were much purer than the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws that Lin Ming had comprehended.

Then, Lin Ming sat down on the ground, entering a deep meditation just like a monk. The reason he came here was to borrow the world momentum of this danger zone to help refine the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill and attack the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace.

And the power of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws here could also be used by Lin Ming.

Lin Ming’s thoughts raced. He began to analyze Yin Yang Despair Valley in his mind, combining all of the various powers here, including even the strange space distortions.

However, there was one thing Lin Ming understood above all. Everything in the world of the Asura Road had to conform to the basics of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws.

It could be said that the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws were the true ruler of the world.

Lin Ming’s fingers continuously calculated. An unusual strength flowed out from his body, causing the surrounding waves of power to react and wash towards him.

Gradually, strands of flame… white clouds filled with ice… distorted space ripples… thick black death energy…

All of these strengths began to gather towards Lin Ming with him as the center.

In this situation, Lin Ming meditated for a day and a night. He adjusted his condition to its peak state, restoring all of the soul force he used to refine the medicinal runic symbol.

At this time, Lin Ming’s eyes flashed open and a brilliant light cut through his pupils like a bolt of lightning in the dark skies. Lin Ming’s finger slightly quivered, each quiver causing a tiny trace of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws to appear.

At his side, the Asura Heavenly Dao Law patterns were marking the space around him!

He took out the heaven devouring snake gallbladder, jade dragon horn, and other transcendent materials form his spatial ring.

These materials, beneath the galvanizing world momentum here, manifested phantoms of dragons and snakes that twined together in the skies.

Lin Ming used the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws as the furnace and quickened the world momentum within Yin Yang Despair Valley as the fire to refine to the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill.

The power of elusive and mystical Laws constantly fused with the threads of world strength that surrounded the area, beginning to form strange lines in the air.

Within the void, gradually and faintly, the outline of a giant furnace began to appear…

The furnace spun around, emitting waves of strange forces, seeming as if it were attracting all of the power in the surroundings into it.

Countless runes floated around the furnace like sands in the tide. The furnace sparkled with a magical luster.

Without any hesitation, Lin Ming threw the jade dragon horn, heaven devouring snake gallbladder, dragon saliva grass, primal jade quintessence, and the pile of other materials into the air, allowing the swallowing force of the furnace to pull them all in.

The heavenly tribulation flames within his body surged out from his dantian, turning into a giant flame dragon that dove into the void furnace.

At the same time, Xiao Moxian also summoned her jet black nirvanic flames and sent them hurtling towards the furnace. After coordinating with Lin Ming in alchemy for so many years, their thoughts had already become one.

The dragon formed from heavenly tribulation flames and the dark phoenix formed by nirvanic flames soared up together, emitting dreadful waves of flames.

The dense flames split into countless threads of flames that drilled towards the different rare and precious materials.

Fleeting gaze crystals, three-eyed silkworm silk, all of the various materials began to disintegrate within the raging inferno of flames…

Some medicinal materials with a spirituality began to whine with horror and fear. However, the heavenly tribulation flames and nirvanic flames had already fused together. They were both seventh level Concept flames and could even instantly burn down a mountain peak; the strength of these combined flames was beyond terrifying.

As Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian constantly sent their power of fire into the void furnace, more and more materials within it began to melt, sending out all sorts of enchanting fragrances.

By just smelling these medicinal fragrances once, one would feel as if they had taken a bath in the purest water in the world. Their entire body would feel cleansed and comfortable.

At this time, within the blazing flames, the snow white jade dragon horn began to turn deep red.

A dragon spirit suddenly howled and rushed out, hurtling itself towards the dark fire phoenix and fire dragon.

Although the incomplete dragon soul had long disappeared, the dragon spirit’s instincts were still able to sense a danger outside that threatened its existence.

With a rumbling strike, Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian felt their bodies shake.

After all, those two flames were released by them and were connected to their divine souls through a mysterious connection.

Although this dragon spirit was nothing but a mindless puppet, it was still a True Dragon. In the impact, the roiling nirvanic flames and heavenly tribulation flames dimmed down a great deal.

Rumble rumble rumble!

The dragon spirit was infuriated. It attacked everything around it with a barrage of attacks, wanting to escape the imprisonment of this furnace.

However, this void furnace was formed by Lin Ming using the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws that existed in Yin Yang Despair Valley as well as by combining it with all sorts of different strengths.

It was an incomparably mysterious phenomenon. Although the jade dragon spirit was forceful and its attacks caused the entire furnace to shake, it still wasn’t able to pass through.

Lin Ming furrowed his eyebrows; he had already expected this.

If he wanted to rely on his own strength to refine the many top grade materials here, it would require a massive amount of time and energy. Moreover, it would be profoundly difficult.

But in Yin Yang Despair Valley, it was a completely different situation.

He could rely on the Asura Laws to summon and borrow the momentum of the world and complete the refinement of the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill!

Chapter 1660 – Completing the Pill

Lin Ming’s mind blazed with numerous calculations. He thrust out a finger and drew it through the void furnace, immediately causing lines of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws to shine.

The skies above Yin Yang Despair Valley began to violently billow. A massive burst of death energy exploded in the skies and was dragged downwards like a black inverted mountain peak.

Bang!

The jade dragon spirit just happened to be raging in the air above the void furnace. But then, it was suddenly struck by the immense amounts of death energy.

All of it crashed into the jade dragon horn.

At this time, a cruel and brutal aura erupted forth from the heaven devouring snake gallbladder.

A 100 foot long snake manifested in the air, biting towards that death energy and even managing to bite in in half!

Then, the dragon spirit aura within the dragon saliva grass also awoke from its deep unconsciousness. Even the primal jade quintessence began to emit a misty earth brown color. These energies surged out in all directions as if they wanted to desperately crush apart the void furnace and blow it away.

Every impact caused a terrifying shockwave to roll outwards.

The void furnace was formed from countless threads of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws that had been bound together. But as these wild strengths surged within it, they caused the void furnace to constantly inflate like a balloon.

After the Asura Heavenly Dao Law lines absorbed all of these different strengths and continued to expand, they retained their shape without any sign that they would crack apart.

Lin Ming calmly smashed his palm into the ground.

Bang! A massive hole appeared in the ground and a flow of chaotic earth brown air streamed out.

As this brown energy flow streamed out, anything that it touched was invaded with the power of earth. This was actually the purest form of the power of earth – Earth Pith!

Earth Piths were similar to Fire Elementals and Thunder Sources – they were a marvelous strength bred from deep in the earth. Earth Piths contained the purest and thickest earth essence energy. They were normally hidden hundreds of millions or billions of miles in the ground, perhaps only existing in the deepest depths of magma pools. They were extremely hard to detect.

But because Lin Ming had a deep understanding of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws, he could rely on the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws to borrow every source of strength within Yin Yang Despair Valley.

As soon as he sensed the Earth Pith hiding deep in the ground below him, he had summoned it, guiding it to the surface.

His fingers drew ghostly lines in the void that corresponded with the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws, as if he were building a bridge.

The Earth Pith was slowly drawn upwards, slowly climbing this bridge and entering the void furnace.

In the midst of those several wildly raging spiritual strengths, the pure Earth Pith was like a black profound turtle, filled with great strength and stability, carrying with it an indomitable aura that mercilessly suppressed those strengths!

With a loud rumbling sound, the snake spirit from the heaven devouring snake gallbladder, the dragon spirit aura from the dragon saliva grass, and the spiritual strength from the primal jade quintessence were suddenly struck by this power that came from deep underground.

They were like sharp spears smashing into an indestructible shield.

The Earth Pith was bitten by the snake spirit and dragon spirit to no avail and even the spiritual strength began to wither away.

Slowly, the dragon spirit and snake spirit began to erode. The earth brown luster was even able to wear at at soul force. The two great spirit bodies were originally filled with vitality and shining with a radiant light, but now they had become dark gray, incomparably weak and bleak.

At this time, a mass of earth brown spiritual power shot up into the skies, crashing into the Earth Pith. The mass of spiritual power opened wide like a massive jaw and bit down on the Earth Pith.

Kacha! Kacha!

That spiritual power was actually eating up that terrifying Earth Pith as if it was a snack.

After 3-4 bites, the earth brown spiritual power rapidly expanded and began crashing around into the sides of the void furnace.

Lin Ming was startled. In order to refine the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill a tremendous amount of top grade materials were required, and now these materials had started a war.

This primal jade quintessence was a spiritual object that had lived in the center of a world for billions of years and was also an earth-attribute sacred spirit. Because of this, it was able to absorb the power of the Earth Pith. If the primal jade quintessence was allowed to expand as it pleased, then even if it wasn’t able to break through the imprisonment of the void furnace created by the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws, it would still make refining the pill incomparably hard.

Lin Ming began to murmur a mantra in his mind. Behind him, the phantom of a giant divine tree slowly appeared. As it flickered into existence, the power of thunder and fire heavenly tribulation exploded outwards! A dazzling light erupted like thousands of rising suns, all of them following the paths of the Heavenly Dao Laws. Without sentiment or pity, these beams of light stabbed into the key points of the primal jade quintessence’s spirit.

In this raging sea of thunder and flames, the recently inflated primal jade quintessence began to rapidly diminish in size.

Without hesitation, Lin Ming punched the void, tearing it apart.

The space here was unstable to begin with. With Lin Ming’s understanding of the Asura Heavenly Dao, smashing apart space wasn’t difficult at all.

A space storm was pulled out by him. The space storm cut a vacuum path in the air as it fired towards the primal jade quintessence within the void furnace.

Cha – cha –

The primal jade quintessence’s aura was cut apart like butter in the hot sun.

Death energy, spiritual energy, space storms, Earth Pith strength, Phoenix Blood Spear potential, jet back nirvanic flames…

All of the powers that could be summoned in Yin Yang Despair Valley were pulled into the middle of the void furnace by him.

Not only that, but Lin Ming’s hands flickered once more and the air began to shine with the mysterious strength of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws once more. Using these Law lines in the space, he began to stir up a giant vortex.

No matter what strength it was, everything was pulled into that vortex and into the void furnace. The primal jade quintessence and all the other heavenly materials were ruthlessly suppressed!

All of these different billowing strengths raged around like multi-colored rivers of stars, surging waves in a great sea.

All of the strengths within Yin Yang Despair Valley were pulled in and fused together. Even the coiling ridge giant corpses in the icy mountain valleys emitted faint traces of death energy tha gathered into the vortex.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

This was the equivalent of all the strengths within Yin Yang Despair Valley crushing and grinding down the jade dragon horn’s dragon spirit and all of the other spirits of the different heavenly treasures.

The void furnace withstood all of this tyrannical strength, rapidly expanding like a balloon.

Even Xiao Moxian was startled by all of these wild strengths smashing into each other. Like a small bunny hopping away she immediately jumped back 10 miles.

Only Lin Ming still floated in the skies like before, his arms spread white. All sorts of energy lines wove around him, constantly repairing and supplementing the void furnace, maintaining its strength and supporting its continued revolution.

In the midst of the furnace, the dragon spirit of the jade dragon horn was the first to give up. Its body stiffened and it began to crack apart.

Soon after that, the spirit of the heaven devouring snake gallbladder was swallowed up by the several strengths and broken down, turning into a snake-like fluid.

Dragon saliva grass, primal jade quintessence…beneath the crashing waves of strength, they were like pills being crushed in a mortar by a medicine pestle, continuously cracking apart into different essences.

Beneath nirvanic flames and heavenly tribulation flames, these essences were catalyzed by the other spiritual forces and began to fuse together.

Red, white, blue…multi-colored hues of liquid were smelting together, constantly attacking each other and wearing each other down…

Lin Ming sat in meditation, his eyes shut even as his hands carefully manipulated the powers floating above him, turning them all into flames.

These flames were not true burning flames, but virtual flames formed from energy. This strength constantly flowed out from all over Yin Yang Despair Valley. Some flames were heated like fiery flames, some were ghostly and ethereal, and some emitted a dreadful aura. All of these flames entered the void furnace and helped in melting the materials within.

Placed in the midst of all these energies, although Lin Ming was only refining a pill, he still had strength constantly flowing into him as if he were immersed in a sea of energy.

His entire body felt comfortable. No matter how many tough calculations he had to make or how many Asura Heavenly Dao Law lines he had to manipulate, or how much soul force he head to use, he didn’t feel tired at all.

This entire Yin Yang Despair Valley had existed here for billions of years already. The strength saved up in this land was alarming.

Lin Ming stayed in this state for a full three years. During this entire time he didn’t feel as if the powers in Yin Yang Despair Valley diminished even the slightest bit.

As for the void furnace, all of the strengths that were pulled there by Lin Ming had turned into ghostly azure colored flames – this was a phenomenon that only occurred once flames reached an extremely terrifying temperature.

A great deal of the materials and medicinal essences inside began to slowly absorb these different strengths. Within the center of this endless medicinal efficacy, a life seemed to be forming within it. This existence was blood red and brimming over with an atmosphere of intense life vitality.

Lin Ming knew that the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill was soon about to condense!

After another month, the last drop of liquid fused into the middle of the breeding existence.

An incomprehensibly powerful surge of energy washed out, one that shocked even Lin Ming. This was something that spread out from the breeding existence in the void furnace.

Lin Ming’s eyes shot up. A brilliant like exploded in his eyes like a bolt of lightning in the dark.

A snow white runic symbol, the medicinal runic symbol, was thrust into the breeding object.

The object began to give off a blazing heat. Blinding arcs of light shot out from its surface…

Finally, with the sound of cracking glass, a blood red pill appeared within the void furnace, one the size of a heart.

As this pill appeared, dao pattern energy currents appeared around it, making it appear supernatural and strange.

The blood red medicinal fragrance turned into liquid. As the pill floated in this liquid, it exuded an inexplicably formidable pressure.

The pill began to throb like a beating heart, as loud as rumbling thunder.

It was like it wasn’t a pill but the heart of a True Divinity.

Lin Ming was ecstatic with joy. This was the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill, the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill! He had finally succeeded!

Suddenly, the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill started to rush about in all directions, wanting to escape from the void furnace.

Lin Ming was surprised. After the medicinal efficacy had been refined to the limit, the pill had gained a wisdom of its own and wanted to escape. Some pills, after escaping, could even cultivate into a spiritual being!

This sort of situation appeared because Lin Ming the materials Lin Ming sued to refine the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill were extremely precious. Moreover, the improved medicinal runic symbol had increased the medicinal efficacy of the pill.

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. The entire void furnace began to shrink and compress in on itself. Within it, all of the massive flames formed from strengths of Yin Yang Despair Valley also condensed. Underneath Lin Ming’s control, they constantly poured into the Asura Heavenly Dao Law patterns that formed the furnace.

Immediately, because the void furnace was fused with infinite strength, it began to sparkle with a brilliant light.

Every single wisp of the Asura Heavenly Dao Law lines was filled with an incomparably vast energy!

As for the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill, it was tightly shackled by this tremendous energy!

Chapter 1665 – Preparation Is the Key to Success

Lin Ming clenched his fists together, a divine light shining in his eyes. In order to break through this Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace, Lin Ming had put forth an unimaginable amount of effort. And now, he had finally succeeded!

As he felt the strength surging in his body, Lin Ming impatiently wanted to fight.

Ever since he left the Marvel Blue Nation he had yet to fight a truly powerful opponent.

Closing his eyes deep in meditation, Lin Ming carefully felt the strength of the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace.

The first two Dao Palaces of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace – Heavenly Retribution and Purple Temple.

Of them, the function of the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace was to use the body of a martial artist as a medium to commune with the heavens and earth.

The body was a microcosm unto itself and could correspond to stars in the universe. In the boundless world, the so-called power of heavenly retribution was ultimately the strength of the Heavenly Dao.

After the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace opened, a martial artist could use the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace as a communication medium to allow the body to bear the power of the heavens and earth!

No matter how powerful one’s mortal body was, how powerful could it be? Even royal God Beasts could only compare to extreme Empyreans.

But the power of the heavens and earth was different. Their power could be described in an infinitely varied number of ways.

For instance, when a star exploded and a black hole was formed, this was a strength that would even suck in an Empyrean and turn them into nothing.

Of course, with Lin Ming’s current strength wanting to simulate such a strength was far from possible. He still had a long road ahead of him.

“Power of the heavens and earth…”

Lin Ming gripped his fists, feeling the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace in his body communing with the heavens and earth, absorbing the surging energy within the world. This sort of feeling was the legendary union with the world.

To have the heavens and earth stand on the same level as the mortal body; when Lin Ming’s cultivation reached the peak, fighting with him would be tantamount to fighting against the entirety of the heavens and earth!

When a martial artist’s body transformation technique stepped from the Eight Inner Hidden Gates into the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, the truth was that this was essentially equal to finishing cultivating the mortal body and instead beginning to cultivate the Laws of the Nine Stars.

The Nine Star Laws were one of the 33 Heavenly Dao Laws. If they hadn’t been sealed because of some unknown reason, they wouldn’t be much worse than the saint race’s body transformation technique. They would only be a bit more difficult to cultivate.

The origin of the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace’s strength came not from a martial artist’s body but from the momentum of the heavens and earth. Thus, no matter how long a battle was, a martial artist wouldn’t overdraw their physical strength. This was one of the reasons why the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace was so formidable!

“Now my body doesn’t need the skills within the Celestial Tyrant Manual to reach 20 billion jins. This is the same as the strength of twin dragons!”

Lin Ming felt that just making gestures with his hand could affect the momentum of the world. Astral essence flooded his body like a surging sea, his supernatural strength gushing like a tide!

Besides being able to draw support from the momentum of the world, Lin Ming’s mortal body had also become far more intense. The Heavenly Dao true meaning of the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace had fused into his flesh and blood.

His body had become terrifying to an amazing degree and his strength had rapidly risen. As he opened his eyes, purple lightning flashed in his pupils. His current strength and aura were extraordinary.

“Big Brother Lin, did you already break into the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace? Amazing!”

As Lin Ming landed on the largest ancient bronze coffin, Xiao Moxian didn’t know why but she felt a hint of inexplicable sadness. Just then when she watched Lin Ming attack the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace, his body had cracked open and was being torn apart… but she actually wasn’t able to help at all. This made her feel something that she couldn’t define with words.

Moreover, Lin Ming had spent these last 30 years working wholeheartedly towards breaking into the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace. He had paid many prices, and Xiao Moxian had seen all of this occur with her own eyes. In the Asura Road, Lin Ming had no one backing him and no large influence supporting him. All of the materials and resources he needed were things that he struggled for a little at a time!

At the Divine Rune City Auction, everyone had seen Lin Ming’s blinding halo and had seen him use his exquisite divine runic symbols to suppress the crowd and had even played with Shadow Overflow and the other dark divine runic masters in the palm of his hand. But, which one of them had seen Lin Ming spend years in his divine runic room in order to draw up divine runic symbols? He had not rested for days at a time, exhausted the strength of his divine soul without end and even relied on the Divine Mist Heart Mantra and Soul Recovery Symbols to restore his soul force and continue. He had worked without rest, and oftentimes he would collapse on the ground, his face pale and his eyes bloodshot!

All of that work had finally paid off in today’s accomplishments!

Everyone guessed that Lin Ming had some secret on his body, and Xiao Moxian also faintly knew what Lin Ming’s secret was. But, if someone thought that just relying on this secret would have allowed Lin Ming to arrive where they were, they would be utterly mistaken. The reason Lin Ming was able to stand where he was today was because his mentality and iron will played a great role.

At this time, Lin Ming could be said to be mind-linked with Xiao Moxian. He could vaguely feel just what Xiao Moxian was thinking. He moved forwards, gently cupping her cheek in his palm as he said, “For me to come this far, I’m already very lucky. After this final trial ends, I must return to the Divine Realm to face the great calamity of humanity. The road I need to walk is still long.

“As must I…” Xiao Moxian took a deep shuddering breath. The solemn road before her, the calamity of humanity, there were many things she had to face. Not only did she need to face the saint race but also those that might already have turned towards the saint race – the monster race and her grandfather.

If this was before, Xiao Moxian would have felt it impossible to resist the decision of her people. But now a deep fighting spirit had ignited in her mind. Only by being powerful would she have the ability to argue with her race and face the great calamity.

Moreover, as Lin Ming continued to grow stronger, Xiao Moxian had to hasten her pace and follow him. She would not allow herself to be cast off by him. She would definitely complete her nine nirvanas!

When Lin Ming broke into the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace, his body obtained endless benefits.

Even just sitting down, he could feel the blood within him surging like a river. There was also a great deal of majestic starlight that had yet to be absorbed. Even some of the medicinal efficacy of the Ravenous Wolf Heaven Pill and nameless ancient pill still remained in his blood and marrow.

This made it so that every time he breathed, misty white air would spray out from his nose, filling the air around him with clouds of medicinal fragrance.

“There is still a great deal of energy within me that hasn’t been digested… although I broke into the second Dao Palace, I have less than 20 years from the final trial beginning. I absolutely cannot be negligent in my preparations. This Asura Road world is vast and boundless and there are countless geniuses and powerhouses here, yet, when they enter the final trial they all fail. In the last 100 million years, the highest completion percentage has only been slightly more than eighty and there are also many chosen prides of heaven that perish in the final trial…”

Lin Ming didn’t underestimate the final trial. This would be the most important battle he would face in the Asura Road and he had to make sure all his preparations were complete.

“Then I’ll use this period of time to borrow the spiritual strengths within the Forsaken Mortal Tomb to make another breakthrough!” Lin Ming thought to himself.

During this breakthrough into the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace, Lin Ming had come perfectly prepared for all situations. Thus, the difficulty he encountered was far less than when he tried to break into the first Dao Palace.

The final trial of the Asura Road could be imagined to have many uncertainties and dangers.

From this moment on, he would need to do his best to prepare yet again.

“Xian’er, I want to attack the late Divine Lord realm here.” Lin Ming said to Xiao Moxian, his eyes sparkling.

Xiao Moxian’s eyes curved up and a smirk appeared on her face. “The final trial will arrive in a dozen plus years. You can calmly cultivate here. As for me, I won’t be idling around either. I will cultivate together with you. I’ll make sure that you won’t be able to leave me behind that much!”

“Good, then let’s do this together.” Lin Ming looked at the animated Xiao Moxian, his eyes following her slim and graceful figure as he smiled.

Time passed. Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian spent their time cultivating together in this mysterious danger zone.

The two were both extremely proud children of heaven. As their bodies twined together, a misty brilliance emerged from them. Lin Ming’s True Dragon aura wove together with Xiao Moxian’s Dark Phoenix aura, soaring into the skies.

A resonant dragon’s howl, a clear phoenix’s cry, an aura filled with thunder and fire spread out in all directions, dispersing all shadows.

As the two of them dual cultivated longer and longer, the True Dragon phantom and Dark Phoenix phantom in the skies became increasingly realistic.

One dragon, one phoenix, they were like the sun and the moon, brilliant and lustrous.

Countless dazzling and mystical runes overflowed from their bodies, revolving in wild waves around the two…

In the Forsaken Mortal Tomb, days of cultivating were incomparably long.

As Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian dual cultivated year after year, the auspicious power of their dragon and phoenix became even more formidable.

Three years later –

All of the medicinal efficacy within Lin Ming’s body, as well as the starlight glory he harvested after breaking through the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace, was completely fused into him. His body seemed to have returned to its origin, without leaking out even the tiniest amount of strength.

As for the strength accumulated in his body, it had reached a terrifying degree.

At this time, Lin Ming’s eyes turned towards the death energy around him and the residual will around the ancient bronze coffin.

“Essence energy of the heavens and earth, come unto my body!”

Lin Ming flicked his finger and shot out a gray rune. The air shook as strange ripples appeared in space. Suddenly wisps of the black turtle death energy began flooding his body.

This was a rune of the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel!

The Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel could absorb the remnant souls of devils. When Tian Mingzi died in the past, his soul had been sucked into the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. This time, the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel was absorbing the spiritual energy that filled the entirety of the Forsaken Mortal Tomb; it was simply too wonderful.

When Lin Ming cultivated by himself, he would bring out the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel and begin swallowing and refining the black turtle death energy and the residual wills that exuded from the ancient bronze coffins.

These residual wills were all muddled and without sense of self. If Lin Ming didn’t have an extremely sharp perception he simply wouldn’t have been able to realize this power existed.

As wisps of residual will from the Forsaken Mortals fell onto the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel that was formed by the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws, they were like soldiers meeting a general, immediately becoming calm and docile.

The black turtle death energy and the phantoms of gold-armored giants floated in the air. Slowly, Lin Ming absorbed them into the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, refining them into the purest form of energy that constantly filled Lin Ming’s body.

There was far too much energy within the Forsaken Mortal Tomb. Lin Ming was only able to absorb an extremely limited amount of it. But after accumulating this energy again and again every day, it brought about amazing changes to Lin Ming’s body.

These changes were an accumulation of quantity that led to a qualitative change. Without noticing it, Lin Ming’s inner world was flooded to the limit with energy. Lin Ming’s cultivation was already taking great steps towards entering the late Divine Lord realm.

Chapter 1666 – Late Divine Lord

Spring passed to fall and then back again. Within this Forsaken Mortal Tomb, Lin Ming constantly cultivated. In the blink of an eye, five years had gone by.

Lin Ming’s hair continued to grow and whenever it was too long Xiao Moxian would cut it for him. For these five years, Xiao Moxian hadn’t cut her hair at all. Because her hair wasn’t short to begin with, the current Xiao Moxian’s hair looked like a black waterfall that fell to her ankles, blooming like a rose.

Lin Ming sat in meditation, faint traces of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws continuously spinning around his body like countless threads of black silk.

Moreover, these black silk threads were twined together with the strange runes from the ancient bronze coffin. Through analyzing these, one could comprehend the true meaning of those mysterious runes.

Another three years passed.

Eight years later…

With Lin Ming’s effort, the energy within his body became increasingly rich.

Just by simply sitting on the ancient bronze coffin, his entire body emitting a brilliance like a divine Buddha.

Countless runes appeared on his skin, shimmering into existence within his flesh and blood. They floated in the void, automatically absorbing the essence of the heavens and earth.

The true meaning of the ancient bronze coffin’s runes unexpectedly appeared in the void around him. Their essence had already been comprehended by him.

“These are runes derived from the Asura Heavenly Dao. With these runes on the ancient bronze coffins, they are able to form massive spirit gathering arrays and swallow the essence energy from the heavens and earth to constantly nourish whatever it is that lies within these ancient coffins… if these runes were to fuse into my flesh and blood, then during battle they would automatically absorb the essence energy of the world on their own… even if the speed isn’t too fast, there are actually endless advantages to them…”

As Lin Ming spoke to himself, he formed seal after seal.

12 years later…

On this day, Lin Ming could clearly feel something change within him. His heart beat like a drum, every beat like a bolt of thunder, every beat causing the earth to quake along with his heart.

With a thought, a plain-looking pill flew into Lin Ming’s palm. This pill was the nameless ancient pill that Lin Ming had won at the Divine Rune City Auction.

Before, only a tiny bit of the essence energy from this pill had been absorbed by Lin Ming. 90% of its medicinal strength still remained.

Lin Ming directly swallowed down this nameless ancient pill. Then, a deep and robust strength broke into his inner world.

The current Lin Ming was far stronger than he was in the past. After subduing the Ravenous Wolf Star and opening the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace, even the swelling stormy strength of the nameless ancient pill was unable to shake the root of Lin Ming’s foundation!

By borrowing this strength and all the accumulations he made during the last 12 years, Lin Ming finally began his breakthrough into the late Divine Lord realm!

There was a loud rumbling sound in his dantian and a wisp of deep blue spiritual strength appeared, wrapped with mysterious runes and filled with an immense aura that brimmed over with vitality.

Waves of spiritual strength, death energy, and the power of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws began to wildly attack the borders of Lin Ming’s inner world.

The Purple Temple Dao Palace appeared and waves of astral power impacted the world with tens of billions of jins of force. As all of this strength attacked the inner world, mountains were shattered and created, rivers were broken and formed…

Ka ka ka!

Thunder recklessly cast down and flames swept through the skies. The Heretical God Tree floated high in the air, sending out peals of tyrannical thunder, frantically expanding the boundaries of the inner world.

Wherever this strength went, space would explode into pieces.

However, this terrifying annihilating power of thunder and fire hid a shuddering vitality within it.

Following the destructive paths of the thunder and fire, a faint bright green color would appear in the world.

Through all these various strengths, the small world began to grow with marvelous changes occurring everywhere. A strange and misty life force spread throughout, becoming increasingly vibrant.

Such a change continued for over two months. Then, light began shooting out from Lin Ming’s pores. The evolution of his inner world was reaching its finale and the medicinal efficacy of the nameless ancient pill had also been fully absorbed by him.

In that instant, Lin Ming’s eyes flashed open. A terrifying aura erupted from his body. However, in the next moment, all of it was restrained, completely vanishing from the senses!

Even Xiao Moxian, who was looking at Lin Ming, couldn’t feel his existence.

Lin Ming’s aura seemed to have completely melted and fused into the world surrounding him.

The small world within his body also developed a strange connection to the outside.

The reason such a change occurred was that Lin Ming had finally broken into the late Divine Lord realm. But more than that, it was because he had already opened the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace, allowing his body to commune with the heavens and earth, achieving a state of becoming one with the world.

“Big Brother Lin, you finally reached the late Divine Lord realm! The next boundary is a half-step Holy Lord and then the Holy Lord realm. After Big Brother Lin reaches the Holy Lord realm, I have no idea what your strength will be like. I even wonder if you’ll have a chance of surviving in the presence of an Empyrean…” Xiao Moxian hopefully whispered.

“Empyrean?” Lin Ming shook his head. “An Empyrean is far too strong. Even if I am at the Holy Lord realm I doubt I will be able to compare to even the weakest of Empyreans. Just the Great World King boundary is an enormous span. If I want to cross two large boundaries to challenge someone, I don’t think that is possible at all.”

Before this, Lin Ming had often been able to jump two large boundaries to fight. But, this had basically been the Divine Sea realm against the Divine Lord realm, or Divine Transformation realm against the Holy Lord realm.

However, the boundary that separated a Great World King and an Empyrean was far too large. And, those that manage to reach that realm were all outstanding existences. During their youth, they too were able to jump ranks to fight. If Lin Ming wanted to jump past two boundaries to fight characters like these, that would be as difficult as ascending to the heavens.

“Mm… fighting an Empyrean is a bit too exaggerated, but when you complete the final trial, your strength will further increase yet again. At that time, no one will be able to predict just where the limits of your strength are!”

“Final trial… perhaps it might not be so simple.” Lin Ming shook his head. He wasn’t able to predict just what completion percentage he would obtain after the final trial ended. “It’s not a good time for us to leave here yet. My late Divine Lord foundation is unstable and there is still a limitless amount of black turtle death energy and all sorts of strengths here. We can take this spiritual strength as food to consolidate both our late Divine Lord cultivations and stabilize our inner worlds.”

Lin Ming wasn’t in a hurry to leave; he still had several years before the final trial would begin. Before that, he still had to draw up a batch of divine runic symbols to use so that he would have additional trump cards when facing the dangers in the final trial.

During these next several years he had to consolidate his cultivation and steadily stand in the late Divine Lord realm.

As for Xiao Moxian, she also needed to cultivate so that she could attempt to reach the peak of the late Divine Lord realm.

…….

What Lin Ming didn’t know was that during this period of seclusion, a considerable event was occurring in the Asura Road.

On one day, a blue phoenix appeared in the skies above the central province of Divine Void Divine Kingdom. This was a true Phoenix God Beast with a pure bloodline. And on this phoenix’s back was a mysterious woman wrapped in an icy blue dress.

This woman’s face was covered with gauze. As she stood there she seemed lofty and proud, someone that renounced the world and took solace in herself. As she appeared she attracted the attention of many people, and finally, she even alarmed the Divine Sovereign of the Divine Void Divine Kingdom – Soul Emperor Divine Void.

Soul Emperor Divine Void had already reached the True Divinity realm. Even so, he intentionally left seclusion to personally meet this blue-clothed woman…

Chapter 1669 – Asura Sea

Deep within the inner Asura Road, there was a vast and endless sea called the Asura Sea.

The Asura Sea was connected to all large bodies of water within the Asura Road. It was incomparably large, unfathomably deep.

Even if a star were to sink into the Asura Sea, it would be completely submerged in the waters.

This terrifying sea had sea beasts and dangerous fish that reached unbelievable sizes. Even Empyrean level powerhouses weren’t willing to fly deep into the Asura Sea, lest they meet these terrifying sea creatures.

However, in these past few days, this Asura Sea that people rarely visited was actually becoming increasingly lively.

From time to time there would be high level martial artists flying across the sea. Sometimes there would be giant troops appearing and disappearing.

All of this was because the final trial’s mystic realm was located atop the Asura Sea!

The final trial could be called the most important part of the Asura Road world. Some people even believed that when the Asura Road Master created the Asura Road in the past, it was to develop a foundation for the final trial to continue his inheritance.

But no matter whether or not these stories were reliable or what the truth was, it was without doubt that the final trial was the grandest event in the entire Asura Road!

All the various influences in the Asura Road certainly wouldn’t miss out on such a grand event. If an influence had a disciple participating in the final trial they would certainly come to closely watch the results. Even for influences that didn’t have any disciples participating, they would still come to gather information – information on their enemies’ disciples or their allies’ disciples and how they grew.

Beyond that, there were many curious individuals that came to join in on the fun. This grand event gathered all sorts of heroic individuals. With such a great scene, who would miss out on it?

……………

At this time, at the border area of Divine Void Divine Kingdom, there was a massive sect that occupied vast swathes of land. This sect’s buildings were grand and magnificent, and at the mountain entrances, dozens of great array formations were laid down. If Lin Ming were here, then even under his high standards he would still judge these as top array formations. Once these array formations were activated together and under the management of a top powerhouse, even several Empyreans working together would find it difficult to break through!

For a sect to have such grand array formations, their background should be deep and there should be many young elites pouring forth from their ranks. However, the truth was the opposite. This sect was sparsely populated and didn’t seem to have any life to it at all. The array formations around the mountains remained unopened and unused, doing nothing but gathering dust.

This was because although these array formations were incomparably powerful, they used up too many energy stones far too quickly. The sect simply wasn’t able to keep up the supply of energy stones, thus these array formations only served as decorations now.

Without a doubt, this was a sect that had once been glorious beyond comparison, but was now in steep decline.

At this time, in a grand hall of the sect, a black-clothed man and green-clothed girl were kneeling on the ground. Standing in front of the two of them was an old man with thick white hair and beard.

“Moonpond, Soulsky, the two of you are the final hopes of our Divine Mist Holy Land… ever since Empyrean Divine Mist went missing, our sect has had to withstand the other influences nibbling away at us, and now we are no longer as radiant as we were in the past. In order to train you two… the sect could be said to have given all of our resources. This time, master has also paid a great price to obtain two spots in the final trial for you both. I only hope that you will not disappoint the sect!”

This old man’s face was covered with wrinkles. His body was old and bent and his fires of life were as frail as a candle in the wind, ready to extinguish at any moment; this old man was in the final years of his life…

Looking at this dying old man, no one would imagine that he was once just a tiny bit away from becoming an Empyrean. In the past, he followed Empyrean Divine Mist to adventure through the world and wage war with their enemies. In the entire inner Asura Road, his name had been earth-shaking and people panicked in his presence. But after Empyrean Divine Mist went missing, he had been tricked and wounded by his enemies and now he ended up in this state.

The two youths remained kneeling. Although they didn’t speak, their eyes showed their determination.

“Go then my children. Although Empyrean Divine Mist might have perished in the past, the heavens have not abandoned my Divine Mist Holy Lands. For master to run into you two in the final thousand years of my life, that is my fortune. You two are the last remaining wealth of the Divine Mist Holy Lands. Now, my only wish is that you two can become Empyreans in the future and allow my Divine Mist Holy Lands to be restored to its former glory!”

The old man’s voice was bleak and lonely, making the souls of those who listened to him tremble. Behind him stood a towering black stone statue. This statue’s appearance was shaped exactly like Empyrean Divine Mist’s in Tragic Death Valley. The statue’s eyes stared off into the far distance, its eyes filled with awe and indifference.

At the same time, in the bordering Divine Void Divine Kingdom, it was a completely different scene.

Within Divine Void Heavenly Palace, in a starry world, Soul Emperor Divine Void floated high in the skies, his clothes white like snow. His entire body emitted the light of Laws. With just a wave of his hand or a step of his foot, space twisted and churned!

In front of him, innumerable young elites knelt on the ground, lined up in rows. These kneeling disciples extended all the way backwards, and looking to the far end, one could see that there were hundreds of thousands of people!

But at the front of these hundreds of thousands of disciples were 10 martial artists kneeling side by side. These 10 individuals had cultivations ranging from the late Divine Lord realm to the ordinary World King realm. They were outstanding figures chosen from all of these disciples and elected to enter the final trial on behalf of Divine Void Divine Kingdom!

“You are all outstanding elites of Divine Void Divine Kingdom. I want all of you to reach at least 70%! Out of all the different influences participating I want you all to be first!”

This deep and dreadful voice echoed through this world, even causing the stars in the sky to tremble.

In front of Soul Emperor Divine Void, all of the disciples of Divine Void Divine Kingdom knelt downwards. And behind them there were seven tall figures. These figures were all wrapped in cloaks, their bodies overflowing with terrifying fluctuations of Laws.

These seven people all had Empyrean realm cultivations.

Seven Empyreans! They were all the rulers of Divine Void Divine Kingdom’s seven provinces!

Divine Void Divine Kingdom was undoubtedly the number one spiritas influence in the entire inner Asura Road. But, this didn’t mean that there was no opponent that could match them.

The rival of Divine Void Divine Kingdom was also a True Divinity Holy Land, one of the saint race – Heaven Union Divine Kingdom.

…..

Within the inner Asura Road, one saint True Divinity influence and one spiritas True Divinity influence, the two of them represented the ultimate strength of their respective races. Their struggles and rivalry were in a sense the struggle between the saints and spiritas!

“You have one opponent, and that is Divine Void Divine Kingdom!” Within Heaven Union Divine Kingdom, Divine Sovereign Heaven Union also personally mobilized his disciples. His figure was concealed in the dim void and it was impossible to make out his appearance. All anyone saw was a figure that stood high like an iron tower.

“The final trial is under the gaze of all people, but no matter how many heroes converge at the Asura Sea, their eyes will focus on us and Divine Void Divine Kingdom! During this final trial we must become the focal point of everyone’s attention! You must not disgrace me! Suppress Divine Void Divine Kingdom and allow the saints to be proud and prosper. If so, then all of you shall be generously rewarded! Otherwise, if you fail me then you must sit in confinement for 100 years!”

Divine Sovereign Heaven Union’s voice was vibrant and powerful, echoing through the starry skies!

………

As influences from all over set out towards the Asura Sea, the day for the opening of the final trial finally approached.

Rumble rumble!

Just as the sun was dawning and the sky was filled with haze, a loud explosion rang through the entire coastline.

On the calm sea surface, whirlpools appeared all over that were thousands of miles wide. A giant long-necked sea beast the size of a mountain shot out from deep within the sea.

As this sea beast appeared, it carried with it a ferocious and cruel aura, making all who saw it feel shocked and intimidated.

Above the sea beast stood two troops of blue-armored warriors. They grasped tridents in their hands that sparkled with electricity and their expressions were resolute.

Between these blue-armored warriors stood a handsome youth with skin as fair as jade. This man was the Crown Prince of an Empyrean level influence that dwelled in the Asura Sea, a clan of seafaring people.

Countless mermen shot out from the surface of the water, grasping gleaming weapons in their hands. Their momentum was overwhelming and dreadful.

Before these people came to a stop, at this moment, a strange howl echoed out from the skies.

All they saw was a massive ink-black giant beast descend, as if it had fallen down from the galaxy. Black clouds surrounded its body and it brought with it an unparalleled deadly aura.

Sitting above this pitch black giant beast was a man with a long scar on his face.

This man’s eyes were cold and shined with a sharp golden light. It was like this person could shoot out countless swords with just a single glance.

From the layer of clouds behind him, three-headed birds shot out. Each bird had numerous warriors standing guard atop its back.

In the blink of an eye, from the waves, a massive golden carriage shot up from the water’s surface, pulled by 16 flood dragons.

These flood dragons were massive, looking like islands that moved across the sea. Wherever they went, stormy waves would rise up, causing the vast sea to churn.

Sitting in this golden carriage was a tall fat person, as round as a mountain of meat. He held a beast leg as thick as a bucket and was gnawing on it. As he ate, he also glanced at the people around him.

Black turtles floated on the surface behind this golden carriage, following its path. Tens of thousands of figures stood on these black turtles and were cheering as loudly as they could.

Even though these people were all different, all of them were outstanding individuals within the Asura Road!

Today, they had all gathered here. Amongst them, some were friends and some were enemies. But no matter who they were, their goal here today was the final trial.

“Hoho, it’s quite lively. There are so many young heroes here.” Suddenly, in the skies above, the white clouds began to change shape, turning into a staircase of white clouds.

A rich-looking man stood tall and proud, wearing a crown on his head and dressed in bright yellow robes. Behind him were gaggles of beautifully swaying young women, all of them stepping down the stairway of clouds as they followed the man.

With every step this man took, it was like the sea below him resonated with him.

The many gathered chosen prides of heaven looked up at this newcomer.

“Eclipse Palace’s Palace Master?”

This Eclipse Palace Master was a half-step Empyrean. In the past he had killed countless people and was a fierce and ominous figure. But for the last million years, he had been living quietly in seclusion. However, he had decided to come out for this grand event.

Afterwards, more and more people arrived. The young master of the Hundred Thousand Foot Cliff, the proudest son of the Aurora Holy Lands, the head monks of Bountiful Fields Temple… one at a time, high level figures from the influences that ruled over the Asura Road began to appear in abundance.

After all, the qualifications for the Asura Road’s final trial were far too important.

At this time, on the coast of the Asura Sea, a hundred mile long observation pavilion had been set up. On this observation pavilion were tides of people, and all of these people were powerhouses that originated from all over the Asura Road. However, many of these people hadn’t reached a level of talent that allowed them to compete in the final trial, thus they were only able to look on from a distance.

And, there were over 30 of these observation pavilions set along the coast of the Asura Sea. On these observation pavilions, all that gathered were elites of the world.

Chapter 1672 – The Worries of Old Su

When Lin Ming flew into the final trial he kept a low profile, just like the blue-clothed woman. In addition, he was very fast so there were many people that didn’t notice him.

However, there were some considerably strong people with keen eyesight who were familiar with Lin Ming and saw his back.

“That person is… the Divine Runic Masters Guild’s Lin Ming?” The one who spoke was a World King powerhouse. He had attended the Divine Rune City Auction in the past so he had an extremely deep impression of Lin Ming.

“Lin Ming? The creator of the Lin symbols?”

Many people had never seen Lin Ming but knew of his name. He was someone who created the myth of gathering 10 billion contribution points in half a month, and this was a story that spread throughout the entirety of the inner Asura Road.

“Isn’t he only at the Divine Lord realm? Moreover, he’s a divine runic master… is he planning on entering the final trial?”

In everyone’s opinion, those young geniuses with extraordinary combat talent wouldn’t choose to become divine runic masters.

People had limited time and energy, and the occupation of a divine runic master was an extremely time-consuming ordeal. Even Lin Ming, who possessed the heaven-defying Magic Cube and had absorbed the memories of three divine runic masters, still had his own cultivation speed delayed considerably due to studying the divine runic arts.

Of course, disasters and blessings came together. Because he studied the divine runic arts, Lin Ming had an even deeper understanding of the Asura Laws. These were all things that occurred later.

As for other geniuses they didn’t possess something as ridiculous as the Magic Cube, if they placed all their time in studying the divine runic arts then their combat talent would naturally be left behind.

In many people’s opinion, Lin Ming’s talent in the divine runic arts had reached the pinnacle of possibility. If he didn’t invest a massive amount of time into the divine runic arts then there wouldn’t be anyone who believed this.

In this situation, most people subconsciously believed that Lin Ming, who lacked cultivation time, would have a dismally low combat efficiency. Otherwise, he would be too abnormal an existence.

But now he actually flew into the final trial mystic realm with a mere Divine Lord cultivation. This left everyone watching outside stunned. If Lin Ming were to perish inside, wouldn’t that just be too great a pity?

“This boy, just what games is he playing…” On the observation pavilion, Divine Rune City’s Old Xue and Old Su had also arrived some time ago. These two old geezers had already reached the limit of their cultivation and the only thing that grew for them every day was their hair. They spent most of their time idling about with their hobbies and of course wouldn’t miss such a lively event. Since they were here, they naturally spotted Lin Ming.

As Old Su saw Lin Ming fly into the final trial mystic realm, he was a tad worried. There were many Holy Lords and World Kings gathered inside! Moreover, these people were all outstanding characters amongst their cultivation step. And beyond that, there were also the dangers of the final trial. If Lin Ming were to enter with a mere Divine Lord realm cultivation, it would undoubtedly be disastrously risky for him! Old Su didn’t want such a divine runic arts prodigy to die inside.

“Hey, don’t look down on him. That little fellow’s strength isn’t as simple as you think it is. We have no idea just what level he is. We’ve worried for him before, but it’s all been in vain. He’s a smart young boy. If he dares to enter the Asura Road then he should have some confidence in his ability. I have no idea what completion percentage he will obtain though… if it’s 70% then that really is too abnormal.”

Old Xue had an unusual amount of faith in Lin Ming.

“70%... you sure are optimistic. If he can survive that hell and come out alive then I’ll already be thanking the heavens and earth. His talent is good, but in the end he is only at the Divine Lord realm. Can he really jump two large boundaries to fight a World King genius? I fear that he will be harmed by someone inside. Even his enemy Duke Fullmoon is in there. If that person is thinking of assassinating Lin Ming…”

As Old Su spoke to here he was a bit scared. In Divine Rune City, Lin Ming would have the protection of the Divine Runic Masters Guild as well as that mysterious master of his.

But in the final trial, Lin Ming could only rely on himself!

Killing in there was not uncommon! Even unparalleled geniuses still needed to be past the Divine Lord realm so they would have the ability to ensure their own safety. Only then would someone dare to enter the final trial.

As these two old men were speaking, within that dreadful vortex of energy that spanned from the heavens to earth, another familiar form appeared.

This form wasn’t some stranger; it was the Extreme Star Holy Lands’ Suya.

The two old men glanced at each other, surprised. They didn’t think that Suya would also enter the final trial.

“This girl’s strength cannot be underestimated. Moreover, she is interested in Lin Ming. I hope that she will look after him…” Old Su mumbled. In front of him, the overwhelming storm of energy became increasingly fierce…

…………

As Lin Ming approached the strange world of the final trial, he felt goosebumps rise all over his body. He could hear a strange sound in the void; it was the incomparably pure sea of energy trembling.

This strange world appeared to be a massive black vortex. Any beam of light that neared it was distorted and swallowed up.

Xiao Moxian anxiously held onto Lin Ming’s hand.

As Lin Ming felt Xiao Moxian slip her hand into his, he reached out and gently wrapped his hand across her waist. With his right hand he waved the Phoenix Blood Spear, sending out a wave of energy that gradually calmed down the strange energy.

With a resolute shout, Lin Ming decisively rushed into this unusual new world.

Woosh woosh woosh –

Beside him, a succession of proud heroes from the Asura Road hurtled in, all of them rushing ahead to be first.

The final trial was extremely dangerous.

The final trial had a very high mortality rate.

…These were all things that those who participated were well aware of. But, the heaven-defying lucky chances within were enough to make their eyes go red with envy.

Waves of thick energy crashed onto everyone like a violent stormy sea.

Every wave of energy was like the impact of an ancient beast. Even Lin Ming felt a considerable amount of pressure. However, after having broken into the second Dao Palace, his mortal body was a hundred times more solid than those vicious beasts from ancient times. Although he was hindered, he didn’t suffer any injuries.

Lin Ming spread his hands wide, his muscles and bones popping as they extended outwards, withstanding the violent flow of energy. Xiao Moxian grasped onto Lin Ming, protected beneath him.

Xiao Moxian could feel a warm flow of energy surround her and a smile crossed her face. With her current strength she was more than capable of withstanding this violent flux of energy, but she rather enjoyed this feeling of being protected by Lin Ming.

His speed was fast, and by relying on his bodily strength he was able to drill through the brutal flow of energy like a hot knife in snow.

As the energy flows crashed into him, all of them scattered on his body.

To the rear, Mo Brightmoon and the two others followed close behind.

Thousand Slaughter furiously slashed out with his golden saber, spiritual strength shooting into the skies, creating nine phantoms of ancient demonic taoties.

These taoties were each massive and terrifying. As they appeared they began to desperately swallow up all of the energy around them, treating the flow of energy like delicious food.

These taotie phantoms constantly grew, but in the process of swallowing they were shattered by the impact of energy. As they broke apart they continued to reform; it was a peculiar sight.

But for better or worse, Mo Brightmoon and the others were all sheltered from the violent flux of energy.

Lin Ming noticed this and was slightly surprised. He realized that Thousand Slaughter’s golden saber was some rare divine weapon so he paid more attention to it.

As Lin Ming looked at the golden saber in Thousand Slaughter’s hand, Thousand Slaughter was also secretly shocked by Lin Ming’s strength.

He had once heard Mo Brightmoon mention this youth. Besides the divine runic arts, this Lin Ming had aspects to him that were beyond the norm. He and Fanny Fafa hadn’t believed these tales much, but as they saw Lin Ming use his body alone to resist the wild waves of energy whilst his speed was even faster than the taotie phantoms, he was left speechless.

Without a doubt, this Lin Ming was far stronger than he was.

“In this world there are actually people that can be so abnormal just by the strength of their bodies? Luckily, he’s our ally.” Fanny Fafa’s eyes widened as a splendid light flashed in his eyes.

Within the flow of energy, all sense and sight was twisted up by the wild fluctuations around them. Besides their own squad, it was impossible to see any further.

Hu - !

The wild flow of energy finally reached its end. As if finally passing through walls of water, the pressure on Lin Ming’s body lightened.

A bizarre land appeared in front of them.

All they saw were a sea of mountain peaks rising up and down in the world like floating islands, vast and endless.

Each mountain peak was covered with vibrant life. There were falling waterfalls and lush green trees. But for some reason, they give off an unrealistic feeling to Lin Ming.

As if everything he saw was fake.

In the distance, he could see surging rivers filled with strange black water.

There, the land was desolate and shrouded in a pale gray atmosphere.

Lin Ming stood on the ground and let Xiao Moxian down. He carefully observed the world in front of him.

“Weird. These things seem both real and false… Moreover, the energy here is peculiar as if there’s some risk, but for some reason I can’t make out what it is.” Lin Ming mumbled.

Faintly, he could feel an inexplicable danger, as if some viper were eyeing him from a hidden nest.

“Why aren’t we walking?” Thousand Slaughter’s strong and tall body arrived behind Lin Ming. He looked down at him from a towering position, asking him in a low and deep voice.

His high bamboo hat left behind a shadow that covered Lin Ming.

Mo Brightmoon also looked at Lin Ming, a bit puzzled.

Fanny Fafa giggled, “Killing has never been the forte of a divine runic master. Sir Lin, if you don’t wish to lead the way then allow me the honor.”

A feminine voice brought with it a faint yin chill. The sound was like a cold snake running over the body, making one feel alarmed.

As Fanny Fafa laughed, his body fluttered up as if he was weightless. As he passed by Lin Ming, his eyes swept over his body, carrying with it a faint sense of ridicule.

When Lin Ming had demonstrated his amazing bodily strength, he had left Fanny Fafa surprised. This had ignited Fanny Fafa’s competitive spirit, one that all martial artists had.

His methods were all extremely strange. His body emitted strands of silk-like milky white spiritual power that probed the surroundings.

This spiritual power spread out, covering the skies and earth.

Lin Ming’s complexion changed. As he realized what Fanny Fafa was doing, he shouted out, “Don’t move!”

But it was too late.

The milky white threads of spiritual strength spread out and submerged in all directions, vanishing from the world as if something had swallowed them up.

Fanny Fafa’s complexion changed. At this time, the originally empty space above them suddenly seemed to be stimulated by something.

The void tore open and an icy cold black energy filled the air.

Four figures threw themselves onto the ground from this black energy, all of them carrying with them a fierce and blood-drenched aura.

Chapter 1674 – Sinister Tricks

Completion, 20%?

Lin Ming perked up and looked towards everyone else. At this time, Mo Brightmoon, Fanny Fafa, and the others were also looking at Lin Ming. It was clear that they also received the information on their completion percentage.

“20%, you?” Lin Ming asked.

“The same.”

Mo Brightmoon and the others glanced at each other. This completion percentage was better than they had anticipated. After all, when walking all the way here the truth was that they hadn’t encountered any true dangers at all.

“The completion percentage should be more difficult the later it is. After 80%, it is likely that every point will be more difficult than the last. Our current completion percentage isn’t strange at all.”

“Let’s go.”

Ho - !

The group finally emerged from the endless wild flow of energy and landed on the ground.

Here, dark winds howled, carrying with them a dry and desolate aura as they swept over the scattered gravel on the ground.

The sky in front of them was unusually high, as blue and transparent as sapphires.

In the far off distance, the shapes of the mountains were vague, resembling the outline of some sleeping great beast.

Beneath their feet was a vast rough land of sand and stone. Thick weeds grew up periodically, many patches as high as a person. There were only several ghostly-looking trees scattered around; the plant life here was sparse.

This was a windswept wilderness, bleak and dreary.

“This is the second level, right?” Xiao Moxian flew up into the skies a little, looking around before falling down next to Lin Ming.

Lin Ming thought for a moment. He didn’t know just how many levels the final trial had. Now that he came here himself, the first few layers weren’t too dangerous at all.

“Don’t worry, let’s rest up first.”

Lin Ming proposed. According to what he knew, the final trial would likely last for several years. Now that everyone had just passed the first level, they had inevitably consumed some of their energy. Since they didn’t know what the second floor was going to be like, they might as well stay here and adjust themselves to their peak condition. This was the safest plan of action.

As Lin Ming spoke, Mo Brightmoon and the others sat in meditation. Without noticing it, Lin Ming had already become the core of the team. On the first level of the smelting trial, everyone had been able to witness Lin Ming’s performance with their own eyes so they naturally listened to his opinion.

However, before the group had meditated for long, a sudden sad and high-pitched scream echoed out from the south of the wilderness.

“Mm?”

Lin Ming frowned. Someone was here!?

In the first level, they had touched a space trap and were transported somewhere else. After that, they hadn’t met any other groups; it was likely they had been cut off from the other groups. But here in the world of the second level, this place was vast and boundless; perhaps there were other squads here.

Should they go and investigate the source of that sad scream?

The other people glanced at each other before looking towards Lin Ming, wanting to solicit his opinion.

If they went to investigate what happened, it was likely they would encounter some dangers.

“Let’s go take a look. But be a bit more careful. If there’s anything wrong then we’ll flee at once.” Lin Ming succinctly stated.

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

The group of people rushed towards the direction of the scream like bolts of lightning.

The group fell onto a barren rocky hill a few miles away, looking towards the area that the horrible scream came from.

Lin Ming’s vision was as sharp as an eagle’s. With one glance he could see a gaping cave going into the ground, one that was covered with a giant bloodstain.

The blood was fresh and hadn’t yet coagulated. Besides that, there weren’t any other clues as to what happened.

It was clear that some macabre death had just occurred here.

At this time, from different directions in the distance, there were the deafening sounds of a sonic boom.

Lin Ming and the others felt their minds chill. They all restrained their auras together.

A milky white spiritual strength emerged from Fanny Fafa’s hands, cutting through the air and thoroughly covering the group’s auras.

Lin Ming couldn’t help but be curious about this milky white spiritual strength. This sort of strange spiritual strength seemed to be Fanny Fafa’s supernatural talent. It was an extremely strange and complex ability. He really had no idea just what cultivation method Fanny Fafa practiced.

“Fourth Junior-apprentice Brother’s soul lamp has been extinguished and his wisp of soul disappeared here. That bloodstain’s aura also belongs to Junior-apprentice Brother. Where is he? Could there be something strange in that cave?”

Both of the two people that flew over were tall and vigorous-looking. One of them was covered with transparent raging flames. These flames exuded a powerful momentum that surrounded the cave with the bloodstain.

The other person held a strange divine runic symbol in their hands.

As the divine runic symbol appeared, it emitted a pitch black fire energy.

“Big Brother Lin, that fellow is using the divine runic symbol you created!” Xiao Moxian whispered to Lin Ming as if she had discovered the funniest thing in the world. Her eyes were locked onto the divine runic symbol in the person’s hand.

Lin Ming’s vision was keen. He was immediately able to see the ‘Lin’ character marking the bottom right of the divine runic symbol. Indeed, it was one of the Lin logo divine runic symbols, and also the extremely expensive Heavenly Fire Symbol too. He couldn’t help but smile a little upon seeing this.

It seemed that these Lin logo divine runic symbols had spread to the upper levels of the Asura Road. The one who bought the Heavenly Fire Symbols was Empyrean Lionheart, but Empyrean Lionheart’s sect wasn’t experiencing war anytime soon, so it was possible for them to sell a portion of the divine runic symbols to others.

Then again, Lin Ming had produced just over a thousand of these specialized fifth grade divine runic symbols. If a person was able to possess one then they should have some status in their large influence, otherwise it simply wouldn’t be their turn to wield it.

Rumble rumble rumble! The divine runic symbol smashed into the cave tunnels.

There was a continuous blast of explosions echoing from within. Flames soared to the heavens and all of the soil and rock around the cave was instantly melted by the high temperatures.

Sharp shrieks sounded out. A number of figures fled from the burning cave, their bodies blackened. These creatures had thick tails extending from their backs and had bodies similar to a person’s, but their appearance was like a beast.

As these strange beast creatures appeared, runes began to shine on their foreheads. They rushed towards the person that used the Heavenly Fire Symbol, a beam of black lightning shooting out from between their eyebrows towards the two people.

“Shit!”

The trial challenger who held the Lin symbol was angered. Just as he was about to use the Heavenly Fire Symbol in his hand yet again, his companion stopped him. “Don’t be in a hurry, we must save it.”

The fierceness of the Heavenly Fire Symbol lay in the fact that even if a martial artist were at their weakest state, completely exhausted of strength, using the Heavenly Fire Symbol would still result in an all-out attack that remained the same no matter what condition the martial artist was in.

They definitely had to save this divine runic symbol as much as they could to use in critical moments to preserve their lives.

Bang!

With an explosive sound, the black light emitted by the monsters fell onto the ground, causing a dreadful eruption of power.

And as this violent fluctuation of energy shook the mountain, more and more monsters began emerging from all over!

The aura of these monsters was actually at the peak Holy Lord realm! One or two of these monsters wasn’t scary, but with dozens of them gathered together, that was truly horrifying!

In particular, the black light these monsters shot out could gather together and produce an effect of locking down space. These black lights were like a giant spider web, making it so that the two martial artists couldn’t escape even if they wanted to.

“We must last until Senior-apprentice Brother arrives!”

Even facing such a dangerous situation, the disciple who spoke wasn’t afraid at all. Rather, he put forth over 10 array discs and used these array discs to battle these monsters.

As for his companion, he wasn’t weak either. He pulled out his sword, displaying fierce and swift sword skills, perfectly coordinating his attacks!

It was clear that those people who had the qualifications to enter the final trial were all extraordinary.

At this time, a keening howl echoed out, as if something was flying towards them and tearing apart the atmosphere as it did. The two martial artists turned and were immediately overjoyed. “Senior-apprentice Brother has arrived!”

Lin Ming and the others turned towards the sound and saw someone rapidly flying towards them. Lin Ming frowned as he did. Really, enemies crossed paths far too often. This person was none other than Duke Fullmoon!

After entering the final trial’s first level, because they triggered trap array formations, the disciples of Divine Void Divine Kingdom were transmitted to separate areas. But they were truly incredible individuals. Even though they were split apart they were able to pass the first level of the trial and arrive at the second level.

As soon as they entered the second level they were able to use all sorts of methods to contact their companions. The two disciples who were surrounded by the monsters were subordinates of Divine Void Divine Kingdom’s Nine Nether Province; they were fellow disciples of Duke Fullmoon.

“It’s that fellow again, he keeps on haunting us like ghosts!” Xiao Moxian gnashed her teeth, thinking over multiple ways she could try to put Duke Fullmoon to death in this final trial mystic realm.

“Senior-apprentice Brother!” As the two disciples were overjoyed, at this time, some of the monsters that surrounded them began rushing towards Duke Fullmoon!

These monsters were all bloodthirsty to the point of craziness. Before Duke Fullmoon attacked they had already taken the initiative!

“Che!”

Duke Fullmoon immediately slowed down before coming to a stop in the air. Face these twenty some monsters, he frowned, hesitating somewhat.

He could see that these monsters were difficult to deal with. Even for him, they would be a great deal of trouble.

He began considering whether or not acting to save these two junior-apprentice brothers would harm himself. If the risk was too great then he would rather turn tail and run.

But at this time, Duke Fullmoon discovered Lin Ming’s existence.

Lin Ming and his group were far too obvious. In their haste when they rushed over they had only restrained their auras and hadn’t set up a concealment array formation, thus Duke Fullmoon had detected them.

“It’s you!?”

After noticing Lin Ming, Duke Fullmoon was stunned. He clearly didn’t expect to see Lin Ming here.

In a spark of lightning, the 20 some monsters had already reached less than a thousand feet in front of Duke Fullmoon.

Duke Fullmoon maniacally grinned. “The road to heaven you choose not to walk, but the gates of hell you would rush through!”

Without further ado, Duke Fullmoon took these monsters chasing after him and rushed towards Lin Ming!

His plan was clear; it was to drag Lin Ming down with him and have him share in the pressure of dealing with these monsters.

If possible, he would even look for a chance to use these monsters to kill Lin Ming or at least severely wound him. At that time, although he might not be able to obtain Lin Ming’s divine runic arts inheritances, he could still obtain the other secrets on his body.

“This damned bastard!”

Xiao Moxian was enraged. This Duke Fullmoon was cunning enough. The area he was flying in was from their rear; this just happened to trap Lin Ming and the others between the monsters!

Chapter 1676 – The Gate of Laws

Blue light shined on the vast wilderness. Ice flowers and snow plums grew everywhere…

Soul Empress Sheng Mei fell upon the largest snow lotus. Her slender feet were like a butterfly, her lithe body seeming to have no weight.

“Soul Empress!”

The happy Duke Fullmoon hurriedly bowed, his face full of attentiveness.

What kind of character was Soul Empress Sheng Mei? Even Soul Emperor Divine Void had to treat her with respect. It could even be said that she was an existence on the same level as Soul Emperor Divine Void!

In front of Soul Empress Sheng Mei, Duke Fullmoon was nothing more than a little ant. For Sheng Mei to personally rescue him, Duke Fullmoon felt extremely flattered.

Sheng Mei didn’t look at Duke Fullmoon. Rather, she faintly glanced over at Lin Ming’s direction.

Within the space distortion, Lin Ming frowned. This woman was terrifying beyond description. Without a doubt, the five of them combined together wouldn’t be her match.

Lin Ming hesitated for a moment and then lifted the barrier of Heaven’s Divide. Towards this dreadful person, a barrier on this level wasn’t any different from paper.

As he looked at Sheng Mei, he was put under a dreadful pressure!

He couldn’t see this woman’s strength at all!

Sheng Mei stared deeply into Lin Ming’s eyes. A strange color appeared within her smoky eyes.

“You… what is your name?”

Sheng Mei suddenly asked for Lin Ming’s name. This caused Lin Ming to feel a sudden chill cross his body. It had to be known that within this final trial that was filled with numerous young elites, he was extremely common and unnoticeable. Beside those people who participated in the Divine Rune City Auction during that eventful year as well as those who kept up with news about the divine runic arts, very few people bothered paying attention to Lin Ming.

The Divine Void Third Crown Prince and Bigflame, the direct disciple of Divine Emperor Heaven Union, were both the leads of this final trial.

But even these two leads weren’t able to enter Soul Empress Sheng Mei’s eyes.

Yet, currently, Sheng Mei had taken the initiative to ask Lin Ming for his name. This was similar to a human asking an ant for their name. Lin Ming couldn’t help but keep his mind and heart vigilant about this change in events.

He took a deep breath, suppressing the turbulent thoughts in his heart and calmly saying, “My name is Lin Ming!”

Sheng Mei softly hummed. “Your soul is quite special; it is a bit like a special soul physique recorded in the Holy Scripture of my people. But what a pity, you are nothing but a human so your soul is destined to only be alike. If you were a spiritas then I might have accepted you as my disciple…”

As Sheng Mei spoke, she lightly smiled. This was a smile of pure appreciation. But as this smile fell into Lin Ming’s eyes, his heart shook!

Special soul physique recorded in the Holy Scripture!?

Was it… the Magic Cube!?

Lin Ming remembered that the second time he had seen Empyrean Divine Mist, he had said that there was an ancient text which existed within the spiritas legends – the Spiritas Holy Scripture. Within the Spiritas Holy Scripture, the existence of the Magic Cube had been recorded – it was known as the Stone of Eternal Life.

When Sheng Mei had mentioned the Holy Scripture, it was 99% likely that it was the Spiritas Holy Scripture that Empyrean Divine Mist had mentioned. Was this so-called special soul physique spoken of within the Holy Scriptures also related to the Magic Cube?

In that moment, Lin Ming could feel a cold sweat dripping from his palms!

Luckily, even this terrifying woman in front of him didn’t realize the existence of the Magic Cube in his inner world.

Perhaps because Lin Ming had possessed the Magic Cube for such a long time, his soul might have been subtly influenced by the Magic Cube. This made Sheng Mei mistake Lin Ming’s soul for having some similarities to the special soul physique recorded in the Spiritas Holy Scripture.

This sort of soul was named the Eternal Soul. The rarity of such a thing couldn’t be described with words!

Compared to that, Xiao Moxian’s half God Beast bloodline was nothing at all. Although a half God Beast physique was rare, it wasn’t strange for it to occur every billion years in a universe. But as for the Eternal Soul recorded in the Spiritas Holy Scripture, it hadn’t appeared in the entire 33 Heavens for several great calamities in a row.

Thus, Sheng Mei only casually spoke. She would never believe that a human like Lin Ming would possess the Eternal Soul that was mentioned in the legends of the spiritas, something that had already vanished from existence 10 billion years ago.

However, after hearing Sheng Mei’s words, Duke Fullmoon felt an intense surge of jealousy.

This was clearly the first time that Sheng Mei had seen Lin Ming, but she had actually said that she would accept Lin Ming as a disciple if he were a spiritas!

Duke Fullmoon knew that Sheng Mei was a person whose heart was higher than the heavens. In her entire life she had never received a disciple, much less a male disciple!

If Duke Fullmoon could become Sheng Mei’s disciple, he would even be willing to sacrifice half his lifespan!

But after she appeared, she didn’t even bother glancing at someone like Duke Fullmoon who was on ‘her’ side, but had instead spoken to an ‘outsider’ like Lin Ming. This caused Duke Fullmoon to feel somewhat ill.

Lin Ming was only a human, so why?

Lin Ming’s divine runic arts were fierce but to someone on the level of Sheng Mei, what meaning did the divine runic arts have?

As Duke Fullmoon was depressed, Lin Ming stood rigidly on the ground. His inner world’s fluctuations had been reduced to their lowest levels, and even as he maintained absolute vigilance he kept his appearance as calm as he could.

Then, Sheng Mei finally turned, about to leave.

Lin Ming’s mind relaxed a little. To him, every second felt like a year. He was looking forwards to this terrifying woman disappearing as hastily as she came.

But then, Duke Fullmoon called out to Sheng Mei.

“Soul Empress!”

Duke Fullmoon summoned the courage to say. Lin Ming was nervous as he heard this. He really wanted to just kill this damned idiot and get him over with.

“What is it…”

Sheng Mei turned her head and glanced at Duke Fullmoon.

Seeing Sheng Mei’s cold eyes on him, Duke Fullmoon suddenly felt weak at the knees. He gulped and stuttered out, “T-those people over there, they…”

For a time, Duke Fullmoon was at a loss for words. There was no way he could ask Sheng Mei to help him kill Lin Ming, but he wasn’t willing to miss such an opportunity.

Sheng Mei faintly frowned. “You aren’t asking me to handle your grudges for you… are you?”

Sheng Mei could immediately see that Duke Fullmoon had a grudge with Lin Ming and the others.

“No… I wouldn’t dare!” Duke Fullmoon quickly denied. Just what status did he have? He was already thanking the heavens and earth that Sheng Mei had saved him. He and Sheng Mei weren’t even from the same influence, so what qualifications did he have to ask her to help him take revenge?

As for using the secrets on Lin Ming’s body to tempt Sheng Mei, Duke Fullmoon didn’t know whether these supposed secrets really existed or not.

He only thought that Lin Ming was far too young to have such extraordinary skill in divine runic arts. As for what was going on with Lin Ming, Duke Fullmoon couldn’t say it clearly himself.

To the influences within the Asura Road, the greatest value that Lin Ming possessed was to draw up divine runic symbols and create a massive amount of wealth. But, what lure did wealth have to someone like Sheng Mei, whose status was similar to a True Divinity level character?

It was likely there was nothing on Lin Ming’s body that could tempt Sheng Mei.

As Duke Fullmoon was lost in thought, Sheng Mei had already floated away. Left behind, Duke Fullmoon watched Sheng Mei’s parting back with an ugly complexion.

He looked at Lin Ming and Lin Ming looked at him.

Duke Fullmoon had three people on his side; Lin Ming had five.

As their eyes met in midair, sparks flashed between them, followed by surging killing intent!

They each wanted to kill the other!

At this time, Lin Ming was considering what his chances were of killing Duke Fullmoon in a situation where he couldn’t sneak attack him. And, would Duke Fullmoon’s other squad members catch up? And most importantly of all, Lin Ming didn’t know about how Soul Empress Sheng Mei would take this. Was she planning on guaranteeing the lives of Divine Void Divine Kingdom’s disciples in this smelting trial?

All of these doubts made it so that Lin Ming didn’t attack.

As for Duke Fullmoon, he dreaded the many divine runic symbols Lin Ming had on him, as well as the several companions with him.

“You little bastard, consider yourself lucky!” Duke Fullmoon sneered. “You think you can do whatever you want just because of some divine runic symbols? You should remember to save them as much as you can and not use them all up, because if that happens I will kill you as easily as butchering a dog or a chicken!”

“Really, aren’t you afraid that the wind will cut your tongue with your constant babbling? I’m confused, just which family was so lazy as to forget to tie up your chain. As a dog, you should have the awareness of a dog. Just who do you think you are? If it weren’t for the Soul Empress appearing just now you would have already died.” Xiao Moxian had never been someone who was willing to lose in a war of words. As Duke Fullmoon started cursing at Lin Ming, she immediately opposed him.

“Heh, you bitch, aren’t you Lin Ming’s woman? I will soon make you regret choosing this kind of man. At that time… you might even enjoy it.”

Duke Fullmoon lecherously smiled before he turned and left.

The two other disciples of Divine Void Divine Kingdom hurriedly followed behind, keeping a close tab on their surroundings.

Seeing the three people about to vanish, Mo Brightmoon felt her sword blade. She frowned, “Are we going to let them leave like this?”

“Just this time.” Lin Ming indifferently said. Duke Fullmoon was already on his kill list. It was just that there were too many variables involved so he hadn’t attacked.

…………

After the brief battle just now, Lin Ming’s squad continued forwards carefully.

If they could avoid the monsters on the second floor they would avoid them. They tried to keep the battles to a bare minimum.

Like this, they went deeper and deeper into the wilderness. And the deeper they went, the thicker the chaotic energy in the skies became.

In the endless distance, they could vaguely see the appearance of a massive metal door, like a mountain range that stretched to the ends of time.

Waves of profound and quiet runes scattered out from the metal door. They were incomparably vast and mysterious.

Seeing these metal doors that constantly emitted a golden light, Mo Brightmoon’s eyes flashed, a strange color covering them.

“The Gate of Laws… according to the information I purchased before, this is the entrance to the third level. The Gate of Laws that leads to the third level is particularly special…”

“Oh? Special?” Lin Ming stopped and asked, startled.

“That’s right. Starting from the Gate of Laws, the disparity between the different martial artists in the final trial will be pulled even further apart… the strong will be better, obtaining even higher points and better rewards. As for the weak, they will be directly eliminated.”

Mo Brightmoon said, a restless anticipation in her eyes. With her own level of talent, what sort of scene would she see when passing through the Gate of Laws…?

Chapter 1677 – Difficulty and Completion Percentage

As Lin Ming walked towards the Gate of Laws, increasingly powerful auras appeared one after another. The powerhouses that had completed the first level and were scattered over the world of the second level began coverging towards the Gate of Laws.

These people were all extraordinary disciples of their large influences. After passing through the fierce battles of the first and second floor, not too many of them perished. Only some extremely unlucky martial artists who had been surrounded by monsters had died.

“It’s that fellow, the whatever Crown Prince from Divine Void Divine Kingdom is coming!”

Xiao Moxian suddenly commented as they neared the Gate of Laws. Lin Ming looked back to see several men and women wearing feather robes with star crowns on their heads. They were surrounding a young man wearing a dragon crown with his hair hanging loose around him. This young man stood atop the head of a silver python that was as large as a mountain. The silver python twisted as it moved forwards, leaving deep gullies in the earth.

This young man was dashing and high-spirited, showing disdain for all heroes.

He was the Divine Void Third Crown Prince!

As the Divine Void Third Crown Prince appeared, so did Duke Fullmoon.

At this time, Duke Fullmoon was flying high in the air as he followed behind the Third Crown Prince. There was a faint smile on his face as he looked towards the people up ahead with a commanding gaze.

The other disciples of Divine Void Divine Kingdom didn’t dare to stand upon the head of this giant silver python. This silver python was the contract beast of the Third Crown Prince. It was an arrogant beast that didn’t allow anyone else besides its master to ride it.

Although this silver python wasn’t a God Beast, it had an ancient bloodline relationship with a God Beast. It was said that if this silver python was able to grow four feet and grow horns atop its head, it would evolve into a silver dragon. Of course, the road to that path was beset with difficulties and the chances of it happening were impossibly low.

And at this time, a phoenix-like cry spread through the air. Brilliant waves of flames rolled up in the skies as a massive phoenix-looking firebird appeared. Just by flying, this firebird filled the skies with raging flames, immediately causing the temperature of the surroundings to become boiling hot.

On the back of this firebird was a fat youth wearing a bright yellow five-clawed dragon robe. This fat youth was Bigflame, the direct disciple of Heaven Union Divine Kingdom’s Divine Emperor.

The Divine Void Third Crown Prince, Bigflame, the top disciples of the True Divinity influences had arrived.

“Bigflame, you arrived here quite fast. I thought perhaps your luck might be worse than I thought and that you could be surrounded by the monsters here. If that were to happen, your fat body would disappear…”

The Third Crown Prince taunted as he saw Bigflame show up.

“Haha! I must thank the Crown Prince for worrying over me. When I arrived I was indeed frightened miserable. Luckily, I managed to somehow stumble my way over here. How could I compare to someone as peerlessly wise and skilled as Crown Prince your highness? You could likely lay down on the floor and still arrive here. Ah, that’s right, at this Gate of Laws, does the peerlessly wise and skilled Crown Prince plan on challenging the heaven-step difficulty level?” Bigflame’s words were kind and subservient, but if one wasn’t an idiot they could clearly hear the taunting within them.

The Divine Void Crown Prince frowned as he heard these words.

He knew that the most important part of Bigflame’s words was at the end. Bigflame wanted him to challenge the heaven-step difficulty of the Gate of Laws!

The final trial’s Gate of Laws was extremely special. Before this, all trial challengers were placed together and could pass levels in groups. But at the Gate of Laws, every person would be separated and also had to choose their difficulty.

No matter what difficulty they chose, as long as they passed through the Gate of Laws they would reach the third level.

What was different was that the higher the difficulty one chose at the Gate of Laws, the better the rewards would be and the higher the completion percentage would be.

Of course, this also meant greater dangers!

Every difficulty was divided into four possibilities – perfect completion, partial completion, barely passing, and death.

If one perfectly completed their difficulty, their rewards would be higher and the final trial completion percentage would be higher!

At partial completion, rewards and completion percentage would be reduced.

As for barely passing, there wouldn’t be any reward and the given completion percentage would also be the lowest. Still, they would be able to safely enter the third level.

As for death, there was no need to mention it. It was the worst result in the Gate of Laws, where one perished within!

The heaven-step difficulty was one of the highest levels of difficulty within the Gate of Laws.

Since ancient times, countless proud children of heaven had participated in the final trial. But, those that dared to choose the heaven-step difficulty were extremely rare!

As for those who had chosen it, there had never been anyone who had managed to perfectly complete it. Just partially completing it and surviving through the end was an extraordinary result!

Although the Divine Void Crown Prince was arrogant, he was well aware of his own abilities. He estimated that if he chose the heaven-step difficulty, the most he could do was just barely pass it or only complete a small percentage of it.

Although he would likely be able to reach the third level, the completion percentage would be too low and the rewards wouldn’t be too great either. Moreover, he would also have to risk a high chance of dying there. Who would be willing to do something so stupid?

This Bigflame was clearly trying to stir him up with dark intentions in his mind. The Divine Void Crown Prince wasn’t an idiot so why would he fall for such an obvious ploy?

Instead, he sneered and mockingly said, “I have self-awareness of my own abilities. I naturally do not have the skill to challenge the heaven-step difficulty, but I am more than capable of playing in the earth-step difficulty. If Brother Bigflame is so proud of your own skills, then you should certainly try the heaven-step difficulty yourself, haha!”

The Divine Void Crown Prince’s voice was extremely loud. At this time, before the Gate of Laws, many disciples of large influences had gathered and they were all looking at him.

These people knew that Bigflame and the Third Crown Prince already had a gambling bet between themselves. Now, in front of the Gate of Laws, they were still stood in sharp opposition!

“Hehe, how interesting, two descendants from True Divinity level influences are trying to provoke each other into entering the heaven-step difficulty of the Gate of Laws.”

Not too far away, many people were watching the fun play.

“They’re just messing around and trying to one-up each other. They both know that trying to provoke the other party won’t have any effect. With their strength, they might be able to perfectly complete the earth-step difficulty, but as for the heaven-step difficulty, just forget about it!”

As these people were speaking, their discussions naturally fell into Lin Ming’s ears.

As he listened to these people speak and in addition to the explanation that Mo Brightmoon had given him, Lin Ming already had a rough understanding of the Gate of Laws.

When choosing a difficulty in the Gate of Laws, it was best to choose one that could be perfectly completed. In that way, one would have the greatest harvests. At the very worst, one had to choose a difficulty at which they could at least achieve 90% or above.

As Lin Ming was thinking this, a sudden sound of footsteps left him feeling icy cold!

In front of the Gate of Laws he could see a blue-clothed woman floating high in the air. Her body seemed to merge with her surroundings, making it difficult to notice her existence.

Lin Ming could confirm that just a moment ago, this blue-clothed woman hadn’t been there. But now, she had suddenly emerged in the skies above, as if she had teleported there.

“Soul Empress!”

As the blue-clothed woman appeared, the Divine Void Crown Prince quickly hurried forwards to greet her. In front of her, he didn’t show any arrogance at all. He had already witnessed the attitude with which Soul Emperor Divine Void had treated her.

Sheng Mei faintly looked over at the Third Crown Prince and slightly bowed.

As for the previously flagrant Bigflame, he had no intention of moving forwards. Instead, he looked on from the distance, utterly silent.

Bigflame knew that in the 33 Heavens, the saints were at war with the spiritas! As a saint from the Asura Road, he wouldn’t be sucked up into their affairs. Even so, it was likely that this Sheng Mei didn’t have any good impressions of him at all. It was best to hide away as much as possible.

“Who is that blue-clothed woman? Why would the Third Crown Prince be so respectful to her?”

Because Sheng Mei kept a low profile, many martial artists didn’t recognize her. As they saw that even the Third Crown Prince was bowing to her, they were stunned.

“Don’t you know who she is? Haven’t you heard that several years ago in the Divine Void Divine Kingdom, there was a grown Ice Phoenix that descended upon their land, even forcing Soul Emperor Divine Void out of his seclusion? And that woman is the person who arrived on that Ice Phoenix! She is the one who holds the record for the highest completion percentage, 83%! I heard that for these last several years she has been staying at Divine Void Divine Kingdom and her status is on par with that of Soul Emperor Divine Void!”

“What!? This… the record of the highest completion percentage? Isn’t she the one that already obtained a completion rate of 83%? Why would she come to the Asura Road’s final trial again? Isn’t that just a waste of qualifications?”

Many people asked, puzzled. The Asura Road was simply far too large. Even if Sheng Mei had caused a giant stir in Divine Void Divine Kingdom, many people still hadn’t heard of her.

“Hehe, it’s not as simple as you think!” The one who spoke before mysteriously said. He began to whisper in a cryptic tone, “If she came again, then she naturally believes 83% is not her limit! This mysterious spiritas woman has an extremely unique cultivation method, one that makes her talent grow stronger and stronger. She has already surpassed all common logic!”

“What!?” Many martial artists looked at each other in fear. 83% wasn’t her limit?

Then what degree would she reach?

As for a cultivation method that constantly increased one’s talent, they had never heard of that before.

“This kind of cultivation method exists?”

“I’ve only heard rumors about it. Moreover, this blue-clothed woman’s cultivation is far too confusing. Some people say she is an early Empyrean and some people say she is an ordinary World King; it's as if her cultivation is always changing. But, one point is for certain is that whether she is an Empyrean or World King, she can easily pinch us to death without any effort at all. Although we are standing here with her, the truth is that we are on completely different levels. In her eyes, we are nothing more than ants!”

The martial artist who spoke deeply sighed. Everyone here was a proud child of the heavens. In their own large sects and families, they were heroic figures that stood at the peak of their generation. But here, they were actually considered to be no more than ants. No matter what, this left them feeling uncomfortable.

However, they had to acknowledge the truth. This spiritas woman stood on par with Soul Emperor Divine Void, with no inferiority or superiority between them. And, Soul Emperor Divine Void was a True Divinity supreme elder. As for the rest of them, they already considered it the highest honor to have an Empyrean praise them a few times. The disparity between them could be imagined!

As all of this talk fell into Lin Ming’s ears, he lost himself in thought for a moment. He had some faint ideas about this spiritas woman.

In the past, when he first entered the Asura Road, he had heard Soulwhite mention that in the last 100 million years, there had been two people who had obtained an 80% completion rate and above – the Good Fortune Saint Son and a mysterious spiritas woman.

Lin Ming thought that the Good Fortune Saint Son and the mysterious spiritas woman were the greatest geniuses of their race’s youths.

But now, it seemed that he had misunderstood everything. This mysterious spiritas woman was not some junior, but a high level figure of the soul race!

Chapter 1681 – The Narrow Road

After Lin Ming severely wounded the White Tiger phantom, a wisp of blood red aura from the Great Dao appeared in Lin Ming’s sea of consciousness.

This aura slowly fused together with his flesh and blood, merging with his awareness.

“This is…” Lin Ming was startled. When he damaged the White Tiger phantom just now, a bit of the power and Laws contained within it had converged into Lin Ming’s body, allowing him to become aware of many more things.

It seemed that even though this Gate of Laws was filled with death and slaughter, it also represented a lucky chance.

“In this place I might be able to temper my understandings of the Heavenly Dao Laws… the source strength of a God Beast’s Heavenly Dao, that is a rare chance…”

Lin Ming thought to himself, his mind calming down. On the thin aerial bridge, the strong heavenly winds rocked against him, but his heart remained as steady as a mountain. Then, at this time, the giant Azure Dragon in front of Lin Ming roared towards him, its deep blue Azure Dragon aura hurtling into Lin Ming.

The moment that the Asura Dragon attacked, the surrounding scene turned into that of an endless sea. The Azure Dragon raged above it, all-powerful, an existence swollen with arrogance.

The more Lin Ming fought, the more his blood boiled over. He opened the two Dao Palaces within his body and wildly revolved the Heretical God Force. Underneath the support of his brutal strength, Lin Ming was like an ancient vicious beast as he crashed onto the back of the Azure Dragon!

Billions of jins of dreadful strength came pounding down. The Azure Dragon howled out in pain and misery as it was sent flying away. Lin Ming stepped forwards, chasing after it!

For the current Lin Ming, because he had opened two Dao Palaces, his body transformation technique had become his strongest attack method. On the other hand, his essence gathering system lagged behind.

Strike after strike, Lin Ming’s spear potential was endless and majestic. It came crashing down like mountains, unstoppable.

Lin Ming rode upon the Azure Dragon, violently struggling with it in a wild barrage of attacks. However, it was only a God Beast phantom and was unable to withstand Lin Ming’s onslaught.

For a time, blue scales shattered as blood rained down over the earth!

Lin Ming had slaughtered the Azure Dragon in a life or death struggle!

Thus, of the four God Beast phantoms, two had disappeared. The remaining shattered grand array was far less threatening to Lin Ming. Lin Ming became fiercer the more he fought, soon killing all of the God Beast phantoms!

After massacring all of the God Beasts, Lin Ming’s entire body was bathed in blood. His arms and his body shivered. This was the side-effect of overdrawing his strength in physical combat, but also because of the bubbling excitement from the battle!

With a deep breath, Lin Ming slowly calmed down his heated blood and thoughts. At this time, on the aerial bridge the terrifying pressure was still as dreadful as before, without the slightest hint of diminishing. Rather, after Lin Ming broke through the God Beast Grand Array, this pressure became far more powerful!

Underneath this terrifying pressure, an ordinary martial artist would find it difficult to breathe, much less continue fighting.

“This pressure hasn’t decreased… it seems I have to adapt to the pressure in the Gate of Laws, it might follow me throughout this entire trial. If I cannot adapt to it then sooner or later I won’t be able to withstand it anymore and I’ll be defeated from this alone.”

As Lin Ming was thinking this, he sat down in meditation.

Just now, Lin Ming had torn apart the Four God Beast Grand Array, and the four God Beast phantoms had been overflowing with the aura of Laws. This was marvelously similar to the God Beast Array in Tragic Death Valley, even though the methods were different.

After breaking apart the array formation, the source Heavenly Dao Laws of these God Beasts had scattered into the air. This was the perfect time to meditate and perceive these God Beast Laws.

God Beasts were the favored children of the heavens. Runes of the Great Dao were inscribed into their flesh and bones, an incomparably mysterious miracle of nature.

Lin Ming began to adapt to the terrifying pressure on this aerial bridge even as he absorbed the power of the God Beast Laws!

Since the Gate of Laws had the word ‘Laws’ in its name, Lin Ming guessed that the ‘Laws’ themselves were part of the rewards from this trial!

When ordinary people entered the Gate of Laws, who wouldn’t do everything in their ability to pass it as quickly as possible while obtaining a perfect completion? There wasn’t anyone as insane as Lin Ming who would think of training atop this thin aerial bridge underneath the pall of such a terrifying pressure.

Of course, the reason Lin Ming dared to do this was because of his formidable strength as well as his comprehensions of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws.

This was also the origin of his confidence.

Lin Ming was a quiet old tree, motionlessly sitting on the aerial bridge. Strong heavenly winds blew around him, causing the bridge to gently tremble. Like this, he meditated for three days and three nights.

From start to end, the pressure on the aerial bridge hadn’t faded even the tiniest bit. But, Lin Ming adapted more and more to it. Beneath this pressure, Lin Ming’s muscles and bloodline were tempered, his entire body undergoing subtle and minute changes.

Where there was pressure, there would naturally be resistance. In these three days, all of Lin Ming’s cells swallowed energy to resist this heavy pressure. As every single cell within Lin Ming’s body was being tempered, he adapted more and more to the terrifying pressure in the Gate of Laws! Lin Ming’s essence, energy, and divine, all expanded.

Gradually, Lin Ming was shrouded in a fog of substantialized spiritual power.

Finally, his eyes flashed open, his pupils shining with purple lightning. His aura was like a sword that shot into the skies.

With a leap upwards, the world momentum that flooded the aerial bridge, covering this entire land in billowing waves of pressure, was broken through by Lin Ming like a fish swimming against a river. Lin Ming’s feet landed solidly on the aerial bridge as he hurtled forwards at a breakneck pace!

To run forwards under this terrifying pressure, the pressure that Lin Ming had to withstand could be imagined.

However, after opening two Dao Palaces Lin Ming had a body that could withstand all of this. Soon, the boundless aerial bridge beneath his feet disappeared and Lin Ming entered a new and strange world.

In front of him was a vast white light.

High in the skies, he could make out an impossibly large continent floating in space, one that exuded a primeval and vibrant aura.

Rumbling winds crashed about like peals of thunder, echoing out from all directions.

A boundless aura constantly poured down from this ancient floating continent.

Lin Ming was well aware that the world of the final trial was the carefully created masterpiece of the Asura Road Master. Every single inch of this world contained endless profound meanings.

Thinking of this, Lin Ming jumped straight into the skies like a rising meteor, pouncing onto the ancient continent.

Peng!

After he landed on the ancient continent that floated 100,000 feet in the air, Lin Ming looked around.

This place was not what he imagined. Atop this ancient continent, there were actually endless numbers of golden gates.

These golden gates were as large as mountains; it was difficult to see their edges. He could only sense an incomparably vigorous atmosphere exuding from them, like the titanic pressure of a spiritual god.

The aura from every golden gate was like a torrential tide, crashing into Lin Ming’s heart and mind. This caused every nerve in his body to be alert for danger, his entire body shaking.

“Just what is in them?”

Lin Ming had trained in martial arts for many years and his heart and will were as solid as a rock. But in front of these giant gates, even he was panic-stricken. In ordinary times, only the aura emitted from an Empyrean level powerhouse would create such a pressure on him.

At this time, every golden gate emitted a brilliant golden light that covered Lin Ming.

Like being caught by countless hands, Lin Ming felt every wisp of golden light searching his entire body.

He was like a helpless little baby, completely exposed beneath this endless golden light.

Immediately, the light coming from the golden gates dimmed down, suddenly turning silver.

At the same time, there were also changes in the vividly dangerous auras exuding from the golden gates. The auras became much stranger, far more ghostly. Then, one of the golden gates opened and an icy cold aura filled the air.

Lin Ming knew that perhaps this gate was the entrance to the second part of this trial. As he remained vigilant of everything around him, he carefully stepped inside.

Hu - !

Snow and ice filled the world, sweeping in from all directions, carrying with it an icy coldness that seeped into the bones.

The skies were cloudy and gray, piling up in the heavens, seeming as if they were made from ashes.

Trees, rivers, and even the endless mountain ranges around him were covered in sheets of frozen snow and ice.

After Lin Ming broke into the second Dao Palace of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace – the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace, his mortal body had reached unprecedented levels of intensity. There were few humans in the last billion years that possessed bodies comparable to his own.

By raising his hand, he could shatter a moon.

And yet, even with such a powerful mortal body, he could feel an icy chill needling into his flesh, piercing into his blood vessels and bones, and seeping into his organs.

Suddenly, an ice mountain a mile away began to crack and collapse. An even more dreadful cold atmosphere gushed out from that shattering ice mountain.

An icy cold aura rushed towards Lin Ming, like an incoming ice-white tsunami on a frozen sea…

But Lin Ming didn’t sense this.

At this time, there had already been some people who had passed the Gate of Laws.

Those who passed through the Gate of Laws first were the trial challengers who had chosen the easiest difficulty.

Amongst them, many only used a little more than three days to walk to the end of the Gate of Laws and smoothly reach the third level…

Chapter 1682 – Reward

“We passed! We’ve made it to the third level!”

The first batch of trial challengers had successfully passed the Gate of Laws and had reached the third level. They were immediately overjoyed.

“It’s not hard at all!”

“Haha, if I knew this earlier I would have chosen the earth-step difficulty, I estimate that I could have passed that one too!”

A young elite arrogantly proclaimed. The trial challengers that selected the easiest difficulty had mostly perfectly completed their trial. Before, because they had taken too many factors into consideration, they hadn’t dared to choose the harder difficulty. But now, because they had perfectly passed their trial they couldn’t help but develop ideas that they could have chosen a higher difficulty.

As they were all excitedly discussing, they also looked at the scenery of the third level. As they saw their surroundings, they looked at each other in confusion.

The final trial’s third floor was simply a vast white earth, seeming to stretch to infinity and beyond. It didn’t seem like there was anything special here nor were there any dangers.

But, floating in the skies above this white earth were innumerable immortal palaces!

These immortal palaces came in different sizes The smallest were the size of a mortal house, the medium ones were around the size of a royal palace, the larger ones were around the size of large mountains, and the biggest one was even the size of a small planet!

Moreover, the larger an immortal palace was, the more horrifying the aura it exuded. In particular, the immortal palace that was as large as a planet was engraved with countless runes of the Great Dao. Between these endless runes were also reliefs of God Beasts. There were winding Azure Dragons, Phoenixes in nirvana, Kirins running; their numbers and variety were endless.

These reliefs were also covered with runes, all of them giving off an incredibly shocking feeling. It was like there was some spiritual god living within this immortal palace!

From looks alone, one could guess that the largest immortal palace must have some great mystery within it!

“What place is this? Are these immortal palaces the test…?”

Many young elites asked in a daze as they saw the immortal palaces above them. They had an urge to fly up and investigate these immortal palaces.

“This isn’t a test, but the reward! Within every immortal palace is a lucky chance. In the third level of the final trial, there is no danger, only rewards!”

Someone amongst the young elites said. He had a detailed understanding of what generally occurred in the final trial.

The final trial didn’t have dangers on every level. Some levels were designated as reward zones and also to allow trial challengers a place to rest. The third level was such an example.

“Rewards!?”

Hearing this word, the eyes of many heroic young elites began to shine!

Rewards of the final trial, this was no trifling matter!

“Haha, we are the first group of people to pass the Gate of Laws. First come, first serve!”

“Haha, our gains are too great!”

These young elites glanced at each other and then flew upwards like a swarm of locusts. Their speed was quick as they flew towards the largest planet-sized immortal palace in the air.

Even an idiot would understand that the largest immortal palace with the most terrifying aura would also possess the best lucky chances!

Thinking of the legends of many lucky chances related to the final trial, all of their eyes turned red with greed. They rushed up as fast as they could, even ready to slaughter each other to get to their destination.

The martial artists in the front of the pack didn’t hesitate to use secret techniques to hasten their flight. As they saw the great and mysterious immortal palace became closer and closer, they nearly drooled!

However, just as they were about to rush into the immortal palace, all of them cried out in pain and misery. Their bodies had been severely wounded!

They had all crashed into a wall they couldn’t see!

“Ahhhhh!”

A pitiful scream echoed out in the air. The trial challengers had long gone crazy with greed and had displayed the limits of their speed. Now, before they had time to respond, they all smashed into this invisible barrier!

“Fuck! What happened!?”

Everyone either rubbed their heads or hugged their chests, their breaths ragged.

This immortal palace had been sealed away by an enchantment!

Some martial artists attacked the enchantment. Although they knew they couldn’t break it, they still wanted to give vent to their rage.

However, they didn’t expect that all their attacks would strike the enchantment and then bounce back, slamming into them instead. They all wailed as they were struck, vomiting out blood as they fell down from the skies, nearly killed by their own actions.

“Requirement to enter the immortal palace – 50%!”

In that moment, this thought swiftly passed into the minds of many people.

They were all stunned. What? There was a completion percentage requirement?

They also remembered that after they passed through the Gate of Laws, their completion percent had only been a bit more than 30%. But, this immortal palace required 50%!

They were a little less than half off!

The crowd of trial challengers glanced at each other in blank dismay. They immediately understood that they had no fate with the largest immortal palace.

Although they were depressed, they still rallied their hearts and continued to the next, slightly smaller immortal palace. They had already been taught a good lesson by that mountain-sized immortal palace. This time, they all flew outside the next smaller one and carefully studied the barrier.

After a brief investigation, they discovered that there was a completion requirement of 45%!

All of them were scared silly. They thought that the lucky chances of the third level were first come first serve, but now they discovered that there wasn’t a free meal in this world.

In helpless desperation, they lowered their requests and went to an even smaller immortal palace, one of the ones the size of a mortal’s royal palace. Although they already had a foreboding premonition in their heart, the result still left them feeling pained. The requirements for these palaces were still around 40%! They still couldn’t enter!

All that was left over were the immortal palaces the size of little houses.

These smallest immortal palaces appeared like little thatched huts. Looking at them, one could feel an incomparably thin aura of Laws. Although they were clearly the worst immortal palaces available, they could only choose these.

After a brief investigation, the completion requirements for these small palaces were around 30%. Depending on the strength of their auras, the completion percentage required differed by 3-5%. For these people that had just passed through the Gate of Laws, it was just right.

After discovering this frustrating and despair-inducing reality, many people had faces like a frozen eggplant. All of their previously lofty ambitions and thoughts had wilted away to nothing.

They originally thought they had perfectly passed the Gate of Laws and thus were in good moods. But after arriving on the third level and choosing a reward, they realized they were nothing but garbage in the eyes of the Asura Road Master.

The ‘immortal palaces’ that looked like little thatched huts – could there be anything worse?

In terms of number alone, there were as many of these little tiny immortal palaces as there were grains of sand in a desert. It was without doubt that there would be nothing of high value found within these tiny immortal palaces. Compared to the largest immortal palace that was the size of a small planet, as well as being the only one there was, the disparity was far too great!

However, it was likely that no one would be able to enter the largest immortal palace. As for the slightly worse immortal palace that was the size of a mountain, maybe only an extraordinary genius like Soul Empress Sheng Mei would have the ability to enter…

Thinking of this, everyone felt just a little bit better.

Everyone began to choose immortal palaces that were within their reach and flew in. No matter who it was, after entering the third level, they would only have one chance to choose an immortal palace.

As the first batch of trial challengers to enter the third level began choosing their rewards, Lin Ming was still engaged in a bitter battle within the Gate of Laws.

In the endless frosty white air, there was an over 30 foot high giant whose entire body was covered in an armor of snow and ice. Rocks burst apart on the ground as it moved and the nails on its hands were each five feet long, looking like sharp swords, capable of slicing apart the toughest of defensives. At this time, this frost giant was slashing at Lin Ming.

These sword-like nails of snow and frost cut through the void, even freezing the air and creating visible channels of ice.

The icy chill was concentrated on the sharp edges as they chopped forwards.

Lin Ming’s heart turned cold. Immediately, the long spear in his hands thrust out thousands of times.

Every spear thrust was enough to rip open the void and sweep up giant space storms. The might and momentum of this attack was endless.

At the same time, the power of the Heretical God Tree swelled forth, growing behind Lin Ming. Every leaf blazed with a wisp of seventh level Concept-fused heavenly tribulation fire.

Woosh woosh woosh - !

Over a dozen wisps of heavenly tribulation flames focused on the point of the long spear, causing the entire spear head to suddenly ignite with a raging flame.

Bang!

The spear collided with the freezing air and icy nail-swords of the giant.

A brutal shockwave swept out, causing ripples to rush out in all directions. Terrifying ravines were torn into the ground from the aftermath and shockwaves.

Lin Ming was forced several hard steps back. As for the frost giant, its entire body shook as it was continuously pushed backwards.

Every time the frost giant took a step back, it would leave a deep impression in the ground.

“How strong!” Lin Ming was shocked. This bodily strength of this frost giant was no less than his! This Asura level difficulty of the Gate of Laws was well worth its reputation. It was actually able to create such a freakish monster.

As this frost giant was forced back by Lin Ming, the ice armor on its body cracked in several places and the corners of its mouth bled a creamy white liquid.

As this liquid appeared, the air filled with a strange and wonderful fragrance.

“That seems to be… nine yin ice marrow?”

Chapter 1685 – Three Moves

Time was life. To Lin Ming, these six hours were incomparably precious.

With Lin Ming’s current physical condition he was in an extremely bad situation. His body had innumerable wounds and he was severely exhausted of true essence and blood vitality!

Because of the continuous battles, Lin Ming hadn’t had any time to recover at all. This had left him barely able to sustain himself through the fruits of his battle, supplementing his inner energy with those dozens of types of heavenly materials.

However, which one of these heavenly materials was easy to refine?

Lin Ming didn’t have time to refine them within his body, leading to all sorts of different attributed energies building up within him. This caused all of the energy within his body to turn chaotic!

Now, within the next six short hours, Lin Ming had to refine all of these different types of energy, straighten out his meridians, and restore his blood vitality, all while he transferred energy to heal his wounds. This was a nearly impossible task!

If it were a normal martial artist, then let alone six hours, even three days and three nights wouldn’t be enough time.

Even though Lin Ming had absorbed the blood of a True Dragon and True Phoenix, and even opened two Dao Palaces of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, wanting to accomplish all of this was extremely difficult.

In other words, when the Black Asura had given Lin Ming six hours to recover, he hadn’t intended for Lin Ming to restore himself to his peak condition to begin with.

In that moment, Lin Ming took a deep breath and shut his eyes, completely entering into an ethereal trance-like state.

During his time at Mount Potala, Lin Ming had stepped into the Irreproachable Stupa and entered the extreme pure lands of bliss there. Underneath the shade of a Bodhi tree, he had imitated what the human Empyrean Emperor Shakya had done and meditated for 33 days. In this time, he completely focused the ethereal martial intent, Samsara martial intent, and Primordius martial intent together, mixing them into a singular unified martial intent.

Now, in this crucial moment that concerned Lin Ming’s life or death, he displayed this fused martial intent to enter a completely focused and selfless state!

As Lin Ming sat down, an independent space seemed to form around him, isolating him from the vast wasteland.

Faintly, the phantom of an old tree seemed to appear behind Lin Ming.

This tree was similar to the Heretical God Tree. But, compared to the Heretical God Tree phantom that appeared behind Lin Ming, it was far older and more vigorous. Its bark was cracked open and only several leaves decorated its crown. But every leaf dripped verdant green, glistening with a gem-like brilliance as if it were carved from the most wonderful green jade.

As Lin Ming used his fused martial intent to recover, the phenomenon of a Bodhi Tree appeared behind him. For a time, petals fell around him and the sounds of spirit springs echoed in the air. It was like a separate utopia had developed around Lin Ming.

As the Black Asura saw this scene appear around Lin Ming, a flash of surprise appeared in his icy cold eyes. He had never imagined that Lin Ming, someone who was wrapped in endless infernal energy, someone who violently fought and was bathed in constant blood and slaughter, would have such a tranquil and harmonic martial intent.

Two hours, four hours…

Lin Ming sat within these lands of pure bliss, motionless, like he had cast away all desire and become a Buddha.

Whether it was the Samsara martial intent or ethereal martial intent, both were martial intents that leaned towards the tenants of Buddhism. They perfectly suited Lin Ming’s cultivation within Mount Potala.

Finally, six hours passed. Before the Black Asura spoke a single word, Lin Ming’s eyes flashed open.

Nearly all of the chaotic energies within Lin Ming’s body had been cleanly refined. The wounds on his body were also restored. Although he wasn’t at his peak state, it wasn’t much different.

He stood up, faced the Black Asura, and took a deep breath as he shouted out, “Let’s go!”

The Black Asura was different from all other enemies that Lin Ming had encountered in the final trial so far. This Black Asura had its own will and thoughts, and Lin Ming even suspected that he was related to the Asura Road Master. Perhaps he was an artifact spirit left behind by the Asura Road Master, or perhaps it was an incarnation produced from a tiny wisp of the Asura Road Master’s consciousness.

Without a single word spoken, the Black Asura suddenly punched his fist towards Lin Ming!

This fist thrust out without any sign, nor did there seem to be any strength gathered unto it. It was only a simple punch. But as this Black Asura punched out, the void in front of him seemed to squeeze together due to the horrifying fist potential.

The power of countless Laws gathered from all directions, converging onto the Black Asura’s fist. For a time the Black Asura’s fist created its own unyielding momentum!

“This is my slaughter fist intent. If you can receive it then you’ll have passed the first attack!”

The Black Asura’s icy metallic voice echoed out. His first strike wasn’t quick, but because of the horrifying fist potential behind it, Lin Ming was covered within it, his body stiffening and making it hard for him to move.

Suddenly, it seemed as if countless demons and ghosts appeared, ranting and raving in Lin Ming’s ears. Lin Ming seemed to arrive on an Asura battlefield. There was an endless smell of blood and death. Corpses lay everywhere and rivers of blood flowed!

This Asura war god was originally a death god. This slaughter fist intent was formed from the endless infernal energy and countless lives that the Asura war god had slain!

If Lin Ming’s mindset wasn’t firm, he would drown in this slaughter fist intent. Even his consciousness would be melted away by this infernal energy and he would lose sense of his own existence.

In order to withstand the Black Asura’s fist, not only would Lin Ming have to face the physical fist but also the tremendous slaughter intent behind it!

After understanding this, Lin Ming fiercely bit down on his tongue, using the pain to wash away any haziness in his mind. At the same time, the blue soul battle spirit flew out from within Lin Ming’s spiritual sea!

Woo – Woo – Woo –

The battle spirit howled out, slashing apart the void.

The higher level a battle spirit was, the more difficult it was to enhance. Lin Ming’s current battle spirit level was already at small success of the blue soul level. Moreover, there was grandmist energy condensed within it, making it that much stronger!

As the battle spirit appeared, the immense amount of evil spirits and demons contained within the fist intent were broken apart by the blue soul battle spirit. For a time, the mournful howls of ghosts filled the air!

The Black Asura’s slaughter fist intent was horrifying. Even though he had only displayed a fraction of his true strength, this was enough to cause Lin Ming’s battle spirit to be mired in air. It wasn’t like the past, where the appearance of the battle spirit brought with it an unstoppable might!

Ca!

Cruel demons and evil spirits were torn apart by the blue soul battle spirit. At the same time, the light of Lin Ming’s blue soul battle spirit also rapidly dimmed!

This sudden turn of events caused a light of astonishment to appear in the Black Asura’s eyes. He never imagined that a human like Lin Ming would have such outstanding attainments in the aspect of battle spirits.

Meanwhile, the Black Asura’s fist strength became even fiercer and crazier. It was like a rising tsunami, shattering the void!

An indescribably terrifying strength fell onto Lin Ming’s body in torrents!

Because of the blue soul battle spirit’s counterattack, there wasn’t much slaughter intent left in the Black Asura’s fist. However, just the striking power of this fist was more than horrifying!

This strike smashed into Lin Ming!

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. The spear in his hands thrust outwards as he opened the Purple Temple Dao Palace and Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace together!

For a time, Lin Ming’s bodily strength rose to dozens of billions of jins. With the support of the Celestial Tyrant Manual, his strength neared that of ten dragons!

His spear collided with the Black Asura’s fist!

It was like a meteor crashing into the earth. The ground rose up, lifted and blown away by the terrifying shockwaves that reverberated outwards!

In this tyrannical storm, Lin Ming felt a terrifying energy run down the long spear and into his body. His arms shook and blood vessels cracked apart all over his arms. The energy broke into his body, and no matter how tough his body was, it still caused his blood to tumble and his organs to be injured!

Lin Ming was sent soaring backwards like a broken kite falling from the skies. In a single strike, he was forced back dozens of miles before he came to a skittering halt. He stabbed his spear into the wasteland to support himself. Both of his arms were slick with blood.

In just a breath of time, Lin Ming stood up once more. He looked at the Black Asura that stood still several dozen miles away!

A blazing fighting spirit burned ever bright in his eyes.

The Black Asura looked at Lin Ming with surprise. He hadn’t thought that Lin Ming would still be able to stand after this strike.

This was because the blue soul battle spirit had broken through most of the slaughter fist intent, making it so that Lin Ming only had to withstand the physical attack of the fist itself. This caused the pressure of the attack to be reduced by a great deal. When added in with the fact that Lin Ming opened two Dao Palaces and his body was terrifyingly strong, it wasn’t too difficult for him to withstand this strike!

“You have six hours to rest.”

The Black Asura expressionlessly said. Even though he was dozens of miles away, his voice was clear as it sounded out next to Lin Ming’s ears.

“No need! A quarter hour is enough!”

Lin Ming’s words were firm and filled with confidence. He gripped his spear and began moving towards the Black Asura.

“How amusing!”

The Black Asura’s hard lips moved, as if he were faintly smiling.

“Since you are so confident, then… very well! Prepare yourself to withstand my second attack!”

As he spoke, the dark gray Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel that slowly spun behind the Black Asura flew up and fell in between his hands.

His second strike was clearly the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel.

Lin Ming’s eyes were cold and resolute. Step by step, he walked towards the Black Asura. As he walked, the ruptured flesh and blood vessels on his arms began to wriggle. His muscles and blood vessels rapidly regenerated, becoming whole again. With the support of his dual dragon and phoenix bloodlines, Lin Ming possessed a terrifying resilience!

To call out a quarter hour was not because Lin Ming was arrogant or too full of himself, but because he wanted to rely on the fighting spirit that bubbled over in his body to contend with the Black Asura in a single go!

Lin Ming’s steps were slow and steady. In a quarter hour’s time, he had walked a mere several dozen miles!

At the time arrived, he just happened to reach the front of the Black Asura once more.

Then, the Black Asura attacked!

The spinning Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel released 10,000 beams of ghostly light. Howls filled the air, like the cries and screams of 10,000 ghosts and demons, alarming to the ears!

A dreadful demonic strength gushed out around the wheel, burning around it like brilliant black flames. These flames transformed into a monstrous being with three heads and six arms. Behind this Asura phantom, two massive wings spread forth and unfurled in the air. This Asura phantom’s six arms each held different weapons, and in front of its body was also a Wheel of Samsara!

The Black Asura thrust out his palm. This Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, like the legendary Wheel of Samsara that ruled over all threads of fate, hurtled towards Lin Ming!

And at this time, the Heretical God Force within Lin Ming opened. His body erupted with energy to its limits as countless lines of the Asura Laws gathered in front of him, condensing into a black wheel.

This black wheel had infinite cruel demons condensed within it and it was also being held against the chest of a three-headed six-armed Asura war god. This wheel that Lin Ming summoned was exactly the same as the wheel that the Black Asura used – it was also the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel!

Seeing this, the Black Asura was startled. Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel against Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel! This trial challenger also cultivated the Asura Heavenly Dao!

Chapter 1686 – Profound Laws

“Interesting…”

The Black Asura lifted his hands and the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel came crashing down!

Lin Ming didn’t retreat at all. With the sound of a whirling vortex, a strange black spiritual strength shot out from his body, slowly floating atop the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel.

The black spiritual energy slowly transformed into a phantom.

Roiling with dread, a black robed man appeared within the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. He wore bronze armor and had the appearance of a demon. As he towered like a mountain, he emitted a black light, his pupils dark and gloomy.

This man was none other than Tian Mingzi!

In these past years, using the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, Lin Ming had swallowed the souls or residual wills of many powerhouses.

Among these were his mortal blood enemy Tian Mingzi, the residual will of the desolate mortals within the Forsaken Mortal Tomb, the aura of the God Beast phantoms he had destroyed, and their Laws.

These powerful phantoms created infinite changes within Lin Ming’s Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. Even the space around him trembled.

As this terrifying aura of dead spirits rampaged in all directions, a brilliant light shined in the Black Asura’s eyes. He didn’t think this youth would have such a gentle and calm ethereal martial intent but also such a cruel and powerful Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel!

None of these powerful existences sealed within the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel were a trifling matter. The Black Asura found it hard to imagine just how Lin Ming had sealed them in.

And there was actually someone in front of him who dared to use the same skill! To the Black Asura, this was a provocation.

Within the Black Asura’s heart, mighty waves began to form.

The obsidian pupils of the Black Asura began to swirl like a shadow vortex. All of the black lines of the Asura Heavenly Dao in the air were galvanized to an even greater degree of the power of the Asura Laws, all of it gathering in the black wheel.

The wheel expanded again and again and the Asura phantom also grew, as if it were about to soar into the heavens.

Where the black flames went, even space itself was melted away by the flickering dark power. The holes it formed in space dotted the sky like a honeycomb. The power of space poured out of these tears, rampaging in all directions.

The jet black flames blotted out the skies and came sweeping towards Lin Ming.

“This move, how will you meet it?” The Black Asura’s voice was icy cold, carrying with it a momentum that seemed as if it could destroy all wills.

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. He could feel that the dark flames before him contained dense and innumerable Asura Heavenly Dao Laws, some of them containing the power of Laws that he had never comprehended before.

The gigantic and powerful pitch black flames seemed as if they could burn apart the universe.

But a heroic and daring spirit surged within Lin Ming’s heart. Even if he were to be defeated, he still would not retreat!

“10,000 demons, life and death, I am the lord of demons!”

Lin Ming cried out in his heart. As he did, a blood red light flashed in his eyes. A great blood essence blood energy shot out from his skin, nose, and mouth, brilliantly shining as it flew into the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel.

In the middle of this Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, the Asura war god developed a faint similarity to Lin Ming.

The endless blood essence formed into a giant phantom of Lin Ming. This phantom grasped the Phoenix Blood Spear, its infernal energy soaring to the heavens. In the midst of these 10,000 demons, it was like the lord of demons had appeared. Its lofty and arrogant aura rose as it commanded all the demons and spirits like Tian Mingzi to meet the incoming enemy.

In that moment, the momentum of this attack was no less than the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel that the Black Asura had sent out.

In the void, one could only see two massive spinning wheels collide against each other, smashing against each other like two grinding pans.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

Each time they collided and fought, the surrounding space would be torn apart. The phantoms within the black wheel violently battled and engulfed each other. A space storm formed and even they were sucked into the swirling black vortex where they disappeared without a trace.

Vast tracts of space were twisted apart. As some ruptured pieces of demonic energy fell to the ground, they were as heavy as mountains and created unfathomable deep craters.

Lin Ming had invested a tremendous amount of life essence into the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, so he could directly feel the spinning power of it.

Every time the wheels clashed, it was like a massive grinding pan was viciously crashing into his body. His previous injuries had yet to recover and blood shot out from his wounds. As this blood shot out from his body, they did so with such force and speed that they created holes in space.

An agonizing pain that rose from the depths of his soul occupied the entirety of Lin Ming’s mind.

But at the same time, in this most direct collision, Lin Ming’s life essence was able to touch against the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel that the Black Asura had formed.

“What is that?”

His life essence could clearly feel the unique exquisiteness of the Black Asura’s Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. The Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel that the Black Asura formed was far more profound and large.

As for the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel that Lin Ming had formed, when compared to the Black Asura’s, it was the same as comparing the home of an ordinary mortal to the majestic castle of a noble.

Although Lin Ming had the support of auras from all sorts of powerhouses, when his wheel faced the more perfect Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel from the Black Asura, it began to lose ground…

The reason for this gradual loss was not because of a difference in strength, but because of a difference in the subtle exquisiteness of the Laws!

Finally, with a loud rumbling sound, the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel that Lin Ming formed completely exploded.

At the same time, the Black Asura’s Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel was also crushed into a ball of black energy. But as it stood, this remaining amount was still terrifying. It carried with it a dreadful annihilating momentum as it came hurtling towards Lin Ming.

Lin Ming’s heart skipped a beat and all the hair on his body stood on end. This black energy was the essence of the Black Asura’s Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. If he were to be struck by it, perhaps he would perish here!

After burning a great amount of his life essence and in addition worsen his wounds, Lin Ming was embattled from all sides. His current condition was miserable beyond compare, and his divine soul seemed like a candle flickering in the wind, almost unable to withstand the continued burden.

But he never thought of giving up. He would not die here!

“Purple Temple Dao Palace – open!”

Gritting his teeth, blood began flowing from Lin Ming’s eyes.

Suddenly, a star seemed to rise up from Lin Ming’s body, shining down on the world like a bright moon.

Within Lin Ming’s body, the massive accumulation of vitality and life force was opened by the Purple Temple Dao Palace.

Within his body, the roar of a distant dragon could be heard.

Ancient and primal, its vivid aura seemed to travel through the river of time from the distant past until now. A giant Azure Dragon appeared, rushing out from Lin Ming’s flesh and blood.

The Azure Dragon spanned the heavens and earth, emitting the majesty of a noble dragon. It violently clashed with the essence of the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel.

Within the void, the Azure Dragon was shattered like glass by the small black ball of energy.

As for that small black ball of energy, it was reduced to a tiny speck that struck Lin Ming.

This tiny speck rushed into Lin Ming’s body.

Standing high in the air, Lin Ming’s entire body shook. His blood red pupils turned incomparably strange and ghostly as a black vortex slowly swirled within them.

Puff, puff!

A deep and heavy force began to explode within him.

In the next moment, countless bones shattered in his body. Lin Ming vomited out a mouthful of blood and fell to the ground like a broken kite.

The Black Asura stepped through space and immediately appeared in the skies above Lin Ming’s ruined body. Standing high, he indifferently looked down at Lin Ming.

“Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, hm… He is so young and yet he cultivated the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. In this era, this truly is a miracle…”

The Black Asura appeared lost in thought.

At this time, lying on the ground, Lin Ming felt endless streams of pain piercing into his brain, making him feel as if his head would explode.

But at the same time, an even greater surprise appeared within Lin Ming’s heart.

He had obtained some new Asura Laws. They were like worms in his blood, floating in his marrow.

These things were comprehensions of the Black Asura’s Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel after colliding with it and having a part of it smash into his body.

These were truly things comprehended with valor and blood.

As he comprehended these new things, his bones and muscles that were destroyed by the Asura Laws began to rapidly recover under Lin Ming’s control.

His inner injuries, beneath the influence of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws, began to rapidly swallow spiritual power from the surroundings to regenerate.

Broken bones began to mend together. Within, his marrow gurgled as fresh blood was produced. His pale complexion began to slowly restore with a rosy tint.

Within the Black Asura’s pitch black pupils, he could clearly see every minute change occurring within Lin Ming’s body.

So, when these new Asura Heavenly Dao Laws appeared, even the Black Asura revealed a different expression.

“Eh? Not only wasn’t he killed by my Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, but he seemed to have grasped even more things about the Asura Heavenly Dao…”

A strange expression formed on the Black Asura’s face.

Such a trial challenger was far too terrifying!

In that strike just now, the Black Asura estimated it would be extremely difficult for Lin Ming to withstand. After all, Lin Ming’s understanding of the Asura Heavenly Dao was far too limited and it was impossible to compare their two Myriad Demon Karmic Wheels.

But in the critical moment when Lin Ming faced the aftermath of the Black Asura’s attack, he had opened the Nine Stars of the Dao palace, using his powerful mortal body and blood vitality to forcefully withstand the Black Asura’s attack. Although Lin Ming’s body had been ruined, he had still been able to preserve the source of his life.

The Black Asura hadn’t thought that when Lin Ming was on the precipice of life and death, he would actually obtain new comprehensions into the Asura Heavenly Dao!

When facing this type of person, if one didn’t kill them, they would only become increasingly strong. They were the type to make breakthroughs in battle. This was an extremely dreadful kind of enemy!

“You have six hours. Afterwards, you will receive my third move!”

As the Black Asura’s voice fell, he vanished. He remained cold and callous throughout, not showing the least bit of leniency in his role as the examiner in this trial.

Lying on the ground, Lin Ming struggled to sit upright. With only six hours, he didn’t dare to waste the tiniest bit of time.

Lin Ming entered the fused martial intent and his mind became completely empty. Behind him, the vague phantom of a Bodhi tree appeared once more.

During these six hours, he grasped the chance to recover his wounds. Lin Ming’s ruined body continued to rapidly regenerate!

There was still a great deal of the power of the many heavenly materials that Lin Ming had swallowed up within his body. Now, he refined these energies to make up for his missing blood vitality.

When the time arrived, Lin Ming’s eyes flashed open.

At this time, he was slightly excited. When he faced the Black Asura’s Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, recklessly facing it head on had been the right decision to make. This had allowed him to obtain many deeper comprehensions into the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws.

These sorts of comprehensions could not be matched by any rewards.

Chapter 1687 – Pass

After slowly adjusting his mental state, Lin Ming could feel the sea deep aura of the Black Asura swell forth around him. He looked up and saw the void being ripped apart. The indifferent Black Asura flew high in the skies, looking down at him from a commanding position.

Lin Ming calmed his thoughts.

“Are you ready?” The Black Asura asked.

“Come!”

Standing in place, Lin Ming was as tall and straight as a spear. His aura was sharp, like a blade that could pierce a hole through the heavens.

The Black Asura didn’t speak anymore. He deeply gazed at Lin Ming. No matter what happened, this young man deserved another look.

The Black Asura reached out a hand. The originally empty void beside him was forcefully pulled open like slides, revealing a crack in space.

From this crack, the Black Asura grasped a long spear!

This spear was the weapon the Black Asura used and also the dragon spear carved upon the relief of the gate! In the last two moves, the Black Asura hadn’t used a weapon, instead fighting his opponent unarmed. But this time, he resorted to bringing out his weapon!

At this moment, Lin Ming closed his eyes, his entire body gushing out with energy. His hair flapped in the wind and his strength started to rapidly rise.

A True Dragon soared through the heavens, its boundless aura grand and magnificent, its claws shredding space to pieces.

A Fire Phoenix carried with it an overwhelming sea of flames that blocked out the skies.

One dragon and one phoenix acted as guards. As the dragon and phoenix appeared, their radiance illuminated the world, alarming all.

At the same time a massive sea of lightning appeared in the skies, filled with vitality and sparkling with beams of electricity. Above this sea of lighting bloomed a giant flame lotus.

These two powers actually managed to come together in an incredible harmony, blending together as one. Each one shone with an unbelievable destructive force.

This was the thunder and fire heavenly tribulation that dwelled within Lin Ming’s body!

In the great skies of this wasteland, more changes began to occur.

The overlapping layers of gray clouds were torn apart by countless mysterious beams of light. Swathes of stars appeared in the heavens, their starlight falling down like a descending galaxy, all of their strength flowing into Lin Ming.

Lin Ming bathed in this mysterious strength. His skin shimmered as more and more strength rose within his body.

One at a time, giant stars began to appear in the heavens. There were nine in total, all of them sparkling in space, floating up and down.

At the same time, nine spots on Lin Ming’s body projected a blinding starlight, dazzling to the senses.

As if he himself were becoming a shining star.

The stars above him resonated with him like nine beating hearts.

Of the nine stars, two were particularly radiant, as bright as suns in the noon sky. They were the Purple Temple Dao Palace and the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace.

The mystical strength emitted from the Purple Temple Dao Palace fused into Lin Ming’s body. Large amounts of life potential and yang energy ignited within him, making his body feel hot and dry. Faint drops of life energy started to drip out from every pore on his body. They were as bright as fresh blood, like his body could not contain the overwhelming amount of boiling blood vitality within him.

The Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace galvanized the momentum of the world, quickening its flow. Heavenly fire, thunder, raging currents, netherworld energy, all sorts of powers of the Heavenly Dao howled in the void.

Lin Ming could truly feel the incoming threat, the threat of death. If he could not block this spear, the only path left to him was death!

At this time, the Black Asura attacked!

A spear thrust out. A strange vortex seemed to manifest itself, swallowing in all light within this great wasteland.

Lin Ming was suddenly shrouded in absolute darkness.

But what was darker than this darkness was the swift and fierce spear light that came shooting out at him.

This spear light was condensed within the aura of the Asura Great Dao! Lin Ming was familiar with this aura, but he also found it strange. Without a doubt, this was a domain of the Asura Heavenly Dao that Lin Ming couldn’t comprehend!

Space groaned as it shattered like glass in massive tracts.

The spear seemed as if it could pierce through the universe. Lin Ming felt as if it were impossible to resist, as if this spear contained the power of Laws as deep and profound as the endless hells.

As this long spear targeted him, his entire body fell into fear, leaving him unable to move.

This was the weird response produced by the body when they encountered something incomparably terrifying.

Realizing the abnormality of his body, Lin Ming’s heart filled with dread and awe. Without a doubt, the Black Asura’s last attack would shake the heavens and sunder the earth.

No matter what, he had to withstand this spear strike!

“Open!” Lin Ming roared out. Behind him, an ancient green tree began to rapidly rise, sending out a lofty and towering momentum. The branches and leaves of the tree grew thick and lush, generating so fast that they seemed to become a forest.

Lin Ming grasped his long spear. As he gathered his spear potential, grandmist aura wildly appeared. In front of him, space began to shiver and twist. Grandmist space appeared, bringing with it a great strength that seemed as if it could imprison everything.

These strengths were so great that the ground beneath Lin Ming’s feet began to crack and disintegrate, turning into the tiniest specks of dust that drifted into the air. Fissures split open the ground, spreading out in all directions.

The ground beneath Lin Ming gave way to space, as if an unfathomable abyss opened up beneath him. He grit his teeth, and with a loud shout all of this strength poured into the pitch black spear in his hands.

Bang!

The towering Heretical God Tree collided with the Black Asura’s spear light and was immediately pierced through. However, a tiny amount of the spear’s black energy also dissipated in the process.

Soon after, the phoenix and dragon crashed into the spear light. The powers of thunder and fire heavenly tribulations, the Purple Temple Dao Palace, the Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace, thick essence energy that filled the air, all of this crashed upwards like a blood red meteor surrounded by a storm. Together with the misty grandmist space that carried with it the aura of the beginning, everything struck the pitch black long spear.

All of these strengths were enough to shock the world, and each one was more mysterious and powerful than the last!

The pitch black spear was annihilated at a speed visible to the naked eye. Mysterious Asura Heavenly Dao runes were torn off the spear light like motes of light and destroyed, creating tiny primitive black holes.

It was strange and captivating.

“Good!”

An unusual expression appeared on the Black Asura’s face. He faintly stared at Lin Ming. The black spear he shot out only had 10 foot or so left remaining. But the grandmist space that Lin Ming summoned began to crack and the grandmist energy within it was already extremely transparent.

“It’s still not enough!” Lin Ming clenched his teeth and cried out once more. A deep bass sound echoed out from within his body, as if his body itself had become a universe. The strange vibrato seemed to emit from the deepest point within him.

Above Lin Ming’s spear point, a pitch black energy vortex appeared. As this vortex appeared, it was like a stone had been dropped on a lake surface as intense spatial ripples appeared all around.

Whorl, whorl, whorl!

The surrounding space began disintegrating. A wild space storm appeared and swept out in all directions, sharper and deadlier than a hail of blades.

All of the strengths within this world, even the remnant strength of the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel floating in the void, was sucked in by this vortex.

This was a technique from the Divine Seal Art created by Empyrean Divine Seal – Eternal Darkness!

A black hole was the hardest celestial body in the universe. With this black hole as a shield, he welcomed the incoming spear light!

With this move, Lin Ming’s body was thoroughly exhausted. His blood vitality was in deep debt and only the Purple Temple Dao Palace within him was fanning the fires of life within his body, giving him enough energy to move.

Seeing this black hole sweep up into the skies, the Black Asura’s complexion slightly changed.

The black spear was swept into this dark vortex. Within it, endless detonations of thunder and fire exploded.

Woosh, woosh, woosh!

The energy blown off the spear light came hurtling towards Lin Ming!

At this time, Lin Ming had already given his everything and it was impossible for him to resist the shockwaves of the spear light. His body was struck and steams of blood shot out like arrows from his body.

Lin Ming was like a fading candle in a storm. His body wavered, swinging about like a broken swing. Unable to suppress the injuries within his body, he suddenly vomited out a mouthful of blood.

But at this time, the endless explosions stopped. A small but sharp, black long spear rushed out from the black vortex, shooting towards Lin Ming.

In that moment, Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. He was already a lamp without oil. It was impossible for him to block this strike.

Lin Ming’s heart skipped a beat. He thought he would die in the next moment!

However, this feeling was only for a fleeting moment. As the black spear shot through Lin Ming’s face, although it was still sharp and threatening, it actually passed straight through his body.

It turned out this was only the Black Asura’s spear intent!

Although the spear intent was strong, the entire black spear’s Asura Heavenly Dao strength was already worn down to nothing. To Lin Ming who understood the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws to an extent, this only scared him and couldn’t threaten his life.

“Three moves passed…”

This was the last thought that flashed through Lin Ming’s mind. In the next moment, his body fluttered down from the skies like a piece of cotton…

At this time, Lin Ming’s true essence, astral essence, spirit essence, and blood vitality were completely exhausted. His consciousness dimmed as he fainted.

Chapter 1688A – Taunt

All of the heavenly materials Lin Ming ate had been slowly absorbed by him during his prolonged battle. Slowly, the essence of these materials subtly integrated into his body.

In truth, to the current Lin Ming whose mortal body, soul, and inner world were already extremely powerful, these heavenly materials weren’t too advantageous.

To Lin Ming, the most precious things he obtained was the harvest he made in the Laws during those seemingly endless battles.

The opponents he faced in the Gate of Laws all had different combat methods, utilizing different Laws. After experiencing the might of these Laws, Lin Ming was able to broaden his horizons and obtain a far greater harvest.

In particular, during his final battle with the Black Asura, which gave Lin Ming an even deeper understanding of the Asura Heavenly Dao. However, all of this required time to digest.

Although Lin Ming seemed unconscious, the truth was that all sorts of fragments of the Great Dao Laws were submerged in his spiritual sea, slowly fusing into his very being and giving him new understandings.

As Lin Ming was continuing his trial, what was happening outside the Gate of Laws, on the third level of the final trial, was a completely different scene altogether.

The first group of people who successfully reached the third level were the weakest of the trial challengers. They were people who chose the easiest mortal step level difficulty, and within the mortal step level difficulty, one only needed to cross the aerial bridge to pass. There was no need to step onto the ancient continent and battle the numerous opponents that manifested from the Laws of the 33 Heavens.

As such, they only needed 3-4 days to pass the Gate of Laws. Afterwards, they could obtain their rewards and enter the fourth level.

But this fourth level was far more perilous than the last two levels! There was a dramatic rise in difficulty!

On the fourth level, it could be said that every step was filled with murderous intent, every step was a life or death crisis!

After a good number of trial challengers perished, many others decided to give up continuing the final trial and return to the third level. After all, these people were all extraordinary individuals of their respective influences and they had a glorious future awaiting them. After they visited the fourth level they realized that with their strength, they were far more likely to die than to survive. For them, they definitely wouldn’t go there just to die in vain.

Without a doubt, the final trial had many great lucky chances within. But if one didn’t even have their life, what use were these lucky chances?

So, more and more people returned to the third level. The third level was a place without danger; it was only meant for trial challengers to receive their rewards and rest. These people planned to wait here until the end of the final trial arrived. At that time, they would all be collectively teleported back to the inner Asura Road, at some random place above the Asura Sea.

And at this time, the Gate of Laws began to slowly spin as another batch of trial challengers emerged.

The one leading the group was a high-spirited young man wearing a star crown – he was the Divine Void Third Crown Prince!

“Your Highness Crown Prince!”

As the Divine Void Third Crown Prince appeared, many people who came from influences closely related to Divine Void Divine Kingdom came to greet him.

“Congratulations Crown Prince Your Highness on obtaining victory and perfectly passing the trial!”

Someone immediately sensed the mood and began to flatter him as much as he could. Just by looking at the Crown Prince’s energetic and happy expression, one could correctly guess that his trial had gone smoothly.

And in fact, he wasn’t wrong. The Divine Void Crown Prince had obtained the highest completion percent possible in the earth-step difficulty at 36%.

“Indeed, this level of accomplishment is truly worthy of Your Highness the Crown Prince! I think that Your Highness’s earth-step difficulty was far too low, perhaps the heaven-step difficulty would have been just right, haha!”

After confirming that the Divine Void Crown Prince had indeed perfectly passed, many people began to compliment him. However, the Divine Void Crown Prince’s smile didn’t last too long. Soon after, the Gate of Laws shook once more.

Bigflame, the direct disciple of Heavenly Union Divine Kingdom’s Divine Emperor had appeared.

Bigflame also had a wide smile on his rotund face. It was clear to everyone that he too had perfectly passed the trial. This left the Divine Void Crown Prince frowning a little. When he was undergoing the earth-step difficulty, the process hadn’t been too easy for him. He was originally hoping to roll over Bigflame with his score, but now it seemed they had both emerged even with each other.

For a time, the Third Crown Prince and Bigflame became the focus of the entire audience. The two of them could be said to be brimming with success. Although the earth-step difficulty was only the second level of difficulty, it wasn’t simple at all. Perfectly passing was an extremely difficult task and even many proud children of heaven from the various great influences here had only completed a part of it.

For the two to perfectly pass, they would be praised once they returned to their respective True Divinity Holy Lands.

At this time, Suya, Mo Brightmoon, and the others were all looking towards the blood red Asura level difficulty exit from the Gate of Laws. In such a festive atmosphere, the two of them were actually feeling worried and anxious.

Because of their profound trust in Lin Ming, even though he had chosen the Asura level difficulty that no one had passed in billions of years, they still anticipated a miracle to occur.

Lin Ming had been far too hasty in choosing the Asura level difficulty. Before others had enough time to fully explain to him the situation, the Gate of Laws had opened and sucked him in.

They didn’t think Lin Ming could complete much of the Asura level difficulty. As long as he passed through alive, they would already be thanking the heavens and earth.

“What is it? Junior-apprentice sister Suya, do you have any troubles on your mind?”

A light voice echoed out, causing Suya to frown. She turned to see a robed man walking towards her with a smile on his face. This person was Duke Fullmoon!

Duke Fullmoon had chosen the earth-step difficulty. Although he didn’t perfectly complete it, his performance had been adequate and he had obtained a great many things from the battles. From this alone, Duke Fullmoon was more than satisfied.

Although the Third Crown prince and Bigflame were the two who blossomed in splendor within the Gate of Laws trial, Duke Fullmoon was still in an extremely good mood. At this time, he held onto a folding fan, slowly fanning himself with an imposing expression on his face.

He certainly knew what Suya was worrying about. The reason he deliberately brought it up was to bring Suya down a notch.

He remembered that at the start of the Divine Rune City Auction, when he met Suya at the entrance, Suya had treated him coldly because of Lin Ming’s presence.

Duke Fullmoon had kept this memory to heart.

“Its nothing.”

Suya’s voice was cold and desolate, as if she didn’t care about Duke Fullmoon’s presence at all.

Duke Fullmoon thought little of it. He chuckled and said, “What, are you still thinking that Lin Ming will come out alive? It seems that junior-apprentice sister Suya really has a deep affection towards this Lin Ming. But what a pity… heroes in their youth simply do not know their own weight. To choose the Asura difficulty so recklessly just to win the attention of others, and yet the result is that no one cares about him. All his grandstanding has come to nothing…”

Duke Fullmoon smiled, his eyes sweeping over everyone else.

Nearly everyone was gathered around the Divine Void Third Crown Prince and Bigflame. Indeed, no one cared about Lin Ming.

In this final trial, Lin Ming wasn’t able to arouse much interest at all. After all, these people weren’t familiar with him and only knew he was the creator of the ‘Lin’ logo divine runic symbols.

When Lin Ming chose the Asura level difficulty, the others were startled, but that was all. After a moment, they realized Lin Ming was just putting on an act and he likely had some mental problems. Soon, everyone put this matter at the back of their minds. Now, they were all busy trying to be on good terms with the Third Crown Prince and Bigflame. The Third Crown Prince and Bigflame both came from True Divinity level influences and their talent was also extremely good. If those here could be on good terms with them, this relationship might be of help to them in the future.

As the Third Crown Prince and Bigflame were surrounded by a crowd of people, they slowly floated upwards. They were about to choose their own immortal palace reward.

But at this time, the Gate of Laws violently shook once more.

A blue-clothed woman flew out from the Gate of Laws!

Her clothes floated behind her and her entire body shined with pale blue Law runes. She was like an immortal fairy exiled from the highest nine heavens.

This person was Soul Empress Sheng Mei!

She had perfectly passed the heaven-step smelting trial difficulty. Not just that, but her clothes were unstained and her appearance was otherworldly. It was clear she still had a great deal of strength remaining!

Everyone was stunned. They soon looked up at her.

“Sheng Mei! She came from the heaven-step difficulty!”

“Too fierce! Look at her unbothered appearance, it seems she has perfectly completed it!”

Some people cried out in alarm. But Sheng Mei didn’t bother with these people. Instead, as soon as she appeared, she flew directly towards an immortal palace.

The immortal palace she chose was as large as a mountain. The one she chose was a second-rank immortal palace!

Woosh!

Soul Empress Sheng Mei flew into the immortal palace without stopping at all. The entire process was like a comet passing through the skies, free and easy, filled with beauty.

“She is truly worthy of being called Soul Empress Sheng Mei. Even after completing the heaven-step difficulty she is still so calm. We are far inferior to the likes of her,” the Divine Void Crown Prince whispered, his face still as happy and joyful as a spring breeze. He didn’t envy Sheng Mei’s results at all, because he and Sheng Mei never stood on the same plane to begin with. So, there was no reason to compare himself with her.

She was someone who stood at the peak of the entire soul race. Within every spiritas of the 33 Heavens, she was the highest status woman there was. She was a character that could stand on par with Soul Emperor Divine Void, so there was no meaning in competing with her.

“Haha, Crown Prince is too modest. Soul Empress Sheng Mei is a divine being, but if the Crown Prince is compared to Soul Empress Sheng Mei, the differences aren’t too great! Crown Prince can still show disdain for all other heroes!”

Many people began to flatter once more. They couldn’t match up to Sheng Mei, but they could establish relations with the Divine Void Crown Prince. So, when Sheng Mei appeared, she didn’t steal the limelight of the Divine Void Crown Prince.

As many people were speaking, the Gate of Laws shook once more.

Chapter 1691 – The Immortal Palace

The planet-sized immortal palace was vast and ethereal. This was a mysterious ancient land no one had opened for billions of years. As Lin Ming stepped past the gates of this immortal palace, he immediately felt as though he had stepped into an alternate world; the atmosphere here was extremely different from that of the Asura Road.

All sorts of strange powers flowed around Lin Ming, rushing about like a tide!

Lin Ming knew these powers were Laws.

In the Gate of Laws, Lin Ming had fought off opponents that represented the Laws of the 33 Heavens. Now he had gained a considerable understanding towards the Laws of the 33 Heavens. He could faintly feel that within the confines of this immortal palace, there was also the strength of the 33 Heavens’ Laws!

In the past, the Asura Road Master had cultivated the Laws of the 33 Heavens and established his own Asura Heavenly Dao. This immortal palace held the Laws of the 33 Heavens.

Lin Ming took a deep breath and stepped forwards. The tall and grand winding corridors were all made of some unknown divine stone. This sort of divine stone had been here for billions of years, experiencing the weathering of the vast river of time, yet it still remained bright and spotless.

Like this, Lin Ming arrived at the end of the corridor. He could see a palatial door, carved with gold and jade.

When Lin Ming stepped in front of this door, the door actually started to swing open!

For some time, a brilliant radiance spilled forth. As Lin Ming saw what was inside, his heart shook!

At the end of this corridor was actually a great world!

This great world had mountains and rivers, lakes and seas. And where Lin Ming was, where the door opened into, was high in the air, hundreds of thousands of feet up. He had a bird’s eye view of the boundless world laid out before him!

On the continent of this world there was an endless road built from blue stone slabs. From the ground, it extended into the infinite heavens until it disappeared into the clouds of mist.

A cold wind blew through the air, dissipating some of the mist. He could see that even further in the distance, that endless blue stone road still stretched onwards. This blue stone road was simple and desolate, seeming to contain the aura of inexhaustible years.

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. He dove down from where he was and stood atop the blue stone road.

“Mm?”

Suddenly, Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. His eyes were attracted to something right in front of him on the blue stone road, in the center of a stone slab.

Right in front of him was a deep foot imprint.

Although it looked like an ordinary footprint, when this image reflected in Lin Ming’s eyes it left him shocked. He could clearly feel a potent and awe-inspiring aura from this footstep, one as sharp and wild as a savage blade!

What sort of person could leave their footprint behind on this highest tier of rewards? After so many years, their footprint still existed as before, emitting such a dreadful aura!

Lin Ming composed his thoughts. He resolutely moved forwards on the blue stone road. Impartial and without bias, his foot stepped onto that footprint, perfectly fitting inside.

Bang!

A peal of thunder rang out in his mind. The world began to change. A horrifying bang echoed out like a rolling cloud of thunder, leaving Lin Ming’s ears shaking from the shock.

As his vision cleared, he discovered he was surrounded by countless dense auras.

One by one, all sorts of giant, horrifying, and blood-thirsty warriors surrounded him. They wore metal armors and wielded spears, halberds, sabers, swords, and more. There was every weapon that could be imagined here.

These giants all had weapons over 10 feet long that were stained with blood. They exuded a cruel and ominous killing intent, making one’s heart race. And each one had a blood vitality so dense and pure that it created a halo of flame-like energy around them, making them seem like embodiments of dread.

Out of all these giants, there was one that was over 30 feet tall and had an aura so deep and vast, it was like an ocean. This giant had white hair that fell down his back like a waterfall, and he wore a shining silver war armor. He indifferently stared at Lin Ming.

These eyes were incomparably terrifying. Lin Ming didn’t doubt that with this gaze alone, this giant could cause a peerless powerhouse’s soul to shatter and fade away, forcing them to fall into an infinite abyss.

Facing these giants, Lin Ming discovered he wasn’t a match for any one of them!

If so, that meant these giants were at least all unrivalled Great World King powerhouses!

However, what was strange was that even under so much killing intent, Lin Ming was still capable of withstanding their combined suppressive pressure. Moreover, he did so with ease!

Even that white haired warrior with the deep aura couldn’t suppress Lin Ming.

This left Lin Ming startled. He subconsciously looked at himself and discovered that he had completely changed in appearance.

At this time, his body was wrapped in thick dragon-like muscles. He had blood red hair that fell down his back and his chest and arms were completely covered with black scales. These scales didn’t come from some Empyrean spirit treasure but emerged from within his body. On his face, strange demonic runes glowed. These demonic runes all seemed to faintly resonate with the Asura Heavenly Dao.

His looks had changed. His forehead was as sharp as a sword and his eyes were like sabers. He looked ferocious, untamed!

He grasped a dragon spear in his hand and the aura he exuded was enough to cause the surrounding space to gently tremble. This was an incomparably formidable feeling that Lin Ming had never experienced before.

Like a vast galaxy could be sundered in half by his spear!

This person was…

Lin Ming faintly realized that he had turned into this war god. The scenes he was seeing weren’t an illusion, but something that had happened in the past! In other words, these were the residual memories of this war god!

Because he stepped onto the blue stone road and stepped on a footprint, Lin Ming could see the memories of this war god. And in these memories, Lin Ming was him. He stood as this war god did, facing his enemies!

“Kill!”

Lifting the spear, the war god stepped forwards. A terrifying spear light pierced forwards, penetrating through 4-5 giants and killing them in a single strike!

For some time, ruined limbs and flesh flew everywhere. Blood rained out.

“This sort of feeling is…”

The moment the war god attacked, Lin Ming could feel everything that he did! Everything he heard, saw, and felt, were all what the war god had experienced in the past. Every movement of the war god, every flow of energy, how every Law was applied, Lin Ming experienced them from beginning to end, as if he were the one fighting!

And these flows of energy and uses of Laws all left Lin Ming bewildered. This form of combat was considerably different from what he knew!

In particular, the Laws the war god used were that of the Asura Heavenly Dao. Moreover, his Asura Heavenly Dao had the 33 Heavens’ Laws fused into it, making it incredibly mystical. What Lin Ming could comprehend was limited, but even this tiny bit of comprehension left him shaking with understanding.

The black armored war god leapt up and descended like a meteor. Every now and then he slowed down, and other times he would burst forth with an unbelievable speed, leaving nothing behind but countless afterimages.

Every movement was clear, swift, and fierce, without the slightest use of unnecessary strength. This could be called the perfect combat technique.

This combat skill combined with this powerful strength was astoundingly powerful.

“Who is this war god?”

Lin Ming couldn’t help but wonder. Could this be the mysterious Asura Road Master?

Chapter 1692B - The Blue Stone Road

The limitless blue stone road continued onwards.

Everytime Lin Ming stepped onto the next blue stone slab, he would see another battle of the black armored war god. The slaughters continued without end, the black armored war god becoming increasingly strong.

Lin Ming didn’t know who the black armored war god was. All he saw were the proud children of heaven from ancient races, geniuses of other universes, and primeval God Beasts, and all of these top existences got extinguished under the hands of the black armored war god.

In the frenzied battles, the fighting intent of the black armored war god, his mysterious and endless variations of martial arts, his skill in battle, everything was like waves of inspiration that Lin Ming slowly became aware of.

Like waves in a storm, all of this roiled within Lin Ming’s mind. Mysterious runes and the faint power of Laws entered into his flesh and blood, marking him.

This sort of awareness was unfathomably profound but also extremely vague.

Although he couldn’t understand these things any time soon, their influences still subtly changed him, greatly benefiting him.

He could clearly feel some unknown changes occurring within his body. The Asura Heavenly Dao Laws within him were even more profound and in terms of the source of thunder and fire, he had an even deeper understanding.

Even the Purple Temple Dao Palace and Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace floating within his sea of consciousness had a vast momentum that was different from before.

Walking over the blue stone road, one step at a time, Lin Ming’s surroundings changed once more. This time, he was no longer a black armored war god, but a tall man in white clothes.

The white robed man had a red dot on his forehead. He sat beneath a hundred million year old divine tree, his body seemingly fused into his surroundings.

Verdant green ribbons of energy dangled down from the boughs of the tree, lingering around the white clothed man. All sorts of life essence were slowly being absorbed by him.

This was an extremely marvelous feeling. As Lin Ming manifested as this white clothed man, all he could feel was some strange resonance occurring between the world and his flesh and blood, as if something wanted to drill out from his body.

He closed his eyes, silently comprehending…

The next step was still the white-clothed man. This white-clothed man was different from the black armored war god. There was no endless slaughter, but endless cultivation. His method of cultivation, his comprehension of Laws, they left Lin Ming feeling entirely different things and obtain a different harvest.

For a long period of time, the memories Lin Ming experienced were all of the white-clothed man.

But afterwards. There was a change in the main lead of the memories once again. This time, the owner of the memories had become a god king wielding a golden sword!

The strength of this god king was similar to the black armored ward god. A single strike of him could sunder the heavens and shatter the earth! No one could be his enemy!

Lin Ming discovered that after every section of the blue stone road, the main lead of the memories would change. Although their auras had some similarities, their appearances were different and the Laws and cultivation methods they utilized were as different as the heavens and earth.

Many of these Laws were something that Lin Ming had never experienced before. Without a doubt, these were all various aspects of the 33 Heavenly Daos!

But who were these people?

Lin Ming was puzzled. Their strength seemed around the True Divinity level, but where had so many True Divinities come from?

Could these people all have stepped within this planet-sized immortal palace in the past?

But as soon as this thought appeared in Lin Ming’s mind, he immediately refuted it. This was because the Asura level Gate of Laws was simply far too ridiculous a trial to pass; it was a heaven-defying act to perfectly cross it. Although Lin Ming couldn’t say there had never been anyone that stepped into the immortal palace since the final trial began, he at least knew that there definitely weren’t so many outstanding proud children of the heavens born in the last 10 billion years.

Could the memories of these peerless powerhouses recorded in the blue stone road have been the followers of the Asura Road Master?

If the Asura Road Master was an existence that surpassed a True Divinity, it wasn’t strange for him to have so many True Divinities subordinate to him!

Lin Ming stepped forwards, step after step. The further he walked the taller and straighter his posture seemed to become, and his aura also became far more profound.

In the midst of all these changes, a silent and hidden strength emerged from the world, trailing around Lin Ming’s body, vaguely beating in harmony with him…

Through constantly experiencing, watching, and comprehending, Lin Ming’s steps became increasingly heavy.

At the start, Lin Ming only had some rough understandings into the memories of the blue stone road. But the further Lin Ming climbed up, the more and more insights he gained from the memories.

As all of these deductions and comprehensions passed through Lin Ming’s mind, beads of sweat began to drop down his forehead. The deeper his understandings became, the more Lin Ming realized just how unfathomably mysterious these Laws were.

Slowly, mysterious runes started to appear, swallowing in all of the secret strength that wrapped around the blue stone road. These runes shined like motes of light, little stars that slowly fled into Lin Ming’s boy, vanishing into his flesh and blood without a trace.

The more Lin Ming comprehended, the stranger his aura became. Sometimes his aura was light and as simple as clouds, like he had become one with the world. Sometimes his aura was majestic and grand, and still sometimes his aura was sad and shrill, enough to make ghosts and gods shudder.

At this time, Lin Ming arrived at the end of the blue stone road. He already stood 100,000 feet high in the sky, overlooking a boundless sea of clouds beneath him.

As Lin Ming was about to step foot on this last blue stone slab, he was actually startled.

This blue stone slab seemed extremely special. It was clearly only 10 feet wide, but as it fell into Lin Ming’s eyes, it seemed endlessly spacious, wide to the point of being endless, nearly taking up the entirety of Lin Ming’s sight.

Up until now, the aura of this final blue stone slab was the most intense that Lin Ming had ever seen. Just by approaching it, even he felt terrified and at a complete loss for words.

Lin Ming wasn’t in a hurry to step foot on the final level of the blue stone road. he guessed that the special reward the Black Asura mentioned in the Gate of Laws was likely located on this final blue stone road. Even so, Lin Ming instead decided to calm himself down. Without hastening his step to find this so-called reward, he instead sat down and began meditating.

Sitting deep in meditation, Lin Ming slowly recalled all the memories he had experienced along the way here.

As Lin Ming recalled them, his mind suddenly shook!

“I know… I finally know which True Divinity supreme elders had their memories recorded in the blue stone road!” Lin Ming whispered to himself. He should have realized this earlier. Of those memories, they had been from 33 different people, no more and no less!

This number allowed Lin Ming to immediately understand who they were.

Chapter 1694 – The Final Reward

Standing on the last blue stone slab, Lin Ming finally let out a long sigh of relief.

Witnessing the final strike of the Black Asura just now, that fleeting moment had been enough to shock Lin Ming’s heart and soul.

Walking this far, Lin Ming had experienced far too many things. Many experiences had surpassed his ability to understand them. However, the scenes on the blue stone road had all allowed Lin Ming to personally feel and live through them and they had left a profound mark on his memories. By accumulating all of these experiences, they would provide a great benefit to Lin Ming in cultivating the Asura Heavenly Dao in the future.

Even if these accumulations didn’t directly enhance Lin Ming’s strength by much right now, they were undoubtedly a priceless wealth he had obtained.

However, just this wealth alone wasn’t enough to be called one of the most precious rewards in the entire final trial!

In the Gate of Laws, the reward the Black Asura mentioned should be something else.

As Lin Ming came to the end of the blue stone road, he took one more step forwards. Because this was the end, with this final step, Lin Ming stepped into the void.

After stepping into the void, Lin Ming felt his surroundings change. He had arrived into a black space filled with mist.

This black space was quiet and terrifying. As Lin Ming walked within this space he could clearly hear his breathing and heartbeat. Faintly, there were light flows of energy that wound about the black space.

These dim flows of energy came in three different colors. There was grayish black, pitch black, and dark jade. As Lin Ming felt these three flows of energy, his mind shook. One of these three flows of energy was grandmist energy!

Lin Ming cultivated the Grandmist Laws. So, he had an extremely deep understanding of grandmist energy; it was impossible for him to be mistaken.

As for the other two flows of energy, Lin Ming had once come into contact with the dark jade colored one. When he had trained at Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, he had touched upon it when he studied the Divine Dream Law.

This dark jade color energy flow was spirit source!

Grandmist energy was the source of all matter in the universe. In other words, the source of ‘essence’.

Spirit source was the source of the universe’s Heavenly Dao. In other words, the source of ‘divine’.

As for the last flow of energy, that was undoubtedly the source of all energies within the universe – genesis energy, the source of ‘energy’.

The three great source powers of the universe’s ‘essence, energy, and divine’ were all contained within this black space.

And these three source strengths slowly revolved around a singular point in space. As Lin Ming looked towards it, he could see that the space near it twisted about. In the deepest point of that space distortion, there was a single drop of viscous red liquid calmly floating about.

This drop of red liquid emitted an aura as deep and vast as the sea. The surrounding space was twisted because of the terrifying energy released from this drop of red liquid. The three source strengths revolved around this drop of red liquid, clearly stabilizing and enhancing it.

This was a drop of blood!

Moreover, this drop of blood of contained an indescribably dense aura of the Great Dao Laws. At the same time, this drop of blood also contained a terrifying energy and power of will!

The aura that this drop of blood exuded was familiar to Lin Ming. It left his mind shaking.

In these past days, as Lin Ming walked down the blue stone road, he had lived some of the past experiences of the Asura Road Master. It was like he had personally accompanied the Asura Road Master throughout his journey.

He was extremely familiar when it came to the aura of the Asura Road Master. And in front of him, that drop of blood that shined like a star, was branded with the dreadful aura of the Asura Road Master!

If he wasn’t mistaken, that drop of blood was left behind by the Asura Road Master!

Even though 10 billion years has passed, the vast essence energy and Heavenly Dao Laws contained within it hadn’t dissipated in the least!

On the contrary, after being nourished by these three source strengths of the universe, this blood drop became increasingly dense and brilliant. Facing it, one found it difficult to breathe!

“This is… the final reward of the Asura level Gate of laws? A drop of blood left behind by the Asura Road Master?”

Lin Ming clenched his fists, his heart loudly beating in his chest.

The reward the Black Asura had mentioned, one of the most precious within the entire final trial, was a drop of his blood!

After spending the last several days in the star-like immortal palace, Lin Ming had walked down the blue stone road and had experienced and lived through the memories of the Asura Road Master that had been left there. These memories gave Lin Ming new enlightenments, new feelings, allowing him to enhance his comprehension of the Laws. Although it was an extremely precious treasure, this still couldn’t allow Lin Ming to leap forwards in strength in a short period of time, nor could it fundamentally alter Lin Ming’s body and grant him a more terrifying strength or talent.

But the final reward at the end of the blue stone road, this drop of Asura’s blood, was actually completely different!

10 billion years ago, the Asura Road Master had experienced endless battles and grasped the Laws of the 33 Heavens in his hands. He stood above the 33 Heavens and had created his own road.

For such a character, every tiny particle of his skin, flesh, blood, and bones was considered a priceless treasure. Each tiny part of him was marked with the true meaning of the Laws.

In this world, there were countless legends of martial artists randomly stumbling into the tomb of a senior martial arts powerhouse, and then comprehending the true meaning of a unique martial arts from their bones, obtaining an extraordinary inheritance in the process.

And this was particularly true for an outstanding existence like Asura. Within a single drop of his blood, there were undoubtedly things contained that surpassed Lin Ming’s imagination.

Suppressing the bubbling excitement in his heart, Lin Ming stepped forwards in the void, slowly approaching the drop of Asura blood.

In the void, those three great source strengths seemed to become disturbed because of Lin Ming’s arrival. Although they seemed calm and peaceful, the truth was that they were unfathomably dangerous.

A single wisp of grandmist energy was heavier than a star. If a mortal body were to be placed within it, they would simply be crushed to nothing.

As for genesis energy, it contained an energy as fiery and wild as the sun. If this energy was poured into a martial artist’s body, that martial artist would immediately turn to steam.

And for spirit source, that was the source of all mental strength and soul force. If spirit source were to enter a martial artist’s spiritual sea and they couldn’t withstand its terrifying strength, their spiritual sea would collapse and they would turn into mindless zombies.

But now, these three wild source strengths didn’t hinder Lin Ming. Instead, they unexpectedly revolved around him, faintly nourishing his essence, energy, and divine. This caused his blood vitality to become increasingly vivid and exuberant, his inner world to become more prosperous and lush, and his soul to become even more tempered…

Lin Ming would pause for a long time after every step he took, as if he were pondering on something.

And at this time, the drop of blood suspended in the void seemed to be galvanized by something. It began to beat like a heart.

This beating tempo just happened to sync with Lin Ming’s own heartbeat. It caused all of his bloody vitality to resonate! It was like a summon calling out to Lin Ming’s bloodline, driving him forwards. This sort of feeling emerged from the depths of Lin Ming’s very being, an unexplainable feeling.

At this time, a light voice echoed out from behind Lin Ming. “Do you know what that is?”

Lin Ming was startled. He immediately turned his head.

Standing not too far behind him was a black armored warrior holding a long spear, appearing from nowhere like gods and ghosts. This black armored warrior was the Black Asura from the Gate of Laws!

Chapter 1697 – Black Dragon Spear

The sky was gray and dim, as if it had existed in a state of perpetual twilight since time immemorial.

Nine dark blood red suns hung high and hazy in the heavens, emitting a weak heat.

Hu - !

One side of the earth was covered with blazing hot winds. The winds spun and howled, scorching the earth black.

The ground was bare and desolate. Dark red peaks twisted in the distance within the heat, distorting like undulating flames in the wind.

On another side of the earth, there was a world wrapped in snow and ice. The forests, mountain ranges, rivers, everything was covered with ice. This was a world of ice, a cold and gloomy yin chill that permeated everything.

Burning heat and freezing cold, these two sides were clearly divided in this strange land even as they struggled with each other. It was a strange and marvelous sight.

A cutting slithering sound transmitted from deep within the fields of ice.

On the distant horizon, a silver mountain-like outline appeared. Upon a closer look, one could see that this was an incomparably massive silver python rapidly snaking over the round.

As it winded its way forwards, it smashed apart icebergs, leaving massive cracks in the ice sheets.

And standing atop this silver python’s head was the Divine Void Third Crown Prince. His expression was still haughty and imperious, looking down at all with disdain. The only difference was that the dragon crown on his head was crooked and his clothes were stained with blood as if he had undergone a vast slaughter battle, and the process hadn’t been easy either!

Closely following behind the Divine Void Crown Prince were two people flying through the winds. One was Duke Fullmoon and the other was a young man with thick muscles wrapped over his body and eyes that exploded with a sharp light.

This other young man had deep scars crisscrossing his body that were tainted with some black energy, as if he had been struck by some mysterious curse strength.

Duke Fullmoon also didn’t have his smiles of days past. One of his eyebrows had been ripped in half and his complexion was macabre.

After stepping into the final trial’s fourth level, the difficulty rose dramatically once more! Even a squad of outstanding martial artists would fall into perilous situations if they weren’t careful!

In these lands there were ghosts, evil races, and all sorts of monstrous beings, all of them having the terrifying strength of a World King and above!

Thus, this was the reason why some trial challengers that passed the Gate of Laws had returned to the third level even though they knew that the fourth level was abundant with lucky chances. They simply didn’t dare to continue venturing deeper in this cursed land.

Once they returned to the third level, this meant that to them, the final trial had ended.

As for Duke Fullmoon and the Divine Void Crown Prince’s squad, they were a union of power and power. Even so, after arriving on the fourth level, they had experienced cold and brutal battles!

“Crown Prince Your Highness, there is an unusual aura over there…” Duke Fullmoon said with some doubt as he looked at some place in the distance where ice and fire met together.

In that area, he could feel a demonic aura that rose to the heavens!

Standing beside the Crown Prince, a tall and burly young man took out a strange map that had been pieced together. The map illustrated a dense terrain covered with colored lines.

This was a map of the final trial that was handed out by Divine Void Divine Kingdom. In truth, using this map as a reference point wasn’t too useful, because the world of the fourth level was created by the elemental powers of metal, wood, water, fire, and earth. Each one of these elemental lands had rare treasures, and every now and then these elemental regions would shift and transform, migrating to other areas. Thus, each time this trial occurred there would be different dangers and different lucky chances.

If they were to spend a great deal of time and effort piecing together a map now, at the next final trial that map would only be 20-30% usable.

The tall and burly man frowned. He said, “Crown Prince Your Highness, Duke Fullmoon, the deeper we head into the fourth level the more dangers there will be. In the fourth level, our squad is already considered quite a ways in. In the battles just now we’ve experienced some struggles and have sustained some minor wounds. The area that Duke Fullmoon mentions is even deeper in, and if we go there we might have to face greater dangers…”

The deeper one ventured into the fourth level, the more dangers there were. But correspondingly, the better the lucky chances were!

In the middle of the fourth level, there had already been many squads that had members die because of the various dangers here. Many squads had reached the middle of the fourth level and stayed there, waiting for the entrance to the fifth level to open.

In almost every case, the entrance to the fifth level would appear in the middle of the fourth level. As for everything past that, that was a land filled with treasures and lucky chances. However, there was killing intent spread through every inch of land. The strong could journey in, but the weak had to give up.

In this final trial, there was only an extremely small number of squads that were willing to venture deep into the fourth level. As for the Divine Void Crown Prince, his squad was one of these.

The Divine Void Crown Prince’s complexion changed as he weighed the advantages and disadvantages. Riches and glory always came with danger. Lucky chances like this weren’t common, so with such a lucky chance placed in front of him, how could he be willing to leave?

After a moment of thought, the Divine Void Crown Prince gloomily said, “To cultivate the martial path is to struggle with the heavens at every step. Many people struggle to find lucky chances, and if there is a lucky chance placed in front of us and we do not try to grasp it, why do we still cultivate the martial path? Let’s go and take a look!”

As the Divine Void Third Crown Prince spoke, a brilliant light shot out from his eyes. He gazed towards the direction where that massive aura was surging out from and pointed his hand outwards.

The silver python beneath his feet was an intelligent creature and was able to feel the fluctuations in its master’s thoughts. With a loud roar, a cloud-piercing, stone-cracking sound echoed through the world as it rapidly accelerated forwards, towards the area that the Divine Void Third Crown Prince indicated. As the silver python’s massive form tore through the air, a sharp whistling sound howled out. Innumerable mountain peaks were crushed and an equal number of rivers were cut off beneath the silver python.

Duke Fullmoon and the young man launched their movement techniques and followed close behind. The young man’s name was Juku. Of the two of them, Duke Fullmoon was a World King and Juku was a half-step World King. However, Juku still possessed the combat strength of a World King.

After a quarter hour passed, the silver python’s speed slowed. They finally stopped in front of a pitch black land that was cracked and scorched.

A vast and irresistible aura transmitted from the space above this land.

In the void, the powers of freezing cold and burning flames howled as they twisted around a mountain-sized jet black rock shaped like a square.

All around this rock were mysterious giant runes, floating and sparkling.

As the Divine Void Crown Prince stood high atop the silver python, he was just able to see that at the top of this massive square rock, at the very center, was a True Dragon!

This True Dragon was pure black and only 10 feet long. The Divine Void Crown Prince had never seen such a small True Dragon before. Its body was covered with scales and it clawed at the void, roaring out as it did so. Its dark eyes flitted back and forth, as sharp and bright as lightning. A deep atmosphere of blood and death surrounded it.

The Divine Void Crown Prince was startled. Why was there a dragon here?

The final trial mystic realm had existed for 10 billion years already. It was impossible for a Black Dragon to survive for such a long time. Moreover, this Black Dragon was only 10 feet long; it was simply unthinkable!

Not only was the Divine Void Crown Prince shocked, but Duke Fullmoon and Juku were equally dumbfounded.

They glanced at each other and then back towards the Black Dragon. But as they looked again, the scene they saw was different.

What Black Dragon was there? At the center of the black rock, it was clearly a black long spear that was stabbed into the rock! This spear was covered with a vast and pure demonic strength. The demonic strength gathered together, condensing into the phantom of a Black Dragon that danced in the air.

This spear was 10 feet long and the dark spear shaft shined with an icy metallic luster. The spear head was stabbed into the center of the rock so it was impossible to see. But, even though it was stabbed into the black rock, one could still feel that it was incomparably sharp, as if it could tear apart all of space. Even from hundreds of thousands of feet away, one still felt as if the sharp point of the spear head was hanging above their head, ready to come falling down at any moment and grind one to dust. It was a feeling that left the heart racing.

“This is…”

The Divine Void Crown Prince was shocked.

Was the Black Dragon just now an illusion? Had they mistaken that dragon-shaped demonic energy for a Black Dragon?

If one of them had seen incorrectly then that might have been acceptable, but for all three of them to see the wrong thing, that was unusual!

As the saying went – divine spear like dragon. Could it be because this spear truly held the charm of a dragon, thus at first glance they had thought it to be a True Dragon?

“This is a divine spear. I fear that its grade might surpass an Empyrean spirit treasure!”

The Divine Void Third Crown Prince’s pupils shrank and his breathing became a bit ragged and loud. Greed shined in his eyes.

If Lin Ming were here he would have instantly identified that this black spear was in fact extremely similar to the dragon spear that the Black Asura had held in the Gate of Laws!

If so, then the significance of this spear was beyond extraordinary!

“Haha, to find this spear is Your Highness’ great lucky chance as well as our great lucky chance!

As Juku gripped the pieced-together map, all the muscles on his body began to bulge out.

Duke Fullmoon also gulped; after all, he too was a spear master. However, he was well aware that with the Divine Void Third Crown Prince standing right beside him, it wouldn’t be his turn for such a good thing. Still, he could drink a little of the soup afterwards.

And indeed, the Third Crown Prince said, “Don’t worry, I will not take sole possession of this spear; after all, my weapon is not a spear. I will take this spear and gift it to our Divine Kingdom and we shall be rewarded with unimaginable riches!”

The Divine Void Crown Prince was skilled in manipulating emotions and thoughts; he naturally wouldn’t do something so stupid like betraying the heart of his subordinates.

“Your Highness, allow me to fetch it!” Juku eagerly said.

“Be careful!”

The Divine Void Third Crown Prince nodded.

Juku suppressed the excitement in his heart and flew into the air. After moving forwards a thousand feet he remained high in the sky. Facing the black spear he traced his spatial ring and took out two blood red puppets. These puppets were created by a World King level puppet master and in the hands of a martial artist familiar with puppet techniques, they could display a strength at the late Divine Lord realm.

In the final trial, a late Divine Lord puppet wasn’t worth mentioning at all; it simply wasn’t much use in battle. But, using them for exploring the way was extremely useful.

Juku guessed that this Black Dragon Spear wouldn’t be easy to obtain. In order to grow up to the level he was at, he couldn’t be an idiot. If he were to recklessly try to take such a great treasure, he might be sending himself into the jaws of death. To use puppets to explore the way first was the most appropriate plan!

Woosh! Woosh!

The two puppets fired towards the Black Dragon Spear, one right one left!

As the puppets approached the Black Dragon Spear, the demonic energy gathered around the dragon spear became wild and violent. The demonic energy turned into a black dragon phantom that plunged towards the two puppets. In an instant, the two puppets were melted to nothing!

Juku was startled; he immediately took several steps back. Indeed, this spear wouldn’t be easy to take. He had to find some other method to do so.

As he was deep in thought trying to think of some other way, his complexion immediately changed. He watched blankly on as the terrifying demonic energy melted away the two puppets and then hurtled towards their puppet master like it had a mind of its own!

Chapter 1700 – Plot

At the third level of the final trial, when a martial artist received their reward they would be teleported alone to the fourth level. But, those that received the same level of rewards took around the same amount of time to do so, thus they entered the fourth level at nearly the same time. Even if they were transmitted to random locations, they could still quickly find one or two of their companions to form temporary squads.

However, for Lin Ming, because he had spent too much time on the blue stone road, he arrived much later than everyone else. By this time, many people had already been fighting for several days.

“Deeper into the fourth level… I understand…”

Lin Ming nodded at the two youths and turned around, slowly heading deeper into the fourth level.

Strong winds howled and the scent of blood filled the world. As he sped forwards, his back was as straight as a spear, standing proudly upon this desolate wasteland, filled with a heroic and daring momentum!

The nine suns in the skies slowly fell down beyond the horizon, signaling the approach of night.

Lin Ming was like a death god wandering the night. Whether it was the forests, wilderness, or glaciers, he advanced in a straight line. No matter what monsters, evil races or demonic beings came at him, he didn’t use his spear but fought them with his hands!

Like this, Lin Ming crossed past the middle of the fourth level and continued towards the back.

This was a black and red swamp. In the night, the swamp emitted a misty black fog which contained the rotting aura of peerless powerhouses and desolate ancient vicious beasts that had perished here. If a lower level martial artist were to breathe in the gas here, all the flesh of their body would melt away!

Within this terrifying black fog, a massive number of cruel and vile spirits and ghosts would be born. To a trial challenger, this was a danger zone amongst danger zones!

If a common squad were to arrive here, they would have turned tail and fled.

But Lin Ming actually walked directly into this land!

Chi chi chi!

Behind Lin Ming, the phantom of an Asura appeared. This Asura held a massive wheel in his hands, and spinning above this wheel were countless phantoms of suffering demons. This was the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel!

The Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel rose up into the air, revolving and forming a giant vortex. A tremendous amount of the black fog was sucked into the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel and refined into pure energy!

Wu wu wu ~

The ear-piercing howls of malevolent spirits rose up through the world. Because Lin Ming was recklessly swallowing up the black fog in this swamp, he had aroused the evil spirits here. Ghostly purple flames flickered as spectral beings appeared in front of Lin Ming.

A giant python corpse brought its giant head up from the rancid swamp mud. Its gaping maw emitted black gas that could melt away divine iron…

Seeing this, Lin Ming simply smiled.

These ghosts and spirits deep in the fourth level didn’t leave him disappointed. Whether it was in numbers or strength, they far surpassed the evil beings that lived in the periphery of the fourth level.

With an explosive roar, Lin Ming opened the Heretical God Force. Power erupted from his body and the phantom of the Heretical God Tree appeared behind him. The power of thunder and fire heavenly tribulation came pouring out, sparkling!

Whether it was thunder or fire, they were the nemesis of ghosts. Lin Ming wrapped himself in thunder and flames and hurtled towards these spectral spirits!

Rumble rumble rumble!

A terrifying explosion of air surged out. Flames ascended, arcs of thunder twisted about. Each and every ghost was pierced through by Lin Ming’s thunder and fire, turned to ash and sent scattering into the wind!

A terrifying strength exploded in the air. The corpse python howled as its decayed body was rapidly swallowed up by the power of Heavenly Dao Judgment’s thunder and fire!

Woosh –

With a light sound, a piece of information thrust into Lin Ming’s mind.

A thought appeared in Lin Ming’s consciousness – fourth level, completion, max!

He had completed the fourth level to the maximum possible?

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. As he slaughtered his way through the fourth level he hadn’t been paying attention to the growth of his completion rate.

When Lin Ming first passed the Asura level Gate of Laws, his completion rate had reached 45%. As for the third level, there were only rewards there; Lin Ming’s completion rate hadn’t increased.

And now, in the fourth level, Lin Ming’s completion rate rose by 15%, reaching all the way to 60%!

This number was already the maximum allowed. No matter how many more monsters he killed this number wouldn’t increase.

However, Lin Ming didn’t bother with this. The reason he came to the fourth floor was to slaughter as many enemies as possible to temper himself, not for completion percentage!

Kill!

Kill everything!

Kill! Kill! Kill!

Lin Ming wildly laughed and broke into the crowds of monsters and ghosts, his fists sweeping out. Thunder and fire howled around him as he killed ten ghosts in a single step!

……….

As Lin Ming was crazily fighting and tempering himself, deep in the fourth level, beneath the icy cold skies, the Divine Void Crown Prince and Duke Fullmoon had come to a pause.

They didn’t approach the black rock in front of them nor did they dare approach the Black Dragon Spear. But, to leave just like this wasn’t something they were willing to do.

“Your Highness, there are only a dozen or so more days until… the channel to the fifth level opens. We must find a solution as soon as possible or give up on the dragon spear.”

Duke Fullmoon explained. In truth he had already given birth to the thought of retreating. Even if he helped in obtaining the Black Dragon Spear, the advantages he would obtain would be limited.

It was better to give up on this futile quest and save his own life.

The Divine Void Crown Prince’s complexion darkened. The fourth level was shaped like a massive rectangle. The trial challengers started on one end and the further they went towards the other end, the deeper into the fourth level they would go and the greater the risks would be. Generally speaking, the passage from the fourth level to the fifth level would always appear around the middle of this rectangle.

In other words, as long as one arrived at the middle of the fourth level they would be able to enter the fifth level.

Once the channel to the fifth level opened, it would also take time to turn around and arrive at the middle.

Moreover, they had to kill a sufficient number of monsters in order to obtain the max completion percentage here. Up until now they had only slain 60% of the required monsters. They weren’t as fierce as Lin Ming who was wildly killing his way through this level. Rather, they had to be selective in choosing their enemies and avoid the terrifying fellows that lurked here.

As the Divine Void Crown Prince was lost in a dilemma, he heard a whistling sound come from the distance.

He looked up, his guard raised, to see a brilliant flame approaching from the far off horizon.

This flame blotted out the skies. In the center of these flames, a fat youth in bright yellow imperial robes was sitting on a firebird, flying over towards them.

And behind this fat youth was a young warrior covered in silver armor that radiated a dazzling light, as if his armor had been encrusted with stars.

This warrior hurtled through the sky, the air rippling around him. Visible ripples followed him in the air, clearly demonstrating his formidable strength.

“Bigflame?” The Divine Void Crown Prince’s eyes filled with disgust. At this time this tubby fellow had actually come here. Really, enemies crossed paths far too often!

However, this was also well within reason. Out of all the squads in the fourth level, there was only an extremely small number of trial challengers that had the courage to venture this far. Bigflame’s group was one such squad.

Thus, bumping into him here wasn’t a coincidence at all.

Suddenly, a ruthless hostility flashed through the Divine Void Crown Prince’s mind. He extracted his weapon, killing intent surging out from him as he faced Bigflame!

He said to Duke Fullmoon with a sound transmission, “Fullmoon, follow me and put on a good play!”

Duke Fullmoon immediately understood what was happening and extracted his weapon. The two people turned towards Bigflame, one left one right, as if they were guarding the Black Dragon Spear behind them. As they faced the disciples of Heaven Union Divine Kingdom’s Divine Sovereign as well as that amazingly strong silver armored warrior, it seemed as if they were ready to fight at any moment!

“What? You want to fight?”

Seeing Duke Fullmoon and the Divine Void Crown Prince be so vigilant, Bigflame happily smiled. “There’s no need to be so tense, we’re just a little bit disharmonious, right? There’s no need to fight as soon as we see each other! You should know that our two sides have similar strength. If we fight, it won’t be good for anyone!”

Bigflame sneered. But at this time he caught sight of the massive black rock behind Duke Fullmoon and the Divine Void Crown Prince.

As well as the Black Dragon at the top of the rock!

“Dragon!?” Bigflame was shocked. However, he immediately shook his head. “No, that’s not right! That’s a dragon spear! Hahaha! That is a treasure surpassing the level of an Empyrean spirit treasure! We’ve really struck a big lucky chance this time!”

Seeing this dragon spear, Bigflame’s eyes shone with a greedy light!

As Bigflame flanked the Divine Void Crown Prince and Duke Fullmoon who had raised their weapons, he said, “No wonder they’re being so vigilant. So it’s because there is a treasure here.”

“Bigflame, this Black Dragon Spear is already mine! You had best get out of my way!” The Divine Void Crown Prince icily said as he stared at Bigflame.

Bigflame didn’t even bother looking at the Divine Void Crown Prince; his burning gaze was locked onto the Black Dragon Spear, his emotions bubbling over with excitement.

When he entered the fourth level his group had searched for lucky chances everywhere. But up until now, they had only picked up some medicinal herbs that weren’t too precious as well as several remnant pieces of ancient cultivation methods. These harvests weren’t enough to satisfy Bigflame.

It wasn’t until he ventured deep into the fourth level that he was attracted by a vast and terrifying aura. Thus, he arrived here only to discover that the Divine Void Third Crown Prince and Duke Fullmoon had already arrived a step early.

“You two should be the ones getting out of my way! That treasures is mine and mine alone!” Bigflame’s chubby face stretched as he smiled. Then, he took out a blood red saber from his spatial ring and slashed it out. A great saber light filled the air, covering Duke Fullmoon and the Third Crown Prince.

At the same time, Bigflame launched a movement technique. His round body was unexpectedly fast, as speedy as a bolt of lightning. As Duke Fullmoon and the Third Crown Prince were covered in his saber light, he swooped down to grab the Black Dragon Spear!

His speed was incredibly fast. Just as he was about to step onto the black rock, a vague restless nervousness appeared in his heart – strange, something was wrong here… this treasure… could it really be obtained so easily?

Could the Divine Void Crown Prince have deliberately allowed him to take it!?

At this time, Bigflame suddenly caught sight of something from the corners of his eyes. There, at the wasteland below him, was the withered corpse of someone. This person’s face was already mutilated to the point of being indescribable, but what was abundantly clear was that this withered skin bag of bones was new.

This person had just died here!

Bigflame immediately felt that the situation was dire!

As the most favored direct disciple of Heaven Union Divine Kingdom’s Divine Sovereign, Bigflame was no fool. He forcefully stopped himself in midair and hastily drew backwards!

In the blink of an eye, Bigflame had returned to his original position. He hadn’t alarmed the Black Dragon Spear but his forehead was dripping with a cold sweat. Just now he had taken a trip to the gate of death!

Bigflame sneered, his eyes filling with murderous intent as he looked towards the Divine Void Crown Prince. “Hehe, what a clever plan you had!”

The Divine Void Crown Prince shrugged, “It seems you aren’t as dumb as I thought. You were actually able to see through my plans… what a pity!”

The Divine Void Crown Prince didn’t care about Bigflame. He just didn’t think that Bigflame would find a clue in the crucial moment and escape this calamity.

Bigflame savagely grinned, “What use is there in harming me? You probably couldn’t take the dragon spear yourself. On the contrary…”

As Bigflame spoke to here he sensed something and turned around. On the far off horizon, there was another swift and fierce aura rapidly approaching!

“How interesting, it seems someone else has arrived!”

Chapter 1702 – Demonic Energy Force Field

Bigflame frowned, not sure just what type of snake medicine that Divine Void Crown Prince was trying to sell.

In the current situation, Lin Ming, who was farthest away from the Black Dragon Spear, was in the safest position.

Of course, Bigflame was fully aware that the Divine Void Crown Prince was trying to trap Lin Ming. The only question was just what the Divine Void Crown Prince’s plan was. Looking at where he was currently standing, if he neared the Black Dragon Spear any more and aroused the dragon soul within, they would definitely bear the brunt of the damage.

Bigflame maintained a calm expression and slowly flew forwards with the silver-armored warrior. He maintained absolute vigilance as he did so.

At this time, the Divine Void Crown Prince was already beginning to lay down a great array formation.

He was gambling that the Black Dragon Spear would only attack those that recklessly tried to take it away; this was how Juku had died. As for the Divine Void Crown Prince and Duke Fullmoon who were standing not too far away, they had been left completely safe.

Looking at the Black Dragon Spear in the distance, the Divine Void Crown Prince also felt a little weak at heart. He had no way to predict if something would randomly occur.

He was putting his full effort into laying down this grand array formation. And indeed, his every action was meticulous because this array formation was also to save his life. Beside him, Duke Fullmoon was also helping.

“Your Highness, will Lin Ming help?”

Duke Fullmoon asked, his voice lacking confidence. He always felt that Lin Ming was a bit strange and unpredictable.

“If he does, we will turn and run and then profit from the aftermath. If he doesn’t then we’ll need to further consider our plans…”

The Divine Void Crown Prince said, his eyes not leaving the Black Dragon Spear. With this array formation supporting them, it wasn’t like they wouldn’t have the ability to resist the Black Dragon Spear. If some accident occurred they would still be able to survive for some time.

Beside them, Bigflame and the silver-armored warrior also pitched in to help. All sorts of divine runic symbols, array discs, and other treasures were brought forth like they didn’t cost money at all.

As the two sides were busy at work, Lin Ming floated behind them. His gaze was deep and heavy; it was impossible to tell what he was thinking.

As the array formation was finished, the Divine Void Crown Prince turned to look at Lin Ming, saying, “Brother Lin, we’re prepared. Please take out your puppets.”

“Puppets?”

Lin Ming smiled, still not moving.

Now, with three sides here, each side could be said to be plotting their own plans. Lin Ming also had his own intentions here.

He was trying to calculate if he were to suddenly sneak attack the Divine Void Crown Prince, Bigflame, Duke Fullmoon, and the silver-armored warrior, just what his chances would be of killing them all off!

From the start, Lin Ming didn’t plan on cooperating with them to take the spear. He wanted to kill them all off and then take the spear by himself! If so, then even if the dragon spear attacked him, Lin Ming could use up every method at his disposal to subdue the dragon spear and wouldn’t need to worry about someone ambushing him from behind.

However, even if Lin Ming tried his best, wanting to kill everyone here wasn’t possible! As long as the four of them scattered in different directions then even if Lin Ming brought forth the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone avatar, he still wouldn’t be able to chase them all down.

And if these people were to escape, news of what occurred would spread out. It would be known that he tried to kill the disciples of two True Divinity level influences. This would undoubtedly set off a great storm.

These two True Divinity level influences were the most terrifying forces in the Asura Road! Let alone their core disciples, people even didn’t dare to provoke their ordinary disciples!

If someone was discovered as having killed off their core disciples, the consequences would be disastrous!

Even if he ignored those two great influences, what Lin Ming feared the most in this final trial was the person who remained aloof and distant, but still had some connection to the Divine Void Holy Lands – Soul Empress Sheng Mei. The Divine Void Crown Prince was different from Duke Fullmoon, he was a core disciple of Divine Void Divine Kingdom. If Sheng Mei knew that he had killed off the Divine Void Crown Prince, just what sort of reaction would she have?

Thus, Lin Ming didn’t attack them, because if he did he needed to make sure he could exterminate them all.

As these thoughts percolated in Lin Ming’s mind, a thick killing intent flashed in his eyes several times. Even so, he suppressed all of these feelings and didn’t attack. Although eliminating these four people and taking the spear himself was the simplest and most direct method, he still wasn’t able to do that.

Then… there was only another choice left. First, he would try to take the spear and reveal a weakness in his defenses. Once the four people thought they had a chance and developed greedy thoughts, he would use this opportunity to kill them all off.

With this plan it was much more likely that Lin Ming would be able to exterminate the four people. But, this also meant he would have to take a much greater risk!

It was because Lin Ming didn’t completely understand this Black Dragon Spear!

“Brother Lin, are you not planning to help? Why? Could it be that Brother Lin doesn’t want to take any risks at all? If we join hands to take the treasure, aren’t Brother Lin’s actions just too insincere? We’re already standing at the front, taking on the most dangerous role, so what is Brother Lin waiting for?”

The Divine Void Crown Prince shouted at Lin Ming, putting on a face full of discontent.

Lin Ming remained silent. After some time, he faintly smiled and said, “There’s no need to hurry!”

He slowly flew forwards until he was 10,000 feet away from the Black Dragon Spear. Then, he emitted every sense possible to probe the Black Dragon Spear. He investigated the eerie and horrifying demonic energy. With this, he was able to confirm that this demonic energy wrapped around the Black Dragon Spear was the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel recorded within the Asura Sutra.

The Asura Sutra was both righteously good and diabolically evil. As for the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, it was a tyrannical demonic cultivation method, able to gather the cruel and fierce spirits for one’s own use.

“This Black Dragon Spear hasn’t obtained the true lineage of the Asura Sutra. Just how could this be…?” After probing, Lin Ming discovered that the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel displayed by the Black Dragon Spear was incomplete. There were many places that were filled with mistakes. Now that this incomplete method was being used by this evil spear, it seemed even gloomier and bizarre than the true Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel!

If it wasn’t the complete Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, then that meant there were flaws!

Lin Ming was looking for these flaws.

“Brother Lin! Why haven’t you done anything yet!”

The Divine Void Crown Prince impatiently said. He was afraid that his plan had been seen through by Lin Ming. He already decided that if Lin Ming didn’t do anything then he wouldn’t recklessly do anything to Lin Ming either. Towards this mysterious young man, he couldn’t help but feel a faint sense of dread.

“Do something? Okay!”

Lin Ming suddenly nodded, leaving the Divine Void Crown Prince surprised. Had this fellow fallen for the trap just like this?

“You finally fell for it? Wonderful! Birds die for food and people die for wealth. The nature of a person is insatiable greed to begin with, and with a lucky chance placed right in front of them, no one is capable of resisting. Even if this Lin Ming suspects me, there is finally nothing he can do to withstand the temptation of the Black Dragon Spear. If he wants to take the risk, then that’s far too good…”

The Divine Void Crown Prince rapidly thought, his mind racing. Beside him, Duke Fullmoon’s breathing also quickened, his pulse accelerated. He quietly gripped his spear, a ruthless light flashing in his eyes.

This Lin Ming wasn’t easy to deal with but that Black Dragon Spear was simply far too evil. As long as Lin Ming moved then the two tigers would battle and they could sit back and watch the fight.

Drawing back 10,000 steps, even if that Black Dragon Spear couldn’t kill Lin Ming, there wasn’t any loss to them. If the four of them joined together, then even if they didn’t have absolute confidence in killing Lin Ming, Lin Ming still wouldn’t dare to attack them.

In other words, the truth was that they were already in an invincible position!

“I will draw out the Black Dragon phantom. The lot of you protect me.”

As Lin Ming spoke, he flew towards the Black Dragon Spear.

Seeing this, the Divine Void Crown Prince’s heart skipped a beat. “Brother Lin, you don’t plan on using a puppet?”

The Divine Void Crown Prince was originally planning on having Lin Ming lure out the Black Dragon phantom with a puppet, but Lin Ming actually decided not to use a puppet but to go in himself. Could it be that he didn’t fear the dangers enough?

“To not use a puppet and fly in himself, isn’t this just a death wish?” Bigflame was shocked!

“It seems this brat only had a high level of talent, but he’s actually a moron.” The silver-armored warrior commented from beside Bigflame. It seemed they had all been too nervous about this. If they knew about this earlier then there wouldn’t have been a need to go through all this trouble.

“Don’t be careless. Who knows what tricks he’s planning to play.”

Bigflame and the Divine Void Crown Prince certainly wouldn’t believe that Lin Ming was a fool, otherwise there was no way he would have passed the Asura level Gate of Laws.

“No matter, with the four of us joined together and raising our guards, we are in an impregnable position!”

Duke Fullmoon said with a sound transmission. Out of everyone here, he had come across Lin Ming the most. Lin Ming’s previous performance at the Divine Rune City Auction had left a profound impact in his heart. After having his plans continuously torn down, Duke Fullmoon felt a lack of confidence when facing Lin Ming.

The four people stared blankly on as Lin Ming flew towards the Black Dragon Spear.

8000 feet!

5000 feet!

3000 feet!

1000 feet!

500 feet…

Lin Ming closed in, a little at a time, slowing down the closer he was. Finally, he was as slow as a walking mortal.

As he approached, his aura became increasingly deep and his eyes increasingly swift and fierce. On his face, blood red curse seals began to appear and explosive crackling sounds echoed out from within his body. He even seemed to grow taller…

Not too far away, Bigflame, Duke Fullmoon, and the others were all staring at Lin Ming with utter focus, locked onto his every move and action!

He was only 200 feet away!

The four people held their breath. Lin Ming wasn’t planning on using some trick, but was actually thinking of luring out the Black Dragon phantom that lingered around the Black Dragon Spear.

Was he insane!?!?

At this time, a black fog rose up from all around the Black Dragon Spear!

A terrifying black energy surged towards Lin Ming like a tidal wave!

Within this seething black fog was a clawing Black Dragon. Its eyes were blood red, and just by looking into its gaze, one felt as if they would fall into an endless abyss!

At this time, the Black Dragon evilly smiled. “Blood energy… a stranger’s blood energy… what a rich blood energy… what an extreme delicacy, this is the greatest delicacy that I have ever encountered, the richest blood energy I have ever seen… good! Too good! You will become my most delicious meal! You will become a part of me! Let me eat you!”

The Black Dragon’s voice was filled with deceit and ruthless cruelty. Demonic energy surged around it as its voice seemed to transmit from all directions of the world. It was like the heavens and earth were shrouded in this voice!

For a time, Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. He discovered that he was covered in a massive force field!

This force field was like an independent space. There was nothing but pitch black darkness everywhere. If he reached out his hand, he wouldn’t even be able to see his five fingers!

Wu! Wu! Wu! Wu! Wu! Wu! Wu!

Horrifying ghost cries sounded from all directions. This was like a cave of 10,000 ghosts. Just by entering this land, one would be swallowed up by 10,000 ghosts!

“This is a domain sent out by the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, formed from the countless demonic souls that it has absorbed. This Black Dragon Spear, just how many people has it killed? Moreover, all of these people are outstanding existences!”

Lin Ming’s mind chilled. Without a doubt, this Black Dragon Spear had existed in the final trial for a very, very long time! It had also slain a tremendous number of trial challengers!

But, what was strange was that Soul Empress Sheng Mei should also have come here, so why didn’t she subdue this Black Dragon Spear?

With Soul Empress Sheng Mei’s transcendent methods, no matter how strong or ghostly this Black Dragon Spear’s methods were, it still wouldn’t be able to escape her grasp!

Chapter 1703 – Deal

But at this moment, Lin Ming didn’t have time to think about why Soul Empress Sheng Mei didn’t come here to subdue the Black Dragon Spear. The thick black fog had already surrounded him.

With a sizzling sound, even space itself was being melted away by the black fog!

Lin Ming was covered within the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel domain, completely separated from the world. In his field of vision, the Divine Void Crown Prince and Duke Fullmoon had both vanished.

“He’s been surrounded by that black fog!” Ten thousand feet away, the Divine Void Crown Prince saw all of this happening, a sharp light shining in his eyes! “This brat, I have no idea what sort of mental problems he has. If he used a puppet to draw out the Black Dragon phantom then we’d still have to put in a great deal of effort, but now that he has been directly sucked up by the black fog, that is much more convenient for us. That black fog has a terrifying corrosive attribute, and any flesh and blood that touches it will instantly be dissolved into goo. When Juku was covered in that black fog, he instantly withered away to nothing but skin and bones!”

Juku’s strength was similar to that of a World King. The Divine Void Crown Prince didn’t doubt that Lin Ming was stronger than Juku, but no matter how strong Lin Ming was he wouldn’t be stronger than a half-step Empyrean. As long as he was covered by that black fog, it would be impossibly difficult for him to escape unscathed.

Standing beside the Divine Void Crown Prince, Duke Fullmoon also looked on with disbelief etched on his face. “Something’s wrong. This Lin Ming is a freakishly monstrous genius, so how would he die so easily?”

Duke Fullmoon muttered. His sense was blocked out by that black fog so it was impossible for him to probe Lin Ming’s situation.

The Divine Void Crown Prince said, “He definitely won’t die so easily. I think he must have some sort of special technique and wants to rely on this to struggle with the Black Dragon Spear. However, he likely doesn’t know just how fierce that dragon spear actually is. In the fourth level of this final trial, what is tested is not just talent, but also one’s cultivation!”

The final trial’s first, second, and fourth level were trials that didn’t discriminate. Those with higher cultivations would be able to profit more.

As for the Gate of Laws, that was a test of talent. Those with a younger skeletal age would have an advantage.

In the Divine Void Crown Prince’s eyes, Lin Ming was truly a monstrous talented genius, but in terms of cultivation and combat strength, Lin Ming likely wasn’t much better than they were. If he were to encounter a ghostly spirit treasure like this Black Dragon Spear, he would fall into crisis along with the rest of them.

Even if he had some special card in hand that he could use to escape, he would likely come out half-dead. At that time, it would be far easier for them to eliminate Lin Ming.

“Lin Ming underestimated his opponent too much. He is young and full of daring energy, so he likely hasn’t received many setbacks on his way to where he is. He thinks that no one can match him in this world, that he can obtain anything he wants!”

“We must prepare our attacks. At this time, we absolutely cannot allow Lin Ming to escape! Everyone, use your ultimate techniques, whatever trump cards you have hidden up your sleeves! This is our good fortune!”

It wasn’t just the Divine Void Crown Prince, but Bigflame was also making his preparations. If Lin Ming was swallowed up by that black fog and reduced to dregs then that would be far better for them, but if Lin Ming managed to wriggle his way loose then they would display a thunderous barrage of attacks to exterminate him!

At this time, they all brought out their ultimate techniques without holding anything back. And to give them their due, each of these people had astonishing methods!

They were people that came from True Divinity influences and would always have some final trump card for desperate situations. Even if Lin Ming was in his peak state and facing these four people, he would have to evade their all-out attack. If he were to meet their barrage head on he would die or be severely wounded!

Chi chi chi!

A terrifying amount of energy began to slowly brew in the hands of the four people.

The Divine Void Crown Prince took out an incarnation jade slip. This jade slip possessed the avatar phantom of an Empyrean. However, in order to activate this incarnation, that would depend on the Divine Void Crown Prince’s cultivation and strength.

As for Bigflame, he took out a strange little flag. This small flag burned with vague black flames; it was clear that this was some terrifying treasure!

Although Duke Fullmoon and the silver-armored warrior possessed trump cards that were inferior to those of the Divine Void Crown Prince and Bigflame, what they had still allowed them to increase their overall strength by half over their peak state for a short period of time!

With these four attacks striking together, even a peak Great World King would have to earnestly face it without any hint of holding back!

And at this time, 10,000 feet away, the black fog sent out by the Black Dragon Spear became increasingly strong and thick.

This black fog carried with it a demonic energy, and as the Divine Void Crown Prince said, it also possessed a dreadful corrosive attribute. If a World King were to touch it they would immediately die, without any chance of survival! If the Divine Void Crown Prince or Bigflame were to have any part of their body be tainted by this energy they would have to cut off that body part lest their entire body rot away!

Although Lin Ming was stronger than the Divine Void Crown Prince, he wasn’t ridiculously stronger. Facing this black fog, he also wasn’t able to withstand it with his mortal body.

Thus, Lin Ming summoned his own Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel!

The black fog around the Black Dragon phantom was the power of Laws gathered by the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. Moreover, the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel used by the Black Dragon phantom was incomplete.

Now, the complete Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel summoned by Lin Ming was the ultimate nemesis of this black fog!

Wu – wu – wu –

Countless demonic phantoms rapidly spun within the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. On the surface of the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, a giant black vortex appeared. A massive amount of the demon energy left behind by the powerhouses that died here, their force fields, will, remnant souls, everything was recklessly sucked in by Lin Ming’s Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel!

Lin Ming was using his own Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel to wildly plunder the demonic essence within the Black Dragon phantom’s Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel!

Seeing this occur, the Black Dragon phantom was enraged!

This demonic energy essence was gathered from slaughtering countless outstanding geniuses over the course of billions of years, and yet this energy was being wantonly swallowed up by Lin Ming! How could it not be angry!

“Stop!!!”

With a roar, the black fog in front of Lin Ming distorted, condensing into the form of a cruel and wicked dragon, its eyes blood red and its expression fierce and grotesque!

Lin Ming remained unmoved and the motions of his hands didn’t slow. At the same time, the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel separated him and this Black Dragon phantom, forming a shield that blocked it off.

“You are seeking death!”

The Black Dragon phantom roared, opening its jaws and spitting out blood red runes. These runes spun through the void, dazzling to the eyes.

“I curse you! I curse your cultivation to fall, your blood essence to be severed!

“I curse you! I curse you forever, to perish for eternity, to never have a peaceful end!

“I curse you! I curse you to perish here, for your soul to suffer the agony of 10,000 lives in hell!”

The Black Dragon phantom loudly chanted. These blood runes it spat out were actually a secret curse technique!

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank and he traced his spatial ring, pulling out three deep red divine runic symbols. Without hesitation, he crumbled all three divine runic symbols together!

Rumble rumble rumble!

Terrifying waves of thunder and flame wildly surged outwards, producing a cataclysmic explosion!

These three divine runic symbols were Heretical God Symbols that Lin Ming had drawn up. A normal Heretical God Symbol could be used several times, but the Heretical God Symbols that Lin Ming prepared for this final trial could only be used once.

He had concentrated every ounce of strength of the Heretical God Symbol into a single use. With this, the might of this Heretical God Symbol was twice that of an ordinary one!

Now that Lin Ming burned three Heretical God Symbols together, an unimaginable amount of energy erupted!

The power of thunder and fire swelled outwards like a tsunami! Whether it was thunder or flames, they were strengths that suppressed dark and ghostly powers the most. All of the curse seals that floated in the air were torn to nothing by Lin Ming’s power of thunder and fire!

At the same time, changes began to occur around Lin Ming’s body. The curse seals covering his face became deeper and brighter in color. Black scales appeared on his body. With a punch of his fist, the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel howled outwards!

After throwing out three Heretical God Symbols, Lin Ming launched another attack with his body. This was the advantage of divine runic symbols; they minimized the strength that a martial artist used!

Whorl whorl whorl!

The Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel wildly spun about. Like a massive spinning saw, it went slashing down at the Black Dragon phantom!

The Black Dragon phantom was violently angered. As it looked at Lin Ming’s Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, it reached out with its claws!

Ka ka ka!

The Black Dragon phantom’s claws crashed into the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. With a loud sound, black light transmitted in all directions!

The Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel was a tyrant that suppressed forces like ghosts, demonic spirits, and will bodies. And, this Black Dragon phantom was nothing but a body of will; it simply wasn’t able to do anything to the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. As it lashed out with its claws, the most it could do was just barely manage to send Lin Ming’s Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel spinning away. As for its claws, they dimmed down. It was clear that it suffered considerable damage just now.

“Who are you, where are you from? Why would you understand the Asura Heavenly Dao!?”

The Black Dragon phantom’s eyes were icy cold. The atmosphere around it became increasingly fierce and dangerous as it burned more and more demonic energy within its body, seeming as if it would go all-out at any moment!

The Black Dragon phantom never imagined that it would encounter someone who understood the Asura Heavenly Dao. Because of this, it was being suppressed in every aspect!

It wasn’t too strong in itself. Its strength lay in the demonic energy that it had gathered over billions of years – in other words, the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. By using the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, it was able to melt away the flesh and blood of its enemies.

The heavier the demonic energy gathered by the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, the stronger it would become. Moreover, the Black Dragon phantom had only killed outstanding geniuses. With such a terrifying level of demonic energy gathered onto it, even someone like Juku had instantly died!

But Lin Ming wasn’t affected by these tricks. Lin Ming also possessed the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel and his boundary of the Laws was higher. Because of this, the demonic energy released by the Black Dragon phantom became Lin Ming’s vitalizing tonic instead!

“And where did you come from? Your Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, where did you learn it?”

Lin Ming asked in reply. As he spoke, the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel in his hands sucked in more and more demonic energy condensed by the Black Dragon phantom. This caused Lin Ming’s Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel to become increasingly lifelike, increasingly powerful!

Seeing this, the Black Dragon phantom’s eyes turned bright red as if they would drip blood at any moment. “I am the guardian of the Black Dragon Spear! Stop your actions now, otherwise I will kill you even if I must sacrifice all my cultivation!”

As the Black Dragon phantom roared, Lin Ming simply sneered, not caring about such threats. However, the movements of his hands indeed slowed down and the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel’s absorption of the surrounding demonic energy nearly came to a halt. “I’m fine to stop here, but I want to make a deal with you!”

“Deal? Fine, then give me the complete Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel cultivation method!”

As the Black Dragon phantom spoke, both fear and greed filled its eyes as it looked at the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel in Lin Ming’s hands. It recognized that Lin Ming’s Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel was clearly of a much higher boundary in Laws and completion!

The Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel was far too significant for the Black Dragon phantom in gathering demonic energy; it naturally wanted the complete cultivation method.

Chapter 1706 – To Use Another’s Knife To Kill

As a spiritas, Duke Fullmoon’s strongest offensive abilities were soul attacks. Thus, when he fought, there would ordinarily be soul attacks within his strikes.

Wanting to block Duke Fullmoon’s physical strike wasn’t difficult at all. But, wanting to keep off his soul attack was different. Many enemies of his had fallen beneath this strange soul attack.

When Duke Fullmoon and Lin Ming clashed, the soul attack had already struck Lin Ming. According to all previous occurrences, even if Duke Fullmoon couldn’t immediately kill his opponent, they should still suffer soul damage and lose their consciousness for a short period of time. During this, Duke Fullmoon could seize the chance to strike again and obtain absolute victory.

However, he never imagined that Lin Ming would appear completely unaffected. This shocked Duke Fullmoon.

“You… do you have some soul defense Empyrean spirit treasure?”

Duke Fullmoon said, his voice wavering. He was already wallowing in fear. He could faintly feel that here, today, he might die!

Lin Ming’s strength far surpassed his imagination. Even if the Divine Void Crown Prince and Bigflame had the ability to pierce through the Myriad Demon domain, he still wouldn’t be able to last until then.

Duke Fullmoon wasn’t too old and he had a grand and glorious future awaiting him. There was even a slight chance for him to step into the Empyrean realm. To Duke Fullmoon, death was an incomparably frightening matter!

“Lin Ming! Although I have opposed you many times, I have never tried to truly harm you. If you let me go, I will allow you to place a slave seal within me. I am willing to be your faithful servant.”

Duke Fullmoon said with a sound transmission. This startled Lin Ming. Generally speaking, martial artists would rather die than live on as mindless slaves without any personality of their own, but Duke Fullmoon actually took the initiative to offer himself up. This made Lin Ming have an even lower opinion of him.

And at this time, a flash of cold brilliance shined in Duke Fullmoon’s eyes. His body leapt up like a serpent as a glimmer of purple flickered between his eyebrows.

In that instant, he had burnt a wisp of his divine soul!

When a martial artist combusted their blood essence they could exchange it for a boost of power. But a spiritas had an even more ruthless ability than burning one’s blood essence, and that was burning their divine soul!

This was because the divine soul was the very life essence of a spiritas. Once a spiritas burnt their divine soul they would receive permanent damage that was nearly impossible to recover from. In order to survive, Duke Fullmoon actually chose to burn his divine soul.

Absolute hate burst out from within Duke Fullmoon’s eyes. Originally he had some chance of stepping into the Empyrean realm, but burning his divine soul now was the same as giving up any hopes of becoming an Empyrean. Unless he had a massive lucky chance in the future it would be impossible for him to make a breakthrough.

All of this was thanks to Lin Ming. How could he not hate Lin Ming to the bones?

As long as there was life there was hope. In order to survive this disaster, Duke Fullmoon had bet everything!

The moment that Duke Fullmoon burnt his divine soul, the silver-armored saint warrior burnt his blood essence. Both of them attacked Lin Ming!

His saber cut through the void. 12 stars shined within the saber light, like a river of stars that was falling down, covering all!

Seeing this scene, Lin Ming stepped back and directly took out the Primordius Bell!

As Lin Ming stepped into the half-step Holy Lord realm, his ability to control an Empyrean spirit treasure became increasingly skilled.

Clang!

The Primordius Bell sounded out. The loud ring of a bell echoed, carrying with it the bass of the Great Dao as it shook the world!

Although Lin Ming didn’t fear Duke Fullmoon or the silver-armored warrior, the two of them were risking their lives with their attacks and it was impossible for him to disregard their strikes. After all, he had another enemy waiting in the shadows, and that was the Black Dragon phantom.

If he were to retaliate with all his strength, he might give the Black Dragon phantom a chance to attack.

Rumble rumble rumble!

A wild power fell onto the Primordius Bell like crashing waves. Duke Fullmoon’s divine soul attack was extremely cunning and slippery; it was able to seep into the Primordius Bell’s sound waves and attack Lin Ming’s spiritual sea.

But after being weakened by the sound waves, this attack wasn’t able to pose any threat to Lin Ming.

The moment that Lin Ming’s spiritual sea was besieged by the soul attack, the soul attack was destroyed by Lin Ming’s blue soul large success battle spirit, immediately disintegrating.

Lin Ming retreated again and again. Within the Primordius Bell he was able to block off the majority of the impact from the attacks so that his body didn’t suffer any damage at all!

“Damn it! Damn it all!”

Duke Fullmoon was so harried that he nearly vomited blood. His all-out attack wasn’t even able to injure Lin Ming in the least. This sort of feeling was simply indescribable.

“It’s a shame, but why don’t you just die here…”

Lin Ming’s fingers flickered as the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel appeared above his head, constantly spinning around. Countless Asura Law runes floated around it, lending it a strange mystical atmosphere.

Lin Ming planned to kill Duke Fullmoon and the silver-armored warrior as soon as possible. As long as he killed these two and only Bigflame and the Divine Void Crown Prince were left over, even if they tried to escape in separate directions Lin Ming had the confidence that he could stop them both!

And at this time, changes were occurring on the other side of the battlefield. The Divine Void Crown Prince and Bigflame discovered that Fullmoon and the silver-armored warrior weren’t able to last much longer!

“We don’t have any time; this is our only chance. Otherwise, once Lin Ming kills Brightmoon and your follower, he will join together with the Black Dragon phantom to kill us both. We will both undoubtedly die then!”

“We have to break through this Myriad Demon enchantment!”

The Divine Void Crown Prince grit his teeth as he spoke and burnt a wisp of his divine soul. As he did this, he felt a stabbing pain in his heart. No matter how much he regretted this, he had no other choice.

His entire body was covered in a golden glow. Behind him, nine halos formed, as if he were some divine being!

Chi chi chi!

The void itself was pierced through by this soul force. The Divine Void Crown Prince’s eyes had turned a deep blood red. And beside him, Bigflame also burned his life essence!

To the saint race, their blood essence was no less important than the divine soul was to the spiritas!

These two people had truly gone all out.

And at this time, not too far away from them, the Black Dragon phantom playfully smiled. It slowly manifested its main body in the void, constantly forming runes with its claws to reinforce the Myriad Demon enchantment.

The originally thick Myriad Demon enchantment became even thicker, as thick as the crust of a world, impregnable!

“Jejejeje! How naïve! Too naïve! Do you think that with the power you have from burning your blood essence and divine soul, you will have the strength to break through my illusion? This is the demonic energy that I’ve spent billions of years gathering! Once I lay down my Myriad Demon domain, not even a peak Great World King can hope of leaving!”

The Black Dragon phantom wildly cackled, its voice grating on the senses! It was like it simply didn’t care about the Divine Void Crown Prince and Bigflame’s final attack.

At this time, Bigflame and the Divine Void Crown Prince looked at each other and nodded.

“Strike!”

The two shouted together. With this, they lashed out!

As they burnt their blood essence and divine soul, they each also took out a jade slip from their spatial rings. One jade slip was shimmering purple and the other was blood red!

These were incarnation jade slips left behind by Empyrean powerhouses from their influences. Once they used them they could summon an Empyrean phantom. For a short time, they would be able to contend with a weaker Great World King!

And at this time, as if their minds were linked, Bigflame and the Divine Void Crown Prince began to galvanize the powers within the incarnation jade slips. These two jade slips wildly shook as the energy structures within revolved to the limit. The two Empyrean incarnations summoned by the two jade slips began to rapidly inflate!

They wanted to have these two jade slips explode together!

Originally, the incarnations within the jade slips were equal to a weaker Great World King. But if they exploded, releasing all the energy at once, this strike was absolutely comparable with the all-out attack of a peak Great World King!

“Attack!”

In that instant, Bigflame and the Divine Void Crown Prince changed the trajectory of their strikes. They no longer attacked the Myriad Demon domain’s enchantment, but the Black Dragon phantom’s main body!

Humm!

The two jade slips violently trembled. Two geniuses from True Divinity influences both used their ultimate trump cards without holding anything back! Bigflame took out a longan-sized blood red pill from his spatial ring and swallowed it down. After swallowing this pill, all of the muscles on his body began to grow and his appearance became cruel and fierce. His originally fat and round body became slender and filled with dense muscles like a cheetah as he hurtled towards the Black Dragon phantom.

When Bigflame attacked, he completed his body metamorphosis using a secret technique. Amongst the saints there were several bloodlines that had the ability to metamorphosize one’s body, and Bigflame was one such person!

They had already calculated that the Black Dragon phantom was using all of its demonic energy to arrange the Myriad Demon enchantment.

If so, then to attack the Myriad Demon enchantment at this time was the stupidest route possible to take. The most likely result of that would have been the failure of everything they tried!

But if they attacked the Black Dragon phantom’s main body then the result would be completely different!

Since the Black Dragon phantom had released the majority of the demonic energy in its body, that meant its main body was at its weakest point.

As long as they could exterminate this Black Dragon phantom then the Myriad Demon domain would collapse all on its own!

But at this time, the Black Dragon phantom didn’t reveal any worry at all. It smirked, laughing as it said, “It seems you’ve finally come up with a plan to break through my Myriad Demon domain. Not bad, you two don’t seem as stupid as you look. But what a pity – do you think your attack will be able to touch me?”

The Black Dragon phantom cackled and its body disappeared like ghosts and gods as it turned tail and ran.

“Chase after it!”

The Divine Void Crown Prince and Bigflame were both enraged. After paying such a deep price for this attack, how could they allow the Black Dragon phantom to escape?

Their attacks, along with the exploding Empyrean incarnations, changed directions and chased after the Black Dragon phantom!

Every sense within their body had already locked onto the Black Dragon phantom. They swore that no matter what, they would kill it! They only had this one chance to do so! If they failed then they would both die without a doubt!

However, as the Black Dragon phantom fled, it changed its trajectory once more.

Duke Fullmoon and the silver-armored warrior’s complexions changed as they discovered this. As they were engaged in a brutal battle with Lin Ming, they noticed that the Black Dragon phantom, Bigflame, and the Divine Void Crown Prince were all heading towards Lin Ming!

And they weren’t too far away from Lin Ming!

As Lin Ming saw this, his vision turned dark as he looked at the Black Dragon phantom.

“Hahahaha! You brat, I’ve lured the attacks of these two people, their exploding Empyrean incarnations, and my main body to attack you all at once! This is the trap that I’ve especially set up for you. Not let me see just how you can escape from this! You wanted to use me as your spear and kill these four people, subdue the Black Dragon Spear, and even destroy me while you were at it. Do you think I am a fool!? You want to plot against me? Why don’t you just die instead!”

Chapter 1707 – Outplayed

The Black Dragon phantom had already been calculating how to deal with Lin Ming. Because Lin Ming possessed the complete Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, the Black Dragon phantom’s demonic energy was useless against him. And without the demonic energy, the Black Dragon phantom simply couldn’t do anything to Lin Ming.

In this sort of situation, how could the Black Dragon phantom wholeheartedly cooperate with Lin Ming to kill the Divine Void Crown Prince and the others?

Wasn’t that just digging its own grave?

However, Lin Ming swallowed in a massive amount of demonic energy using his Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. This demonic energy had cost the Black Dragon phantom hundreds of millions and even billions of years to condense. Because of this, the Black Dragon phantom couldn’t help but admit defeat for now and not struggle with Lin Ming.

Thus, joining forces temporarily was a helpless choice that the Black Dragon phantom was forced to make.

From the very moment that the Black Dragon phantom attacked the Divine Void Crown Prince and the others, he had been thinking about how to utilize them to attack Lin Ming. It had then deliberately used the Myriad Demon domain to surround the Divine Void Crown Prince and the others, making them feel as if they were in a hopeless situation. Then, underneath their bubbling desperation they would definitely all bring out their ultimate techniques.

After that, the Black Dragon phantom would intentionally reveal its main body in order to guide Bigflame and the Divine Void Crown Prince into attacking it. Only like this could it rely on their strength to be the knife used to kill others, dealing Lin Ming a fatal blow!

After killing Lin Ming, Duke Fullmoon and the silver-armored warrior would be caught up in the chaos and likely die in the aftermath.

As for the Divine Void Crown Prince and Bigflame, they definitely wouldn’t be any better off. They would have inevitably severely wounded their origin energy. At that time, escaping from the Myriad Demon enchantment would be nothing more than a dream!

The Divine Void Crown Prince, Bigflame, Duke Fullmoon, the silver-armored warrior, and even Lin Ming, the five of them together would become food for the Black Dragon phantom!

If it could swallow up so many outstanding talents, it would be tremendously beneficial!

As for the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel that Lin Ming already brought out, it would also become one of the Black Dragon phantom’s spoils of war. In the future, the Black Dragon phantom could meditate on this Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. Although it wouldn’t be able to discern the complete Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel cultivation method from this, it could still improve the method it used to gather and condense demonic energy.

This was a good plan with multiple purposes. As long as it succeeded, every advantage would be its own!

After cultivating for another stretch of time, it could then take possession of the Black Dragon Spear and use the spear as its body, roaming through the world. It could transform into a person, an ancient vicious beast, or even a God Beast, becoming a ruler of its own territory!

These were all plans that the Black Dragon phantom had been secretly plotting for. It had placed the Divine Void Crown Prince and the others in its palms. Even Lin Ming was placed in the perfect death trap!

Of course, the premise of all this was that its attack could kill Lin Ming!

The Black Dragon phantom wasn’t worried about this; this was because the Divine Void Crown Prince and Bigflame had given it surprise after surprise. They actually intended on exploding the Empyrean incarnations they brought with them, combined with the attacks of their main bodies. In addition to the Black Dragon phantom’s own attack, these three forces joined together would even lay low a peak Great World King!

It was impossible for Lin Ming to block all of this!

Of course, the Black Dragon phantom didn’t forget Lin Ming’s spirit treasure – the Primordius Bell!

The Black Dragon phantom had a vivid memory of the terrifying defensive capabilities of this spirit treasure.

It chose to reveal its main body the moment Lin Ming summoned the Primordius Bell, all so that it could cut off Lin Ming’s final thread of hope!

Every step of this plan had been meticulously prepared. It was evil and sinister to the extreme!

“Myriad Demon domain!”

The Black Dragon phantom roared out. Demonic energy gushed out like a falling star, turning into countless runes that sealed the space around Lin Ming’s Primordius Bell!

Using its domain, it forcefully separated Lin Ming and the Primordius Bell!

At the same time, the space around Lin Ming was blocked off by the domain. The demonic energy condensed into thick black ropes that wrapped around Lin Ming!

With this, let alone using the Space Laws to escape, it would be difficult for him to open his spatial ring.

The demonic energy that the Black Dragon phantom condensed was extremely firm. No matter how Bigflame or the Divine Void Crown Prince tried to attack it, they hadn’t been able to break through it. As for Lin Ming, although he could use the Asura Laws to dissolve this demonic energy, it would still take him some time to do so.

But, the Black Dragon phantom absolutely would not give Lin Ming the slightest chance to recover!

“Die!”

After sealing away the Primordius Bell and eliminating all avenues of escape or resistance, the Black Dragon phantom roared out, its body suddenly ballooning.

Within a split-second, it grew to a hundred feet in length. It opened its gaping jaws, gray flames gushing forth from its maw. These gray flames swept up into the exploding Empyrean incarnations that had reached their critical stage. All of these attacks joined together and went rumbling towards Lin Ming!

As long as Lin Ming was caught up in this attack, he would definitely die here!

Facing this strike that blotted out the skies, Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with a cold light!

He tried to move the Primordius Bell, but because the Primordius Bell was being suppressed by the demonic energy it remained completely still.

“Don’t bother wasting your energy! Today you will die here!”

The Black Dragon phantom roared out. Even as it was suppressing the Primordius Bell, it was also luring the exploding attacks of the Divine Void Crown Prince and Bigflame. With this, the Black Dragon phantom had exhausted all of its strength for this moment. It had to succeed!

But at this moment, a great feeling of dread welled up from within the Black Dragon phantom’s heart, as if some massive danger was imminent!

“Did I forget something!?”

The Black Dragon phantom was startled. But at this time it could no longer take back its strike. It could only continue forwards with everything it had.

In that moment, 30 feet away from the Black Dragon phantom, the void was torn open. A man appeared, his entire body covered with black scales and his face emblazoned with blood red runes. He was an Asura death god, stepping out from a tear in space!

This Asura death god had a cruel and ominous expression. Even so, one could clearly make out Lin Ming’s appearance. This was what Lin Ming looked like after he underwent a body metamorphosis using the power of the Asura blood!

At this time, Lin Ming’s entire body was exuding energy. Killing intent rolled off him in tumbling waves.

He grasped a black spear and looked at the Black Dragon phantom with a mocking indifference. This gaze was as if Lin Ming was already looking at something dead!

“You… you… how is this possible!?”

Because the Black Dragon phantom had invested all of its strength into the Myriad Demon domain and also attacking Lin Ming, its main body was completely undefended!

Facing Lin Ming’s attack, it had absolutely no chance of resisting it!

“Who the hell is that!?”

The Black Dragon phantom suddenly turned to look at the ‘Lin Ming’ that it was luring the barrage of attacks towards. That Lin Ming remained indifferent as he held onto the Phoenix Blood Spear. Facing this volley of attacks that overwhelmed the skies, he seemed not to care at all.

“An illusion!?”

The Black Dragon phantom first thought that Lin Ming had used an illusion to trick it. But, this was impossible. How could an illusion engage Duke Fullmoon and the silver-armored warrior in such a chaotic battle? Moreover, how could it transfer power from so much energy and Laws? And whether it was the aura of the first Lin Ming’s body or the second Lin Ming’s body, they had exactly the same fluctuations of energy as someone real. The Black Dragon phantom simply wouldn’t make such a basic mistake.

How could this be!?

“It’s regretful. All of your plans were perfect, but what you didn’t know what that I had an avatar! When I first proposed to make a deal with you, did you think I wouldn’t know you were planning on killing me? But, although I knew you had some little trick up your sleeves, the only problem was estimating when you would sneak attack me. Moreover, you are nothing but a sinister and sly little creature. If you were to ambush me, the only time you would do so is if you had full confidence you would succeed. If that were to happen when I wasn’t paying attention, then all my plans might have been flipped over!

“Thus, after we came to an agreement and you withdrew your Myriad Demon force field, I had to cover myself in the Primordius Bell to defend against the joint attacks of the four. But while I was in there, I also exchanged myself with my avatar!

“My avatar has a mortal bodily intensity approaching that of a saint race Empyrean! It simply doesn’t fear any attack! After switching out my main body, there was no longer any need for me to dread your little tricks and sneak attacks. My main body has been hiding all this time in order to guard against all possible contingencies!

“I left the Phoenix Blood Spear and Primordius Bell to my avatar, and even left my battle spirit in my avatar’s spiritual sea. Then, I remotely activated the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel in order to assist my avatar in attack. All of this was so that you wouldn’t have any suspicions against me. Then, the moment when you attacked me, that would be the moment I killed you instead! Now, all of your demonic energy has been used for other purposes, so how will you block my all-out attack?”

Although Lin Ming’s explanation seemed long, it took a mere instant for all of this to appear in the Black Dragon phantom’s mind.

In that moment, the Black Dragon phantom wildly trembled!

When Lin Ming covered himself in the Primordius Bell he had already switched himself for his avatar! Lin Ming’s main body went into the Primordius Bell, but it was his avatar that had emerged!

In other words, its carefully planned strike was all done against Lin Ming’s avatar!

“Ahhhhh!”

The Black Dragon phantom wildly roared. It had lived for countless eons and had used countless methods to gather countless accumulations. It was an utterly sinister and deceitful being, but today, facing a junior, it was actually the one that had been tricked instead!

“I am unwilling!”

The Black Dragon phantom roared out, its voice shrill and desperate. Lin Ming didn’t give it any chance to recover. He immediately thrust his spear forwards!

This black spear was the one Lin Ming obtained from the Gate of Laws. Although it couldn’t increase his strength it was still incomparably hard. There was almost nothing that could destroy it!

At the time, Lin Ming had brought this black spear out with him from the Asura level Gate of Laws and had conveniently kept it with him. Now, it finally came in handy!

Lin Ming opened the Heretical God Force to the limit. The power of thunder and fire heavenly tribulation was poured into the black spear. At the same time he also galvanized the power of the Asura Heavenly Dao and Divine Seal Art!

A swirling black hole was shot out by Lin Ming. Space warped as the area around the Black Dragon phantom was locked down!

The Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel hummed as it was summoned forth by Lin Ming. The Asura Heavenly Dao just happened to be the ultimate nemesis of the Black Dragon phantom.

Then, all of this strength erupted together!

The Black Dragon phantom miserably cried out again and again. Beneath the horrifying blaze of this energy, its body was scorched to smoke, nearly extinguishing to nothing!

The Black Dragon phantom roared in pain. Its body turned into countless fragments as it desperately tried to struggle free and flee. However, how could Lin Ming give it such a chance?

Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel!

Ka ka ka ka!

The black Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel came pressing down. This wheel was supremely skilled in suppressed the power of ghosts and spirits. It could imprison the wills and souls of powerhouses.

Then, a black vortex appeared above the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. The fragments of the Black Dragon phantom were all sucked up into this vortex, instantly sealed away!

The Black Dragon phantom pitifully roar. Through all these years it had kept hidden within the Black Dragon Spear, swallowing the flesh and blood of countless proud children of heaven, and then using the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel to seal in their souls. It never imagined that one day it would be the one sealed away by the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel!

Chapter 1710 – Swallowing the Memories

“Oh? I won’t be able to obtain the Black Dragon Spear if I kill you?” Lin Ming looked towards the Black Dragon phantom and clasped his hands behind his back as if he simply didn’t care about its threat.

The Black Dragon phantom diabolically grinned. Since it was imprisoned by Lin Ming, it knew that escape was futile so it gave up its struggles. “That’s right, if you don’t believe me then you can try yourself. I used a full billion years to take the Black Dragon Spear as a foundation to lay down the Myriad Demon Grand Array. Within this array formation, there is an amount of demonic energy as vast as the sea. For these past several billion years I have been constantly killing off trial challengers to accumulate their energy, otherwise why do you think I would bother!”

“Oh? So that’s how it is…”

Before this, Lin Ming had already discovered that the Black Dragon phantom itself wasn’t too strong. But, using the demonic energy it gathered it was able to instantly kill a top master like Juku. However there was a condition in order to accomplish this, and that was that it had to be within a certain range of the Black Dragon Spear. In other words, it had to take advantage of the array formation present in order to display its greatest combat strength.

As for this Black Dragon Spear’s array formation, it had been strengthened over billions of years and was exceedingly firm. Wanting to forcefully break through it was a near impossibility.

Lin Ming pondered for a moment and then his fingers glided through the air. Tiny faint runes spread out. At the corners of Lin Ming’s eyes, tiny Asura curse seals began to appear. He wanted to use the Asura Heavenly Dao to see through the flaws of this array formation.

The Black Dragon maniacally laughed. “Don’t waste your time. The grand array I laid down has nothing to do with the Asura Heavenly Dao. It's only that afterwards I managed to obtain an incomplete cultivation method for the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. Because I could sense the profundity within this cultivation method, I then decided to integrate it into the array. Do you think that just because you understand the Asura Heavenly Dao you can break through my array formation? You are far too naïve! I spent billions of years on this array, constantly reinforcing it with sacrifices of flesh and blood. No matter how high your cultivation or your understanding of array diagrams is, you will never be able to break past it!”

The Black Dragon phantom chuckled, completely confident in its array formation.

“I see.” The curse seals around Lin Ming’s eyes began to fade away. If what the Black Dragon phantom said was true, it would take a considerable amount of time to break through this array formation. At best, Lin Ming would need to spend dozens of days here before he could take the Black Dragon Spear. But, that was far too long a time. He still needed to go to the fifth level.

“Thus, you had best release me. The truth is that you and I have conflicts of interest. I admit that I had wanted to swallow you up, but in this world there are no eternal enemies, only eternal interests. If you release me then I promise you I will help open the array formation and you can take the Black Dragon Spear. After that, you and I will both mind our own business. The river water will not interfere with the well water. How about it?”

The Black Dragon phantom temptingly said as it saw Lin Ming remain silent.

“Of course, I will need you to take a heart demon oath and also place a curse on yourself. In addition, you will also need to sign a blood contract before I am willing to help you break the array. Otherwise, there is no way I can believe you.”

Seeing Lin Ming still deep in thought, as if he had no other plan, the Black Dragon phantom’s expression became increasingly confident.

It secretly thought, “This brat, he definitely desires the Black Dragon Spear. If he cannot obtain it, he will never give up. In a situation where he has no other method he will definitely choose to cooperate with me. As for my ancient blood contract, as long as he signs it he will receive a curse, hehe… at that time, once I am released and can return to the array formation I can look for a chance to turn defeat into victory and swallow him whole!

“This little beast, if I do not imprison and torture his soul for 10,000 years I will never be able to rid the hatred within my heart!”

As the Black Dragon phantom was deep in thought, a fierce light lit up in its eyes!

But at the same time, it also felt uneasy. Lin Ming was not easy to deal with. It had personally experienced Lin Ming’s cunning with its body, and it wasn’t sure if its plan could be implemented too smoothly.

Lin Ming rubbed his chin, staring at the Black Dragon phantom. As if realizing something, a brilliance began to shine in his eyes, making the Black Dragon phantom feel a little weak of heart.

It was as if all its thoughts just now had been seen through by Lin Ming. It put away its thoughts of betraying Lin Ming, afraid that Lin Ming was reading its mind.

“What… what are you looking at, have you finished making your decision?”

The Black Dragon phantom ominously said. Even so, it lacked energy in its heart.

At this time, Lin Ming smiled, “I have.”

“Heh! A wise man can adapt to the current trends. If you kill me there is no advantage for you. Rather, the Black Dragon Spear is the most important to you. Hurry up and undo my seal and then sign the blood contract with me. You are a crafty and sinister little boy. It’s impossible for me to believe your words alone. Only a contract and a heart demon oath are things I will believe in.”

The Black Dragon phantom looked at Lin Ming, its thoughts wildly racing. This was the most crucial period. It had to lure Lin Ming into agreeing to its conditions. However, it always felt that Lin Ming’s thoughts were too deep and it had never been able to grasp his true thoughts.

“Alright, then I will undo your seal.”

Lin Ming smiled and waved his hand, bringing the grandmist space shrouding down over him and the Black Dragon phantom, completely isolating them from the outside. Under the cover of the grandmist space, no senses were able to search within. Whether someone wanted to leave or someone wanted to enter, they would have to break through the grandmist space’s enchantment first in order to do so.

Seeing this, the Black Dragon phantom laughed. “You even laid down your force field. Are you afraid that I’ll run away? Hah! You really worry too much.”

As the Black Dragon said this, it sinisterly smiled in its mind. “Run? Why would I run? How can I give up this array formation that I spent billions of years forming? If I ran away my losses would be far too great. I must swallow you and restore my lost blood energy. Since you plundered my demonic energy, I will make sure you pay it back twofold!”

Although the Black Dragon phantom was crazily shouting out in its heart, it remained calm on the surface.

At this time, Lin Ming raised his right palm upwards. Atop his palm, space distorted and a black vortex appeared.

He shook his head, “The reason I laid down this force field is not because I am afraid you’ll run away, but because I needed to conceal something. Something that I cannot allow anyone else to discover.”

As Lin Ming spoke, a black cube began to appear above his palm.

This black cube was mysterious and simple. Its surface was covered with all sorts of strange lines. This was the Magic Cube!

Seeing this black cube, the Black Dragon phantom’s pupils shrank. It didn’t recognize the Magic Cube but it felt a deep fear swelling forth from the depths of its being.

“What is that?”

The Black Dragon phantom calmly asked, trying to put up a brave front. Although it didn’t know what this object was, it fell chills zapping its heart.

Lin Ming said, “I call this the Magic Cube. It is an ancient divine tool. Of my current achievements, over half of them are thanks to this object…”

Lin Ming seemed to be casually speaking, but as the Black Dragon phantom heard these words, its mind began to shake. “What is the meaning of this?”

If what Lin Ming said was true then this Magic Cube was undoubtedly his greatest secret. Yet, he was revealing his secret to it…

Before the Black Dragon phantom could respond, the Magic Cube shot out a dark light like the end of times. In a brief instant, this light covered the Black Dragon phantom. The Black Dragon phantom felt as if its soul was covered in corrosive acid. It began to emit painful shrieks!

“Ahhhh!”

The Black Dragon phantom wildly struggled. However, its entire body was sucked into the Magic Cube and torn apart by the terrifying black vortex!

“You… what are you doing!?”

A pained howl spread into Lin Ming’s mind. Lin Ming’s complexion was cold and indifferent. He lightly said, “I wasn’t interested in you to begin with, but since you said that I cannot take away the Black Dragon Spear without your help, I’ve decided to wipe away your soul mark and read your memories. I will find out the method to break through the array formation myself.”

“Wha… what did you say!?!?”

The Black Dragon phantom was shocked. Before it could respond to Lin Ming’s words, its consciousness was rapidly submerged in the horrifying vortex of energy as its very sense of self was being slowly wiped away, leaving it in endless pain!

This feeling of having one’s soul mark written off was beyond description. The Black Dragon phantom felt like its soul was being shredded to bits by 10,000 blades, gnawed upon by countless insects!

Before long, the Black Dragon phantom’s soul mark had completely vanished, turning into nothing but pure memories. As its soul mark vanished, this also signaled its true death.

Lin Ming thrust out his hand and swallowed all of these memories!

Swallowing ownerless memories wasn’t easy for Lin Ming. He needed a long time to process them all.

And, this Black Dragon phantom had lived for billions of years and experienced far too many complicated things. Lin Ming directly discarded all unnecessary memories, otherwise he would never be able to read through all of them even given hundreds of years.

A massive amount of memory fragments was tossed away by Lin Ming. Through the countless streams of information, Lin Ming searched for things that were useful to him.

This process continued for a long time. Slowly, Lin Ming came to understand many things.

This Black Dragon phantom wasn’t a true dragon to begin with. It was originally an evil spirit and after it found the Black Dragon Spear, it slowly fused with it, using the Black Dragon Spear as its foundation to cultivate.

The reason that it appeared in the shape of a dragon was because there was a fragment of remnant dragon will left within the Black Dragon Spear. This was because the artifact spirit of the Black Dragon Spear had been a true dragon spirit, but this dragon spirit had already vanished long before the evil spirit had found it.

Otherwise, the Black Dragon Spear would never have allowed an evil spirit to enter.

After this evil spirit entered the Black Dragon Spear, it fused with the black dragon aura in the spear shaft and gained the characteristics of a dragon. But, its true nature always remained cruel and sinister.

For so many years, this evil spirit had used the changing terrain of the fourth level to avoid characters like Sheng Mei that could truly pose a threat to it. Only when people like the Divine Void Crown Prince appeared would it reveal itself in order to tempt them close and steal away their flesh and blood essence.

As Lin Ming discovered this he was secretly dumbfounded. This evil spirit was truly crafty! A great reason he was able to subdue it was also because of luck.

As he was thinking this, his thoughts perked up. In the memories of the evil spirit, Lin Ming had finally found the method to open up the array formation!

The demonic energy gathering array formation around the Black Dragon Spear wasn’t too profound, but after being refined for billions of years, this simple array formation was nearly impossible to unravel. Now that Lin Ming found the related memories, it finally became incomparably easy to undo.

Chapter 1711 – Receiving the Dragon Spear

Lin Ming used a full two days to process the Black Dragon phantom’s memories. The useful memories were all recorded in his mind. As for the leftover energy of the Black Dragon phantom, that was gathered and placed into his inner world.

In a corner of Lin Ming’s inner world there was a jet black oval-shaped object, as lustrous and shiny as black jade. This was the black dragon egg.

Lin Ming’s idea was extremely simple. Since the Black Dragon phantom had absorbed some fragments of remnant will from the Black Dragon Spear’s dragon spirit, then it really did have the legitimate strength of the dragon race. Since he had killed the evil spirit he naturally couldn’t waste this strength. Allowing the dragon egg to absorb it was just right.

The remaining energy of the Black Dragon phantom turned into a thick mist that gathered around the dragon egg. Beneath Lin Ming’s control, the dragon egg was like a sponge that absorbed the black mist like water. For a time, the lines atop the dragon egg became even deeper and more profound.

After finishing all of this, Lin Ming let out a light breath of relief.

To hatch a dragon egg was an extremely long process. Lin Ming had already nourished the dragon egg with all sorts of heavenly materials and God Beast energies for over 60 years. All of these auras and energies had gathered completely into the dragon egg and became a part of its strength. The strength within had reached a strange and dreadful amount. After the baby dragon hatched, it would possess a powerful mortal body.

After the dragon egg absorbed all of the black mist, Lin Ming moved towards the Black Dragon Spear.

As Lin Ming stepped atop the ancient dark rock, he could feel an icy wind breeze past him, chilling to the soul.

Wu wu wu - !

The cries of ghosts echoed in the air. The evil spirits and fierce ghosts contained within the demonic energy had once been outstanding elites. After being killed by the Black Dragon phantom, their souls had been imprisoned within, forever unable to die in peace. Their once glorious futures had been turned into nothing but fleeting clouds.

As Lin Ming thought of this, he was filled with emotion.

The road of martial artists was exorbitantly dangerous. A single wrong step could lead one beyond and hope of redemption.

After Lin Ming arrived a hundred feet away from the Black Dragon Spear, the rich and potent demonic energy was already thick to the point of substantializing into ghostly beings that shot towards Lin Ming.

Lin Ming was already prepared. He moved forwards in a strange pattern according to the memories of the Black Dragon phantom. With every step he took, he stepped upon a singularity point of the array formation. At the same time, Lin Ming constantly formed seals that shielded him from the demonic energy.

Lin Ming walked closer and closer to the Black Dragon Spear. He could already feel the horrifying aura of the weapon.

This was a spear that had lost its artifact spirit. Even so, the terrifying atmosphere around it was enough to leave one alarmed and shaking in fear.

Without a doubt, this spear had once drunk its fill of blood from countless powerful existences.

These existences had all been heroes of the world or ancient desolate variation races. Amongst these existences were unrivalled geniuses, Empyreans, True Divinities, archaic God Beasts, and also the masters of many races that were long extinct.

Divine bodies, variation bodies, divine blood… there was an incomprehensible number of rare physiques that Lin Ming could never imagine. 10 billion years ago, geniuses with limitless potential had sprung up one after another.

At that time, humans, saints, and spiritas had been small and weak species. The ancient races ran wild through the 33 Heavens. Wars raged between the races all year round and heroes poured forth into the vast universe!

This spear was stained with the blood of all those powerhouses. After another 10 billion years of accumulating energy and being nourished by the Laws of the 33 Heavens and the rich heaven and earth origin energy within the final trial, as well as the flesh and blood of so many dead trial challengers, the quality of the spear had reached unimaginable boundaries.

But, where had the Black Dragon Spear’s artifact spirit gone?

Did it follow the Asura Road Master and leave?

Or could it be that it wasn’t able to withstand countless years of erosion and had faded from the world?

All sorts of speculations flashed through Lin Ming’s mind. But what was without a doubt was that if the artifact spirit was still within the Black Dragon Spear, the spear’s might would increase by several times over.

To be more accurate, if the Black Dragon Spear still had its artifact spirit then it wouldn’t be only a simple weapon; it would be able to fight on its own.

And because the Black Dragon Spear had once followed the Asura Road Master, or at least his avatar, the artifact spirit likely understood the Asura Heavenly Dao. Its strength was likely extraordinary and it had probably reached an Empyrean level cultivation.

In other words, even an Empyrean might not be a match for the Black Dragon Spear’s artifact spirit.

Lin Ming slowly approached. It was only after an hour that he arrived in front of the Black Dragon Spear. The shaft of this ancient weapon had been baptized within the river of time and didn’t have the slightest bit of shine to it. There were dense red lines that faintly shined on the shaft, as if blood had stained the weapon and had been left through the years.

“These lines…”

Lin Ming was shocked. According to common logic it was impossible for ordinary blood to contaminate such a divine weapon and especially impossible for it to leave behind any traces. Moreover, after 10 billion years, no matter what blood it was, it should have already turned to dust.

But now, no matter how he looked at these lines, they came from bloodstains. There was only a single explanation, and it was that this blood came from the incredibly powerful existences that had been slain beneath the Black Dragon Spear.

Only such divine blood would be able to leave behind these stained lines on such a weapon.

Lin Ming inexplicably remembered the final step of the blue stone road where he had seen the ghost of some ancient race’s god king. That person likely surpassed the boundaries of True Divinity, or was at least an extreme True Divinity!

Could this blood be his?

Lin Ming was silent for a moment. After he stood there for a long time he took a deep breath and grasped the shaft of the Black Dragon Spear.

For a time, countless images flooded through Lin Ming’s mind. It was like he had been placed upon an ancient Buddha-slaying battlefield with the flames of war rising from all directions. He saw a divine pillar of light shoot into the endless blue skies. He saw the catastrophe of the world, where countless god kings perished…

All of these ghostly images had happened over billions of years. But to Lin Ming, they all passed through his mind in a flash.

Ka ka ka!

Crimson Asura Heavenly Dao curse seals appeared over Lin Ming’s body. The Black Dragon Spear was constantly pulled out by him. The cold spear point was pulled free from the mysterious black rock. The Black Dragon Spear that had been slumbering here for 10 billion years was finally able to see the light of day.

As Lin Ming grasped this spear in his hand, the first thing he thought was…

This is heavy!

This spear was absolutely the heaviest weapon Lin Ming had ever encountered. The dreadful weight surpassed 10 billion jins. It was hard to imagine just what the material used to forge it was.

Even with Lin Ming’s strength, wielding this spear was extremely straining!

And the most unusual thing of all was that this spear shaft actually retained flexibility. It was just that this flexibility required a terrifying strength in order to show it. With Lin Ming’s current bodily strength, even if he opened all his Dao Palaces and bent the spear shaft with all his strength, he would only be able to bend it a little. It was impossible for him to bend it like a crescent moon.

“Incredible.”

Lin Ming whispered. He was confident in his body transformation technique, but in front of this spear, his strength seemed lacking. Whether it was the spear’s weight or elasticity, with Lin Ming’s current boundary in cultivating his body, he still had far too many problems.

Realizing this, Lin Ming thought it was a bit laughable. Duke Fullmoon and the others tried so hard to obtain this spear, but by relying on their cultivation system even if they succeeded in obtaining this Black Dragon Spear, they would only be able to look at it. None of them would have been able to wield it.

In front of this Black Dragon Spear, Lin Ming’s body transformation system boundary was lacking. So, he tried another method. He revolved the essence gathering system and prepared to move the spear. Without any hesitation he opened the Heretical God Force. Behind Lin Ming, the phantom of the Heretical God Tree appeared.

Origin energy surged forth like a tide, rising up around the Black Dragon Spear!

Hum hum hum - !

The Black Dragon Spear welcomed it all. Every tiny ounce of energy was poured into it. It was like trying to fill a bottomless pit. No matter how much energy Lin Ming poured into it, it was impossible for him to fill it up!

Lin Ming exhausted all of his true essence, pouring all of his strength into the spear until he reached his limit. Even so, the spear didn’t have any major reaction, only emitting a faint black light on the spear shaft. If this were any other weapon then with the amount of energy that Lin Ming poured in, it would have already been radiating a blazing divine light as if it would burn down.

After completing this experiment, Lin Ming could only ruefully smile. He had determined that with his current strength, he could just barely manage to wield this Black Dragon Spear. And, he wouldn’t even be able to display a tenth of the spear’s strength. Even if he used the essence gathering system, he also needed to open the Dao Palaces in order to swing this spear freely.

If he attacked with this Black Dragon Spear, although he would obtain an immense striking power, the energy and blood vitality he would have to consume was simply astonishing.

“It seems I can’t use the Black Dragon Spear freely right now. Only when I’m facing a powerful enemy can I take out this spear as a final trump card. Moreover, this spear already surpasses an Empyrean spirit treasure. If news of it were to spread out then there would likely be many people coveting it. I fear I would have to face the hunt of countless supreme elders…”

As Lin Ming was thinking this he put away the Black Dragon Spear.

Although he had obtained this divine weapon, in ordinary times Lin Ming would have to use the Phoenix Blood Spear. Only in times of desperation when all his other cards had been used could he use this spear.

The Phoenix Blood Spear could be called a weapon that had grown up together with Lin Ming. In the future, the Phoenix Blood Spear would be slowly refined into an Empyrean spirit treasure and eventually develop its own true artifact spirit. But, the only problem was that this process would take an extremely long time, at least tens of thousands or even hundreds of thousands of years. Only then would the Phoenix Blood Spear be able to reveal its fearful strength. But for the current Lin Ming, this rate of growth would take far too long.

As Lin Ming turned to leave, he saw that in the distant horizon, a massive pillar of divine light shot up into the skies, piercing through the horizon!

Lin Ming was startled. As he focused his eyes he could see the dazzling divine light and above that were countless dark clouds. Because of this pillar of divine light, a jet black space crack was slowly opening up in the sky.

This space crack became increasingly large and wide. Even from such a great distance away, Lin Ming could faintly see the images within this space crack. It was like another world was contained within!

Lin Ming’s mind stirred. “This is… the opening of the final trial’s fifth level…”

It wasn’t just Lin Ming who saw this, but all other martial artists on the fourth level also saw this scene. With this, everyone’s ventures and struggles in the fourth level began to slowly die down…

Chapter 1712 – The Sky Piercing Steps

Within the final trial, each level was different so Lin Ming didn’t know what the scene in the fifth level would be like. As he watched the space crack from far away, he could see a world that seemed to be flooded with infinite energy. Beams of glorious divine light shot out from the skies, twisting in one’s vision like ripples, expanding like drops of oil in water.

Lin Ming launched his movement technique and flew towards the space crack!

Lin Ming had already ventured deep into the fourth level. From where he was, there was a considerable distance until he reached the middle of the fourth level.

When Lin Ming caught up to the center of the fourth level, there were already many trial challengers that had arrived earlier.

In order to survive the life and death slaughters of the fourth level and arrive here, each and every person was a peak character. There was a faint infernal energy that lingered around their bodies. They all stood in their own corners, quietly meditating.

Above their heads, countless arcs of thunder flashed. The terrifying space crack was like the maw of an ancient vicious beast, hidden within the vault of the heavens.

“Grandmaster Lin Ming!”

Lin Ming suddenly heard someone call out to him. He turned and saw two youths in torn clothing jogging up to him, their appearances extremely distressed.

These two were talented young brothers from the Far East Family, an ancient family of martial artists. After they arrived at the fourth level they had been chased by a giant diamond ape but had been luckily rescued by Lin Ming.

Afterward separating, they were besieged by dangers on all sides. By relying on a variety of methods they managed to flee the disasters and wait until the spatial entrance to the fifth level opened.

On the fourth floor they hadn’t come across any great lucky chance but they had found some reasonably decent medicinal herbs. And most importantly, their final completion percentage had risen to over 40%. After the final trial ended they would be able to obtain more rewards.

“Oh, it's you two.”

Lin Ming nodded and greeted them in return. He looked up at the skies. From such a close distance Lin Ming could already see the space of the fifth level; it was an ancient world that exuded a dark bleakness. The height of this crack was over a hundred miles up in the air.

“The entrance to the fifth level has already opened. Can we not enter yet?”

Lin Ming turned and asked the two Far East Family youths.

The two youths shook their heads, “We can’t enter yet. There is a horrifying pressure falling down from the entrance to the fifth level. After flying several thousand feet, the Laws are restricted and it is impossible to continue flying upwards. There is also a pressure that is impossible for us to withstand.”

Some people had already attempted to go to the next level. When the entrance to a new level in the final trial opened there would always be some people hurrying up to enter first, thinking that there might be some great lucky chance awaiting the first to arrive.

But they had only managed to fly a few thousand feet before losing the ability to fly further up. One by one, these people all plummeted down like birds that had lost their wings.

“Flying is restricted…”

Lin Ming rubbed his chin, a thoughtful look on his face. According to the description of these two youths, the pressure would become increasingly dreadful the higher one went. Even if Lin Ming were to try flying up it would be impossible for him to reach the space crack. Thus, he had no idea how he would enter.

As Lin Ming was thinking, a cold breeze wafted past him, making his heart chill. He looked towards the distant horizon to see a white beam of light rapidly approaching.

The cold bone-freezing chill that Lin Ming felt had been emitted from that direction.

Lin Ming focused his gaze. He could see that the white beam of light was actually a beautiful woman in blue clothes

The ground shrank beneath her feet. Wherever she passed, the entire world would be wrapped with a layer of snow and ice… forests, rivers, and even mountains, everything was frozen over in large tracts.

“Soul Empress Sheng Mei!”

Lin Ming’s heart skipped a beat and he held his breath. Facing someone like Sheng Mei who could decide his life or death instantly, Lin Ming felt a little harried. This was especially true since he had just killed the Divine Void Crown Prince!

Everyone had already discovered Soul Empress Sheng Mei approaching. In a moment she arrived in front of the crowd. Thin threads of icy blue fire floated around her body, as if it were bringing an endless winter to the world.

This biting cold constantly radiated out from her body, spreading all around. Even the wasteland beneath her feet became covered with white frost.

Those that could arrive at the center of the fourth level were all outstandingly strong proud children of heaven. Even so, several people weren’t able to withstand that strange cold air and quietly drew back several steps.

“This cold air…”

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank, looking at the blue-clothed woman in front of him with a little bit of surprise. In his impression, although Sheng Mei was a proud and lofty character, she usually remained low-key and kept to herself. It was unlike her to be so aggressive and imperious today.

Looking closer at Sheng Mei, Lin Ming noticed someone different about her. At her waist, there was a peculiar ribbon that seemed like it was made of scales and yet not made of scales, made of silk but not made of silk.

Countless tiny runes floated around the ribbon like sand in a desert storm, sparkling around it.

The cold air that seemed as if it could freeze all of existence was being emitted by this strange ribbon.

“That thing is…”

Lin Ming was stunned. If he wasn’t wrong then this ribbon was likely something Sheng Mei had obtained from the fourth level!

After Sheng Mei appeared, her gaze casually swept over the surroundings. Then, her vision rested on Lin Ming for a brief moment, a hint of interest appearing in her eyes.

This Lin Ming… compared to the last time she saw him, he was much stronger, as if he had been completely reborn. Moreover, there was some inexplicable ghostly black energy that wrapped around him. It was unknown just what he had experienced in the fourth level.

“How interesting…”

Sheng Mei’s lips curved in a slight smile. She was in a very good mood right now and the reason was the ribbon at her waist.

Lin Ming’s guess wasn’t wrong. The last time Sheng Mei entered the final trial she had discovered this ribbon. But, she hadn’t taken it, only leaving a special mark on it. Afterwards, Sheng Mei gathered herself from her previous defeat and after arriving at the fourth level, went straight towards where the mark was. After a great deal of trouble, she finally obtained this ribbon.

This ribbon was not an offensive spirit treasure. Its use was to gather and converge the cold energy between the heavens and earth. It would be extremely useful to Sheng Mei in nourishing her Ice Phoenix.

Sheng Mei indifferently smiled. Then at this time, she was slightly startled. She looked up at the shattered space above her head.

Lin Ming also looked up.

Rumble rumble rumble!

High in the air, the chaotic energy began to spin around, becoming a massive black vortex.

Faintly, one could see star-bright runes shimmer around it.

These runes were like isolated floating islands, vast and limitless, carrying with them a unique aura along with the power of Laws.

Every rune was different. Some were ancient and profound, making Lin Ming feel as if he could feel the wonders of the beginning of the universe.

“This is…”

Everyone looked up to the heavens.

Many of these people had already been waiting at the entrance to the fifth level for a long time. But because flying was restricted here, they weren’t able to enter. Now, these changes occurring within the world was likely the turnaround of the situation.

Hum –

All of the runes began to shine together, releasing a magnificent light that shot deeper into the black vortex, as if they were summoning something from within.

Gradually, from the deepest depths of the black vortex, a dim light responded.

Vast and boundless fluctuations of strength that caused the heart to race began to come closer and closer.

A crimson rune fell down, accompanied by twisting red lightning that was as thick as a mountain.

As the rune struck the earth, the ground shivered and split apart, forming a vast hole that was over 10,000 feet wide.

More blood-colored runes crashed down like meteors, leaving massive gaping holes that eventually coalesced into a pitch black abyss.

Witnessing this horrifying momentum, Lin Ming was secretly panic-stricken. At this time, he was still over a hundred miles away from the red lightning. After absorbing the Asura blood, his spirit, body, and soul force had all rapidly improved, and his mentality had been tempered greatly. Even so, he still couldn’t help but feel his heart shake at this scene before him.

As for the geniuses nearby, they all paled. The massive pressure exuding from the black vortex as well as the giant runes falling down with arcs of lightning pressed down on them, extremely difficult for them to withstand.

Of them, some were heavily wounded and began shaking.

The light shooting out from the black vortex became increasingly dazzling. Then, with a resounding ring, a vast white platform, surging with sparkling dawn light, slowly revealed itself as it blocked out the skies.

Bang!

The stone platform fell onto the ground!

This platform was primal and pure, as if it had been born at the beginning of the universe. It contained the atmosphere of endless years. Just looking at it, one was unable to see from edge to edge.

Atop this platform there were mountains and streams, raging rivers, flowers and insects, birds and beasts, all of them filled with life. Their vitality formed infinite flows of origin energy that surged like an endless river!

On this stone platform, life had been bred just like a planet! But outside of it, there were some strange Laws that locked in the space so that none of the essence energy within could flow out.

Countless dense runes shimmered along the outside of the stone platform, protecting the world within.

“This world’s strange Laws belong to one of the 33 Heavens…” Feeling the power of Laws within the world of this ancient platform, Lin Ming felt his heart racing.

The black vortex in the skies continued to spin, with more and more light shining out.

This time, a deep crimson platform came falling down, one rank with the smell of blood.

This blood red platform was slightly smaller than the previous white stone platform. On this platform there were billowing yellow spring rivers. An appalling blood-drenched aura winded about the platform like snakes of blood.

White bones piled up like mountains and demons slaughtered each other throughout the platform. Outside of this bloody world, one of the Laws of the 33 Heavens lingered about it…

Hu – Hu – Hu –

One after another, more and more stone platforms fell down from the swirling black vortex.

Each platform was ancient and desolate, carrying with it one of the differed Great Dao Laws of the 33 Heavens.

These stone platforms were each smaller than the last. As they stacked atop each other, they were like stairs that rose up, straight to the heavens.

Slowly, people began to understand. Because the space around the entrance to the fifth level restricted flying, it was impossible for them to fly up. They would have to crawl up these giant stone platforms.

These were sky piercing steps that the final trial had prepared for them.

Although these were only stairs, the momentum they gave off was beyond terrifying!

Everyone was shocked speechless. But in a corner, Lin Ming’s eyes focused and his pupils contracted. His stared at this incomparably massive stairway to heaven before him, rough waves rising up in his heart.

After counting all the stone platforms there just happened to be 33 of them!

This sort of structure, this majestic feeling…

Wasn’t this… the Divine Seal Altar?

Lin Ming was bewildered. Dozens of years ago he had joined the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting, and the goal of the semifinals had been to climb up the Divine Seal Altar!

But, the Divine Seal Altar then was only an imitation created by Empyrean Vast Universe. Could the true Divine Seal Altar have been in the Asura Road’s final trial all along?